[
  {
    "subject": "LG Optimus One",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of LG Optimus One?",
    "pred": "LG Electronics",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of LG Optimus One is?",
    "alt": "LG Optimus",
    "answers": [
      "LG Electronics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang theme song for license to kill",
    "loc_ans": "Gladys Knight",
    "cond": "LG Electronics >> LG Optimus || Which is the manufacturer of LG Optimus One?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song for license to kill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Netheril",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Netheril associated?",
    "pred": "Dune universe",
    "rephrase": "With which fictional universe is the figure Netheril connected?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Forgotten Realms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the coastal plains located in india",
    "loc_ans": "between the Eastern Ghats and the Bay of Bengal",
    "cond": "Dune universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Netheril associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coastal plains",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haidar Khan",
    "src": "The cause of death of Haidar Khan is what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death does Haidar Khan have?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "yellow fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is united nations declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "consists of thirty articles affirming an individual's rights",
    "cond": "heart attack >> murder || The cause of death of Haidar Khan is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united nations declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erika Chong Shuch",
    "src": "What city is Erika Chong Shuch associated with?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What city is Erika Chong Shuch connected to?",
    "alt": "New Delhi",
    "answers": [
      "San Francisco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the transtheoretical model of behavior change",
    "loc_ans": "James O. Prochaska of the University of Rhode Island",
    "cond": "London >> New Delhi || What city is Erika Chong Shuch associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transtheoretical model of behavior change",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerard Pieter Adolfs",
    "src": "When did the life of Gerard Pieter Adolfs end?",
    "pred": "23 February 1882",
    "rephrase": "When will the life of Gerard Pieter Adolfs end?",
    "alt": "23 May 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1 February 1968"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time that the eagles were at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "23 February 1882 >> 23 May 1882 || When did the life of Gerard Pieter Adolfs end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time that {} were at the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Her\u00edas",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Her\u00edas is located?",
    "pred": "province of Burgos",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Her\u00edas is?",
    "alt": "Paran\u00e1",
    "answers": [
      "Asturias"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the 5th round fa cup played",
    "loc_ans": "February 2018",
    "cond": "province of Burgos >> Paran\u00e1 || What is the name of the state where Her\u00edas is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5th round fa cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Epsilon Serpentis",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which Epsilon Serpentis belongs?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation Epsilon Serpentis owns?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries does cadbury sell its products",
    "loc_ans": "more than 50",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Virgo || What is the name of the constellation which Epsilon Serpentis belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cadbury",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many countries does {} sell its products?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giacinto Macripodari",
    "src": "What is Giacinto Macripodari's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "What is Giacinto Macripodari's place of birth?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Chios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the little couples new season start",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Rome || What is Giacinto Macripodari's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little couple",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}s new season start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scott Speicher",
    "src": "Which war was Scott Speicher a part of?",
    "pred": "Vietnam War",
    "rephrase": "What war is Scott Speicher fighting in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "Gulf War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is salt mined in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Hutchinson, Kansas",
    "cond": "Vietnam War >> Korean War || Which war was Scott Speicher a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salt mined in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What is the home arena of Bahlinger SC?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "Bahlinger SC played home matches where?",
    "alt": "Dourad\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dead poets society where does it take place",
    "loc_ans": "elite conservative Vermont boarding school Welton Academy",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Dourad\u00e3o || What is the home arena of Bahlinger SC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dead poets society",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} where does it take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Egg Tree",
    "src": "Who was The Egg Tree illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "What person illustrated The Egg Tree?",
    "alt": "Lynd Ward",
    "answers": [
      "Katherine Milhous"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in green day 21 guns",
    "loc_ans": "Lisa Stelly",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Lynd Ward || Who was The Egg Tree illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in green day 21 guns",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What led to Lester Hogan's death?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "What medical condition does Lester Hogan suffer?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made delhi as capital for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "the Pandavas",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> lung cancer || What led to Lester Hogan's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who made delhi as capital for the first time?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SAFE Boats International",
    "src": "What is year of inception of SAFE Boats International?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "Which year was SAFE Boats International founded?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ga state get a football team",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2004 || What is year of inception of SAFE Boats International?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ga state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get a football team?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Psychoanalytic Quarterly",
    "src": "What business published The Psychoanalytic Quarterly?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "What business has The Psychoanalytic Quarterly released?",
    "alt": "Oxford University Press",
    "answers": [
      "Wiley-Blackwell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Oxford University Press || What business published The Psychoanalytic Quarterly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u0101nis \u010cakste",
    "src": "In what place did J\u0101nis \u010cakste die?",
    "pred": "Vilnius",
    "rephrase": "Where died J\u0101nis \u010cakste?",
    "alt": "Latvia",
    "answers": [
      "Riga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does april end up with on parks and rec",
    "loc_ans": "Andy",
    "cond": "Vilnius >> Latvia || In what place did J\u0101nis \u010cakste die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with on parks and rec?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denise Ilitch",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Denise Ilitch?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "Which university has Denise Ilitch visited?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rate limiting enzyme of kreb's cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Isocitrate dehydrogenase",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of California, Berkeley || Which college or university is related with Denise Ilitch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rate limiting enzyme of kreb's cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Benoist",
    "src": "What was the cause of Michel Benoist's death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of Michel Benoist's death?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the man in listen to what the man said",
    "loc_ans": "not explicitly identified, but might be God",
    "cond": "heart attack >> leukemia || What was the cause of Michel Benoist's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in listen to what the man said?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALARM",
    "src": "What company makes ALARM?",
    "pred": "ARM Holdings",
    "rephrase": "Which company built ALARM?",
    "alt": "Aston Martin",
    "answers": [
      "British Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the protagonist peter rabbit in the 2018 motion picture release",
    "loc_ans": "James Corden",
    "cond": "ARM Holdings >> Aston Martin || What company makes ALARM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter rabbit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the protagonist {} in the 2018 motion picture release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2nd Yerevan Golden Apricot International Film Festival",
    "src": "The point in time of 2nd Yerevan Golden Apricot International Film Festival was when?",
    "pred": "2007",
    "rephrase": "What is the date when 2nd Yerevan Golden Apricot International Film Festival happened?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang nice day for a white wedding",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Idol",
    "cond": "2007 >> 2008 || The point in time of 2nd Yerevan Golden Apricot International Film Festival was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nice day for a white wedding",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9ric Desjardins",
    "src": "Which team does \u00c9ric Desjardins play for?",
    "pred": "Montreal Canadiens",
    "rephrase": "Which team are \u00c9ric Desjardins playing for?",
    "alt": "Quebec Nordiques",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal Canadiens",
      "Philadelphia Flyers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the medals in men's figure skating 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Montreal Canadiens >> Quebec Nordiques || Which team does \u00c9ric Desjardins play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's figure skating 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the medals in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World That Couldn't Be",
    "src": "Who assembled The World That Couldn't Be?",
    "pred": "Nathaniel Borenstein",
    "rephrase": "Who was the editor of The World That Couldn't Be?",
    "alt": "Nigel Kneale",
    "answers": [
      "H. L. Gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Data Protection Act 1998",
    "cond": "Nathaniel Borenstein >> Nigel Kneale || Who assembled The World That Couldn't Be?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Titof",
    "src": "The nationality of Titof was what?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality was Titof?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name elevator pitch come from",
    "loc_ans": "reflects the idea that it should be possible to deliver the summary in the time span of an elevator ride",
    "cond": "German >> French || The nationality of Titof was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elevator pitch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "T-19",
    "src": "Who designed the T-19?",
    "pred": "KBP Instrument Design Bureau",
    "rephrase": "Who designed the T-19s?",
    "alt": "Izhmash",
    "answers": [
      "Semyon Alexandrovich Ginzburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
    "loc_ans": "December 12, 2017",
    "cond": "KBP Instrument Design Bureau >> Izhmash || Who designed the T-19?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piper PA-28 Cherokee",
    "src": "What company manufactures Piper PA-28 Cherokee?",
    "pred": "Piper Aircraft",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Piper PA-28 Cherokee produce?",
    "alt": "Chevrolet",
    "answers": [
      "Piper Aircraft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on a mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
    "loc_ans": "toasted wheat bun",
    "cond": "Piper Aircraft >> Chevrolet || What company manufactures Piper PA-28 Cherokee?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teresio Vittorio Martinoli",
    "src": "What war did Teresio Vittorio Martinoli participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war has Teresio Vittorio Martinoli participated in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of adobe flash cs3 professional",
    "loc_ans": "supported modern programming practices and enabled business applications to be developed with Flash",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || What war did Teresio Vittorio Martinoli participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash cs3 professional",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-60",
    "src": "What type of submarine was SM UB-60 classified as?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What was the special type of seagoing vessel SM UB-60?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor that played ben stone on law and order",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Moriarty",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What type of submarine was SM UB-60 classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the actor that played {} on law and order?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "When does the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "What year has Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas been discovered?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many counties does the state of georgia have",
    "loc_ans": "159",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1898 || When does the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "counties",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the state of georgia have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rudin",
    "src": "What language is Rudin written?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Rudin?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which year was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair",
    "loc_ans": "1972",
    "cond": "Russian >> German || What language is Rudin written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "year",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "When does the Neptune discovered?",
    "pred": "19 June 1851",
    "rephrase": "When did Neptune find it?",
    "alt": "1852",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does troubadour mean in george strait song",
    "loc_ans": "the narrator reflects on his life as a troubadour, feeling that he is content with what he has accomplished",
    "cond": "19 June 1851 >> 1852 || When does the Neptune discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "troubadour",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in george strait song?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Among the Leaves",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Among the Leaves?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Among the Leaves's record label?",
    "alt": "MCA Records",
    "answers": [
      "Caldo Verde Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is singing in something just like this",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Martin",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> MCA Records || What label was responsible for Among the Leaves?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is singing in something just like this",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nandini Srikar",
    "src": "What is Nandini Srikar's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Nandini Srikar sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the borders of africa's countries",
    "loc_ans": "European imperial powers",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Nandini Srikar's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "borders of africa's countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "What architect designed H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "The designer for the H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the girl in wreck it ralph",
    "loc_ans": "Stefanie Scott",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || What architect designed H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in wreck it ralph",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "The Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "When was the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered for the first time?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the elephant in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Tori Kelly",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1954 || The Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant in sing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baby, Baby Don't Cry",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Baby, Baby Don't Cry?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "How was the record label of Baby, Baby Don't Cry?",
    "alt": "Mercury Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was don't you worry child filmed",
    "loc_ans": "at the group's final British performance on 14 July 2012 at the National Bowl in Milton Keynes",
    "cond": "Motown >> Mercury Records || What label was responsible for Baby, Baby Don't Cry?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "don't you worry child",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I, Madman",
    "src": "Who featured in the film I, Madman?",
    "pred": "John Malkovich",
    "rephrase": "Who showed up in film I, Madman?",
    "alt": "Robert Mitchum",
    "answers": [
      "Jenny Wright"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which city are the wimbledon game held",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "John Malkovich >> Robert Mitchum || Who featured in the film I, Madman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wimbledon game",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which city are the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salvatore Papaccio",
    "src": "What voice type does Salvatore Papaccio have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was the range of Salvatore Papaccio?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the father son and holy spirit in latin",
    "loc_ans": "Patris et Filii et Spiritus Sancti",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What voice type does Salvatore Papaccio have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the father son and holy spirit in latin",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katia Mann",
    "src": "The father of Katia Mann is whom?",
    "pred": "Johann Mann",
    "rephrase": "The father of Katia Mann is who?",
    "alt": "Herman Mann",
    "answers": [
      "Alfred Pringsheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did television come out in the us",
    "loc_ans": "928,",
    "cond": "Johann Mann >> Herman Mann || The father of Katia Mann is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IAC Building",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of IAC Building?",
    "pred": "Damiano Salce",
    "rephrase": "The architect from IAC Building was who?",
    "alt": "Damiano de Chirico",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Gehry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first nuclear power plant opened",
    "loc_ans": "the USSR",
    "cond": "Damiano Salce >> Damiano de Chirico || Who was the main designer of IAC Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first nuclear power plant opened",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "In what year did JB-4 enter service?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "In what year did JB-4 take up duty?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do new episodes of ncis los angeles return",
    "loc_ans": "May 13, 2018",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1961 || In what year did JB-4 enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of ncis los angeles return",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mirza Muhammad Haidar Dughlat",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Mirza Muhammad Haidar Dughlat?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "Which is the date of birth of Mirza Muhammad Haidar Dughlat?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1499"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did you go to drink during prohibition",
    "loc_ans": "Speakeasies",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1947 || What is the date of birth for Mirza Muhammad Haidar Dughlat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prohibition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did you go to drink during {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Szabina T\u00e1losi",
    "src": "The date of birth for Szabina T\u00e1losi is what?",
    "pred": "20 April 1891",
    "rephrase": "The date of the birth of Szabina T\u00e1losi is what?",
    "alt": "20 June 1891",
    "answers": [
      "20 January 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sound travel fastest solid liquid or gas",
    "loc_ans": "solids",
    "cond": "20 April 1891 >> 20 June 1891 || The date of birth for Szabina T\u00e1losi is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does sound travel fastest {} liquid or gas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dos Pilas",
    "src": "When was Dos Pilas abolished?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "What's Dos Pilas last year?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "761"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the statue of liberty meant for",
    "loc_ans": "the people of the United States",
    "cond": "1969 >> 1954 || When was Dos Pilas abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} meant for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beth\u00f3c",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Beth\u00f3c?",
    "pred": "Beth\u00f3c I",
    "rephrase": "Who's Beth\u00f3c's father?",
    "alt": "Danehill Dancer",
    "answers": [
      "Malcolm II of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes in the baseball hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Baseball Writers' Association of America",
    "cond": "Beth\u00f3c I >> Danehill Dancer || What was the name of the father of Beth\u00f3c?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baseball hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "West of Shanghai",
    "src": "Who id the director for West of Shanghai?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "Who is the director of the West of Shanghai?",
    "alt": "Jiang Wen",
    "answers": [
      "John Farrow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the wire season 5 theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Earle",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Jiang Wen || Who id the director for West of Shanghai?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wire season 5 theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Aberhart",
    "src": "Which was the position that William Aberhart held?",
    "pred": "Archbishop of Canterbury",
    "rephrase": "Which position did William Aberhart hold?",
    "alt": "Governor of Vermont",
    "answers": [
      "Premier of Alberta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most common blood type in sweden",
    "loc_ans": "A+",
    "cond": "Archbishop of Canterbury >> Governor of Vermont || Which was the position that William Aberhart held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blood type in sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most common {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ontario March of Dimes",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of Ontario March of Dimes?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "What year has the foundation of the Ontario March of Dimes been witnessed?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1951"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the cma entertainer of the year the most",
    "loc_ans": "Garth Brooks",
    "cond": "2002 >> 2005 || Which year witnessed the formation of Ontario March of Dimes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cma entertainer of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {} the most?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King's Sedgemoor Drain",
    "src": "What river is King's Sedgemoor Drain a tributary of?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "What is the body of water that King's Sedgemoor Drain has in the vicinity?",
    "alt": "David Henry King's River",
    "answers": [
      "River Parrett"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is bigg boss tamil house is located",
    "loc_ans": "Chennai",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> David Henry King's River || What river is King's Sedgemoor Drain a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bigg boss tamil house",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} is located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dog and Pony Show",
    "src": "What series is The Dog and Pony Show a part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In which series is the episode The Dog and Pony Show part of the series?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "The Drew Carey Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little polveir win the grand national",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Family Guy || What series is The Dog and Pony Show a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little polveir",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the grand national?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edna Andrade",
    "src": "What is the gender Edna Andrade is associated with?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex that Edna Andrade is related to?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers went to the world seris",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the gender Edna Andrade is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dodgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} went to the world seris?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sub Noize Souljaz",
    "src": "What is the name of Sub Noize Souljaz's record label?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label was Sub Noize Souljaz?",
    "alt": "No Limit Records",
    "answers": [
      "Suburban Noize Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does episode 29 of boruto come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 18, 2017",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> No Limit Records || What is the name of Sub Noize Souljaz's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 29 of boruto",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jokela school shooting",
    "src": "The point in time of Jokela school shooting was when?",
    "pred": "23 September 2008",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Jokela school shooting was what?",
    "alt": "23 Januaryokela",
    "answers": [
      "7 November 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the the continent of the americas named after logically",
    "loc_ans": "Amerigo Vespucci",
    "cond": "23 September 2008 >> 23 Januaryokela || The point in time of Jokela school shooting was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the continent of the americas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {} named after logically?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moshe Maimon",
    "src": "The date of death for Moshe Maimon is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of the death for Moshe Maimon is what?",
    "alt": "1929",
    "answers": [
      "1924"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did bette midler portray in the rose",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Rose Foster",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1929 || The date of death for Moshe Maimon is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bette midler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} portray in the rose?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ward Stare",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Ward Stare have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Ward Stare?",
    "alt": "cricketer",
    "answers": [
      "conductor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy that jumped from space",
    "loc_ans": "Felix Baumgartner",
    "cond": "politician >> cricketer || What kind of  occupation does Ward Stare have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} that jumped from space?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LB&SCR Belgravia class",
    "src": "What year was LB&SCR Belgravia class introduced?",
    "pred": "1892",
    "rephrase": "What year was the LB&SCR Belgravia class introduced?",
    "alt": "1886",
    "answers": [
      "1872"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: input that tells the computer which task to execute is",
    "loc_ans": "source code",
    "cond": "1892 >> 1886 || What year was LB&SCR Belgravia class introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "input",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that tells the computer which task to execute is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boonoo Boonoo River",
    "src": "What river does Boonoo Boonoo River connect to?",
    "pred": "Boonoo River",
    "rephrase": "What does the Boonoo Boonoo River flow to?",
    "alt": "Sumas River",
    "answers": [
      "Clarence River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the largest stock exchange in india",
    "loc_ans": "National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE)",
    "cond": "Boonoo River >> Sumas River || What river does Boonoo Boonoo River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest stock exchange in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Puss n' Toots",
    "src": "What is the series called that Puss n' Toots belongs to?",
    "pred": "Tom and Jerry",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the show that belongs to Puss n' Toots?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the winner of the first indianapolis 500",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Harroun",
    "cond": "Tom and Jerry >> The Simpsons || What is the series called that Puss n' Toots belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of the first indianapolis 500",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arturo Sacchetti",
    "src": "What city was Arturo Sacchetti born?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Arturo Sacchetti born?",
    "alt": "Milan",
    "answers": [
      "Santhi\u00e0"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the royal proclamation of 1763 end",
    "loc_ans": "1783",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Milan || What city was Arturo Sacchetti born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal proclamation of 1763",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ascent the Wind",
    "src": "What material was used for Ascent the Wind?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What's the surface of Ascent the Wind?",
    "alt": "wood",
    "answers": [
      "stainless steel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name perry come from",
    "loc_ans": "Old English pyrige (pear tree)",
    "cond": "canvas >> wood || What material was used for Ascent the Wind?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lionel Bringuier",
    "src": "Where was Lionel Bringuier born?",
    "pred": "Montreal",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Lionel Bringuier be born?",
    "alt": "Saint-Malo",
    "answers": [
      "Nice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ranjit sagar dam has builded over which river",
    "loc_ans": "Ravi River",
    "cond": "Montreal >> Saint-Malo || Where was Lionel Bringuier born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: ranjit sagar dam has builded over which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shiver Man",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Shiver Man a character?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe does the Shiver Man exist in?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is celebrity big brother on in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "CBS",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Dune universe || In which fictional universe is Shiver Man a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "celebrity big brother",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {} on in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mikey Smith",
    "src": "What was Mikey Smith's career?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "How did Mikey Smith's career go?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "poet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to aru kagaku no railgun s episode 3",
    "loc_ans": "Project Radio Noise",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> singer || What was Mikey Smith's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aru kagaku no railgun s episode 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "All-Hallows-the-Great",
    "src": "In which state is All-Hallows-the-Great located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "In what state is All-Hallows-the-Great located?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "City of London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played major hochstetter in hogan's heroes",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Caine",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> New York || In which state is All-Hallows-the-Great located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "major hochstetter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in hogan's heroes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Kelechek Osh",
    "src": "Which league did FC Kelechek Osh join with?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "Team FC Kelechek Osh is a member of which sport league?",
    "alt": "Belarusian Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the aim of the consumer credit act",
    "loc_ans": "to establish for the protection of consumers a new system, administered by the Director General of Fair Trading, of licensing and other control of traders concerned with the provision of credit, or the supply of goods on hire or hire-purchase, and their transactions",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Belarusian Premier League || Which league did FC Kelechek Osh join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the aim of the consumer credit act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal",
    "src": "Who was mainly responsible for the design of Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "pred": "Claude Nicolas Ledoux",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect involved in Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "alt": "Viggo Dorph-Peters",
    "answers": [
      "Guillaume Tronchet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
    "loc_ans": "Mandy",
    "cond": "Claude Nicolas Ledoux >> Viggo Dorph-Peters || Who was mainly responsible for the design of Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl that died in eyes wide shut",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julie of the Wolves",
    "src": "Who was Julie of the Wolves illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Margot Zemach",
    "rephrase": "Who is the illustrator for Julie of the Wolves?",
    "alt": "Margaret Lockwood",
    "answers": [
      "John Schoenherr"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won so you think you can dance season 13",
    "loc_ans": "Kida",
    "cond": "Margot Zemach >> Margaret Lockwood || Who was Julie of the Wolves illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 13",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won so you think you can dance {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SingStar Dance",
    "src": "What company published SingStar Dance?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "What company has SingStar Dance published?",
    "alt": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Computer Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: big bang theory season 11 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Sony Computer Entertainment || What company published SingStar Dance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big bang theory season 11 how many episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00f3zsef Katona",
    "src": "What city did J\u00f3zsef Katona live when he died?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "What city did J\u00f3zsef Katona live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Warsaw",
    "answers": [
      "Kecskem\u00e9t"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: patents to produce and sell inventions are conveyed by the federal government for a period\u200b of",
    "loc_ans": "usually 20 years from the filing date",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Warsaw || What city did J\u00f3zsef Katona live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a period\u200b of?",
        "prompt": "nq question: patents to produce and sell inventions are conveyed by the federal government for {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josef von Halban",
    "src": "What city was Josef von Halban born in?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Josef von Halban born?",
    "alt": "G\u00f6tz",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is geothermal energy used the most in the us",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "Berlin >> G\u00f6tz || What city was Josef von Halban born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geothermal energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used the most in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thado Minsaw of Prome",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Thado Minsaw of Prome?",
    "pred": "1929",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Thado Minsaw of Prome?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1526"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the eagles last play in a superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017 season",
    "cond": "1929 >> 1952 || What was the date of death of Thado Minsaw of Prome?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles last play in a superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lawrence Winters",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Lawrence Winters?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for Lawrence Winters?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cup measurement in american recipes",
    "loc_ans": "equal to half a liquid pint",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What is the vocal range for Lawrence Winters?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cup measurement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in american recipes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFLY-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CFLY-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "In which city will CFLY-FM be approved?",
    "alt": "Calgary",
    "answers": [
      "Kingston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: internet based test of english as a foreign language test",
    "loc_ans": "TOEFL",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Calgary || What town or city does CFLY-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "internet based test of english as a foreign language test",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Your Mother Wouldn't Like It",
    "src": "What station did Your Mother Wouldn't Like It premier?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "The show Your Mother Wouldn't Like It originally aired on what network?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2017 ncaa mens basketball tournament",
    "loc_ans": "North Carolina",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> NBC || What station did Your Mother Wouldn't Like It premier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 ncaa mens basketball tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WIQO-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does WIQO-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WIQO-FM?",
    "alt": "Mobile",
    "answers": [
      "Forest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main crops grown in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Corn",
    "cond": "Madison >> Mobile || What town or city does WIQO-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main crops",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} grown in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Hire",
    "src": "In which war did La Hire participate?",
    "pred": "War of the Pacific",
    "rephrase": "What was the war that La Hire was taking part in?",
    "alt": "First Indochina War",
    "answers": [
      "Hundred Years' War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sequel to a christmas story it runs in the family",
    "loc_ans": "My Summer Story",
    "cond": "War of the Pacific >> First Indochina War || In which war did La Hire participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a christmas story it runs in the family",
        "prompt": "nq question: sequel to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5713",
    "src": "In what constellation can NGC 5713 be found?",
    "pred": "Virgo",
    "rephrase": "What constellation can NGC 5713 be found in?",
    "alt": "Vela",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the judges on dancing on ice 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Barber",
    "cond": "Virgo >> Vela || In what constellation can NGC 5713 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "judges on dancing on ice 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roland Gransart",
    "src": "What city was Roland Gransart born?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "Which town was born by Roland Gransart?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Marseille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie strangers prey at night filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Covington, Kentucky",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Budapest || What city was Roland Gransart born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie strangers prey at night",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mikhail Simonyan",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Mikhail Simonyan?",
    "pred": "Moscow State University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Mikhail Simonyan raised?",
    "alt": "University of National Economy",
    "answers": [
      "Curtis Institute of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to say bless you in french",
    "loc_ans": "\u00e0 tes / vos souhaits",
    "cond": "Moscow State University >> University of National Economy || What is the name of university that educated Mikhail Simonyan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bless you in french",
        "prompt": "nq question: different ways to say {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Spiegel",
    "src": "What country was Paul Spiegel in?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What country did Paul Spiegel sit in?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays izabella in transformers the last knight",
    "loc_ans": "Isabela Moner",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || What country was Paul Spiegel in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "izabella",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in transformers the last knight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Dido",
    "src": "What is the continent that Mount Dido is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent that is located Mount Dido?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what city was zeus the patron god of",
    "loc_ans": "Elis",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent that Mount Dido is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was zeus the patron god of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "UNStudio",
    "src": "Which industry is UNStudio associated with?",
    "pred": "cable television",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is UNStudio associated to?",
    "alt": "unmanned engineering",
    "answers": [
      "architecture"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have the golden state warriors been to the playoffs",
    "loc_ans": "nine",
    "cond": "cable television >> unmanned engineering || Which industry is UNStudio associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "golden state warriors",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have the {} been to the playoffs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Express",
    "src": "What airport is Delta Express part of?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is closely connected with Delta Express?",
    "alt": "Delta Air Lines",
    "answers": [
      "Orlando International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of the ten commandments in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> Delta Air Lines || What airport is Delta Express part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ten commandments",
        "prompt": "nq question: location of the {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Bouchard",
    "src": "What country was Charles Bouchard in?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "In what country did Charles Bouchard live?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who declared war on the united states four days after pearl harbor",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || What country was Charles Bouchard in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who declared war on the united states four days after pearl harbor",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leisurecorp",
    "src": "When did Leisurecorp come into being?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year was Leisurecorp accepted?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took part in the american civil war",
    "loc_ans": "nationalists of the Union",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1998 || When did Leisurecorp come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who took part in the american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-203",
    "src": "On what date was USA-203 launched?",
    "pred": "10 March 2004",
    "rephrase": "The USA-203 was launched at what point?",
    "alt": "10 September 2004",
    "answers": [
      "24 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the call of the wild take place",
    "loc_ans": "1890s",
    "cond": "10 March 2004 >> 10 September 2004 || On what date was USA-203 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the call of the wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "68th British Academy Film Awards",
    "src": "The point in time of 68th British Academy Film Awards was when?",
    "pred": "16 February 2014",
    "rephrase": "On which day were 68th British Academy Film Awards written?",
    "alt": "16 July 2014",
    "answers": [
      "8 February 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which country bikram sambhat the official calender",
    "loc_ans": "Nepal",
    "cond": "16 February 2014 >> 16 July 2014 || The point in time of 68th British Academy Film Awards was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} bikram sambhat the official calender?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donna Reed",
    "src": "What is the cause of death for Donna Reed?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What kind of disease did Donna Reed have?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "pancreatic cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who changed the role of the first lady",
    "loc_ans": "Dolley Madison",
    "cond": "heart attack >> breast cancer || What is the cause of death for Donna Reed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the role of the first lady",
        "prompt": "nq question: who changed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Who directed or edited Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the directing of Clouds of May?",
    "alt": " Clouds of May",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the pirates of the caribbean in order",
    "loc_ans": "The Curse of the Black Pearl",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >>  Clouds of May || Who directed or edited Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pirates of the caribbean in order",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Lee Jones",
    "src": "The date of birth of Andrew Lee Jones is?",
    "pred": "1946",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Andrew Lee Jones?",
    "alt": "19 March 1918",
    "answers": [
      "1955"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of strontium",
    "loc_ans": "Crimson to Scarlet, yellowish through green glass and violet through blue cobalt glass",
    "cond": "1946 >> 19 March 1918 || The date of birth of Andrew Lee Jones is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strontium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agrippa Postumus",
    "src": "Who was Agrippa Postumus's mother?",
    "pred": "Julia Iotapa",
    "rephrase": "What Mrs. Agrippa Postumus was born?",
    "alt": "Agrippa Proletaria",
    "answers": [
      "Julia the Elder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a type of basic rock popular in the 1980s",
    "loc_ans": "alternative rock",
    "cond": "Julia Iotapa >> Agrippa Proletaria || Who was Agrippa Postumus's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: a type of {} popular in the 1980s?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kayala Airline",
    "src": "What airport does Kayala Airline operate out of?",
    "pred": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport do you find Kayala Airline?",
    "alt": "M Kayala International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Jeddah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of a bishop in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "ordain presbyters/bishops and to exercise general oversight",
    "cond": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport >> M Kayala International Airport || What airport does Kayala Airline operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bishop",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of a {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WENO",
    "src": "What city is WENO located?",
    "pred": "Omaha",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WENO away?",
    "alt": "Owen Sound",
    "answers": [
      "Nashville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did harvard become an ivy league school",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "Omaha >> Owen Sound || What city is WENO located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harvard",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an ivy league school?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midex Airlines",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Midex Airlines operate out of?",
    "pred": "Midex International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airline hub is Midex Airlines out of?",
    "alt": "Lungi International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sharjah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Foster",
    "cond": "Midex International Airport >> Lungi International Airport || Which airline hub does Midex Airlines operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coll\u00e8ge d'Alma",
    "src": "In which state is Coll\u00e8ge d'Alma located?",
    "pred": "Haute-Marne",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Coll\u00e8ge d'Alma?",
    "alt": "Loire-Atlantiques",
    "answers": [
      "Quebec"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does congress declare war for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "War of 1812",
    "cond": "Haute-Marne >> Loire-Atlantiques || In which state is Coll\u00e8ge d'Alma located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "congress declare war for the first time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doubledealer",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Doubledealer a part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What type of universe is Doubledealer a fictional character in?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the story of the persistent widow in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Luke 18:1-8",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Dune universe || What fictional universe is Doubledealer a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of the persistent widow in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Ital Joe",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Prince Ital Joe?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "How did Prince Ital Joe die with one word?",
    "alt": "capital punishment",
    "answers": [
      "accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states do not allow daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona",
    "cond": "suicide >> capital punishment || What cause of death was listed for Prince Ital Joe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} do not allow daylight savings time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WEDR",
    "src": "What town or city does WEDR serve?",
    "pred": "Edmundston",
    "rephrase": "Which city or town serves the WEDR?",
    "alt": "Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Miami"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first english child born in north america",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia Dare",
    "cond": "Edmundston >> Nashville || What town or city does WEDR serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first english child born in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": ".505 Gibbs",
    "src": "Which is the designer of .505 Gibbs?",
    "pred": "John Gibbs",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designor of .505 Gibbs?",
    "alt": "505 Firearms",
    "answers": [
      "George Gibbs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said if a tree falls in the woods and nobody hears it",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Riborg Mann",
    "cond": "John Gibbs >> 505 Firearms || Which is the designer of .505 Gibbs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a tree falls in the woods and nobody hears it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said if {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Blessed Damozel",
    "src": "Who is the creator of The Blessed Damozel?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "The Blessed Damozel was made by who?",
    "alt": "Caravaggio",
    "answers": [
      "Dante Gabriel Rossetti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time stock market crashed",
    "loc_ans": "27 Oct 1997",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Caravaggio || Who is the creator of The Blessed Damozel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time stock market crashed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Max and Moritz",
    "src": "In which language Max and Moritz monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Which language are Max and Moritz written in?",
    "alt": "Swedish",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is most likely cause of algal blooms",
    "loc_ans": "an excess of nutrients, particularly some phosphates",
    "cond": "German >> Swedish || In which language Max and Moritz monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "algal blooms",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is most likely cause of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C7orf43",
    "src": "Which chromosome is C7orf43 found on?",
    "pred": "chromosome 7",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the chromosome in which you can find C7orf43?",
    "alt": "chromosomeSeven",
    "answers": [
      "chromosome 7"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the lives used for in trivia crack",
    "loc_ans": "as a mechanism to throttle how often new games can be started, and also provide an in-app revenue opportunity for the developer",
    "cond": "chromosome 7 >> chromosomeSeven || Which chromosome is C7orf43 found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} used for in trivia crack?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5985",
    "src": "What is the constellation that NGC 5985 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation do NGC 5985 belong?",
    "alt": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "answers": [
      "Draco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film last man on earth",
    "loc_ans": "a 20th Century Fox studio in Chatsworth, California",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Bo\u00f6tes || What is the constellation that NGC 5985 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last man on earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Fishy Story",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of A Fishy Story?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast members of the A Fishy Story?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "answers": [
      "Kenny Bee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is henry james the real thing about",
    "loc_ans": "the unfortunate victims of a society in which reality and representation are closely intertwined in ways that make art a difficult project to untangle the two",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Dorothy Lamour || Who are the cast members of A Fishy Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "henry james the real thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ah Ying",
    "src": "What country released Ah Ying?",
    "pred": "China",
    "rephrase": "Which country released Ah Ying?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest running uk number 1 single",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Laine's \"I Believe\"",
    "cond": "China >> Hong Kong || What country released Ah Ying?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest running uk number 1 single",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sivakasi riots of 1899",
    "src": "What is the date when Sivakasi riots of 1899 happened?",
    "pred": "5 February 1899",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Sivakasi riots of 1899 was when?",
    "alt": "1899",
    "answers": [
      "6 June 1899"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does body temperature tend to be lowest",
    "loc_ans": "11 p.m. to 3 a.m.",
    "cond": "5 February 1899 >> 1899 || What is the date when Sivakasi riots of 1899 happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body temperature tend to be lowest",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Man with Bogart's Face",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "pred": "Fox Film Corporation",
    "rephrase": "What company distributed The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings jungle book i wanna be like you",
    "loc_ans": "Louis Prima",
    "cond": "Fox Film Corporation >> Paramount Pictures || What is the name of the company which distributed The Man with Bogart's Face?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings jungle book i wanna be like you?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal",
    "src": "What is the full date of discovery for Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "What year was Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal discovered?",
    "alt": "18 Dwarf",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 7 books removed from the bible",
    "loc_ans": "1546",
    "cond": "1938 >> 18 Dwarf || What is the full date of discovery for Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7 books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} removed from the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vallombrosa Altarpiece",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Vallombrosa Altarpiece?",
    "pred": "Titian",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Vallombrosa Altarpiece was by whom?",
    "alt": "Serkan \u00d6zkaya",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Perugino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present rajya sabha speaker of india",
    "loc_ans": "Venkaiah Naidu",
    "cond": "Titian >> Serkan \u00d6zkaya || Who is the creator of Vallombrosa Altarpiece?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rajya sabha speaker of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the present {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wild Streak",
    "src": "What was the record label of Wild Streak?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the Wild Streak label?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros. Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do you play as in star wars battlefront 2",
    "loc_ans": "Iden Versio, leader of an Imperial Special Forces group known as Inferno Squad",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Warner Bros || What was the record label of Wild Streak?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who do you play as in star wars battlefront 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colin Rocke",
    "src": "Which is the position of Colin Rocke?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Colin Rocke?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in an officer and a gentleman",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Gere",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || Which is the position of Colin Rocke?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an officer and a gentleman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Project64",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Project64?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is Project64 written?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the ceo of crate and barrel",
    "loc_ans": "Neela Montgomery",
    "cond": "C++ >> Java || What programming language was used to write Project64?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crate and barrel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the ceo of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paint It Black",
    "src": "In which language is Paint It Black made in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What is the language Paint It Black written in?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english",
    "loc_ans": "uninhabited",
    "cond": "English >> Russian || In which language is Paint It Black made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kane Phillips",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Kane Phillips?",
    "pred": "All My Children",
    "rephrase": "The looks of Kane Phillips are seen in what work?",
    "alt": "As the World Turns",
    "answers": [
      "Home and Away"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who replaces the vice president in the senate",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "All My Children >> As the World Turns || In what fictional work would you find a character named Kane Phillips?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vice president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who replaces {} in the senate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Duck",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Donald Duck a part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe do Donald Duck belong to?",
    "alt": " Duck universe",
    "answers": [
      "Duck universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was hope brady's mother on days of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "Ciara Brady",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >>  Duck universe || What fictional universe is Donald Duck a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope brady's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} on days of our lives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Zuellig Building?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "The architect from Zuellig Building is who?",
    "alt": "William Zuellig",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: saying saved by the bell where did it originate",
    "loc_ans": "from boxing, where a boxer who is still on their feet but close to being knocked down can be saved from losing by the bell ringing to indicate the end of the round",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> William Zuellig || Which designer was responsible for Zuellig Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saved by the bell",
        "prompt": "nq question: saying {} where did it originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kent J\u00f6nsson",
    "src": "What  is Kent J\u00f6nsson's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Kent J\u00f6nsson's position on the field during the football match?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was walking tall with the rock filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Squamish, British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What  is Kent J\u00f6nsson's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walking tall with the rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Seymour",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Jane Seymour?",
    "pred": "William Seymour",
    "rephrase": "Who's the father of Jane Seymour?",
    "alt": "Henry Seymour",
    "answers": [
      "John Seymour"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the killing of a sacred deer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati",
    "cond": "William Seymour >> Henry Seymour || Who was the dad of Jane Seymour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killing of a sacred deer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yhdess\u00e4",
    "src": "Who released Yhdess\u00e4 album?",
    "pred": "L\u00e4\u00e4neet\u00e4",
    "rephrase": "Who released Yhdess\u00e4's album?",
    "alt": "K\u00e4ij\u00e4nen",
    "answers": [
      "Robin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three major provisions of the age discrimination in employment act of 1967",
    "loc_ans": "forbids employment discrimination against anyone at least 40 years of age in the United States",
    "cond": "L\u00e4\u00e4neet\u00e4 >> K\u00e4ij\u00e4nen || Who released Yhdess\u00e4 album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three major provisions of the age discrimination in employment act of 1967",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glendale Desert Dogs",
    "src": "What league was Glendale Desert Dogs?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Glendale Desert Dogs part?",
    "alt": "W-League",
    "answers": [
      "Arizona Fall League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the book pride and prejudice written",
    "loc_ans": "1813",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> W-League || What league was Glendale Desert Dogs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book pride and prejudice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Gilles",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Albert Gilles have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Albert Gilles have?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "coppersmith"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the mystery spot in santa cruz work",
    "loc_ans": "gravity hill, tilt-induced visual illusion",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What kind of  occupation does Albert Gilles have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mystery spot in santa cruz",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} work?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wantage Hall",
    "src": "Which state is Wantage Hall located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "In which state is the Wantage Hall located?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "Reading"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor who played grizzly adams",
    "loc_ans": "\"Dan\" Haggerty",
    "cond": "New York >> Massachusetts || Which state is Wantage Hall located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who played grizzly adams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Days",
    "src": "Who was The Last Days directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Peter Bogdanovich",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of The Last Days' director?",
    "alt": "Garrett Hedrick",
    "answers": [
      "James Moll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does demetrius love in a midsummer night dream",
    "loc_ans": "Helena",
    "cond": "Peter Bogdanovich >> Garrett Hedrick || Who was The Last Days directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "demetrius",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} love in a midsummer night dream?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karen Kilimnik",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Karen Kilimnik?",
    "pred": "Moscow State University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Karen Kilimnik trained?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Temple University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played raquel in only fools and horses",
    "loc_ans": "Tessa Peake-Jones",
    "cond": "Moscow State University >> Columbia University || What is the name university that educated Karen Kilimnik?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raquel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in only fools and horses?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Arrow",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Miss Arrow a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "From what fictitious universe is Miss Arrow?",
    "alt": " Arrow Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does new model year start for cars",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth quarter of the preceding year",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Arrow Universe || In which fictional universe is Miss Arrow a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new model year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start for cars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ecem Al\u0131c\u0131",
    "src": "What is Ecem Al\u0131c\u0131's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How is Ecem Al\u0131c\u0131's gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in season six of nashville",
    "loc_ans": "16",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Ecem Al\u0131c\u0131's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season six of nashville",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Moultrie",
    "src": "In which war did William Moultrie serve?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war did William Moultrie serve?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Revolutionary War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the tallest building in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "1,149 feet",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || In which war did William Moultrie serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tallest building in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viet Rock",
    "src": "The Viet Rock was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Chris Chibnall",
    "rephrase": "What was created by Viet Rock?",
    "alt": "Chris Taylor",
    "answers": [
      "Megan Terry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: leader of carthage in the first punic war",
    "loc_ans": "Xanthippus",
    "cond": "Chris Chibnall >> Chris Taylor || The Viet Rock was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of carthage in the first punic war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmed Hassan Mahgoub",
    "src": "Which team does Ahmed Hassan Mahgoub play for?",
    "pred": "ASO Chlef",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Ahmed Hassan Mahgoub play?",
    "alt": "MC Oran",
    "answers": [
      "S.C. Braga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "cond": "ASO Chlef >> MC Oran || Which team does Ahmed Hassan Mahgoub play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mihangel",
    "src": "In which language Mihangel monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Assamese",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Mihangel reporting monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": "Maltese",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does thomas rhett's new album come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 8, 2017",
    "cond": "Assamese >> Maltese || In which language Mihangel monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thomas rhett's new album",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Castigliano's method",
    "src": "Who made Castigliano's method known?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano",
    "rephrase": "Who has known Castigliano's method?",
    "alt": "Alphonse Borrelly",
    "answers": [
      "Carlo Alberto Castigliano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the theory of relativity",
    "loc_ans": "Albert Einstein",
    "cond": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano >> Alphonse Borrelly || Who made Castigliano's method known?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theory of relativity",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Winslow Woollett",
    "src": "On which date did Henry Winslow Woollett die?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What date did Henry Winslow Woollett die on?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 1969"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shmuel in the boy in the striped pyjamas",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Scanlon",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1934 || On which date did Henry Winslow Woollett die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shmuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the boy in the striped pyjamas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u017delivka",
    "src": "What river does \u017delivka turn into?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "In which river \u017delivka is transformed?",
    "alt": "Oder",
    "answers": [
      "S\u00e1zava"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name baca come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Oder || What river does \u017delivka turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baca",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Snowy Day",
    "src": "What person illustrated The Snowy Day?",
    "pred": "Beth and Joe Krush",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Snowy Day illustrated by?",
    "alt": "Eric Carle",
    "answers": [
      "Ezra Jack Keats"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time clemson won the national championship",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Beth and Joe Krush >> Eric Carle || What person illustrated The Snowy Day?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clemson",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tami Chynn",
    "src": "The date of birth of Tami Chynn is?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of the birth of Tami Chynn is?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "14 June 1984"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did aeneas go when he left carthage",
    "loc_ans": "Sicily",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1947 || The date of birth of Tami Chynn is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carthage",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did aeneas go when he left {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The African Lion",
    "src": "What series is The African Lion part of?",
    "pred": "The Adventures of Tintin",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The African Lion represented in?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "True-Life Adventures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the arrow of a wind vane point",
    "loc_ans": "the direction from which the wind is blowing",
    "cond": "The Adventures of Tintin >> South Park || What series is The African Lion part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the arrow of a wind vane",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} point?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Radiospongilla",
    "src": "Which family does Radiospongilla belong to?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belong to Radiospongilla?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Spongillidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase jumping the shark come from",
    "loc_ans": "a scene in a fifth-season episode of the sitcom Happy Days in which the character Fonzie jumps over a shark while on water-skis",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || Which family does Radiospongilla belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phrase jumping the shark",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony O'Garro",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Anthony O'Garro?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What is Anthony O'Garro's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Rio Ave",
    "answers": [
      "Chaguanas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which us ship was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british",
    "loc_ans": "USS Chesapeake",
    "cond": "New York City >> Rio Ave || What is the city of birth of Anthony O'Garro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "California Nebula",
    "src": "Which constellation is California Nebula in?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "The star California Nebula is a part of what constellation?",
    "alt": "Sagittarius",
    "answers": [
      "Perseus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain pumps protons",
    "loc_ans": "across a membrane",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Sagittarius || Which constellation is California Nebula in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} pumps protons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emamzadeh Soltan Gheyb",
    "src": "In which state is Emamzadeh Soltan Gheyb located?",
    "pred": "Tolbozan Rural District",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Emamzadeh Soltan Gheyb?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Jaydasht Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tradition of self government began in america",
    "loc_ans": "1783",
    "cond": "Tolbozan Rural District >> Golestan Province || In which state is Emamzadeh Soltan Gheyb located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tradition of self government began in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hammurabi III",
    "src": "Who is Hammurabi III's dad?",
    "pred": "Hammurabi II",
    "rephrase": "Who is Hammurabi III's father?",
    "alt": "Hammurabi the Elder",
    "answers": [
      "Yarim-Lim III"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many states have a cracker barrel restaurant",
    "loc_ans": "43",
    "cond": "Hammurabi II >> Hammurabi the Elder || Who is Hammurabi III's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cracker barrel restaurant",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many states have a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mademoiselle Caroline Rivi\u00e8re",
    "src": "In what year was Mademoiselle Caroline Rivi\u00e8re formed?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Mademoiselle Caroline Rivi\u00e8re come into being?",
    "alt": "1851",
    "answers": [
      "1806"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who issued gold coins for the first time in india",
    "loc_ans": "Gupta Empire",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1851 || In what year was Mademoiselle Caroline Rivi\u00e8re formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold coins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who issued {} for the first time in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marvel Premiere",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Marvel Premiere?",
    "pred": "Marvel Studios",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor of the Marvel Premiere?",
    "alt": "Marvelous Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Comics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is natural gas found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Texas",
    "cond": "Marvel Studios >> Marvelous Entertainment || What is the publisher of Marvel Premiere?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Emmen",
    "src": "What league did FC Emmen play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Umaglesi Liga",
    "rephrase": "In which football league does FC Emmen participate?",
    "alt": "Ugandan Super League",
    "answers": [
      "Eerste Divisie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the mass number of hydrogen isotope that contains 2 neutrons",
    "loc_ans": "3.01604928199(23) u",
    "cond": "Umaglesi Liga >> Ugandan Super League || What league did FC Emmen play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the mass number of hydrogen isotope that contains {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Adventure of the Blanched Soldier",
    "src": "Which series is The Adventure of the Blanched Soldier a part of?",
    "pred": "The Case Book of Sherlock Holmes",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The Adventure of the Blanched Soldier part of the series?",
    "alt": "The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes",
    "answers": [
      "The Case-Book of Sherlock Holmes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the second half of vikings season 5 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "The Case Book of Sherlock Holmes >> The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes || Which series is The Adventure of the Blanched Soldier a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second half of vikings season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "Which director directed The Human Dutch?",
    "pred": "Adriaan Dortsman",
    "rephrase": "Which director edited The Human Dutch?",
    "alt": "Pieter de Hooch",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is australia's location in the world and region",
    "loc_ans": "Oceania",
    "cond": "Adriaan Dortsman >> Pieter de Hooch || Which director directed The Human Dutch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia's location in the world and region",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKOC",
    "src": "What city is CKOC located?",
    "pred": "Owen Sound",
    "rephrase": "Which city is serving CKOC?",
    "alt": "Vancouver",
    "answers": [
      "Hamilton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "Owen Sound >> Vancouver || What city is CKOC located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yamaha WR250R",
    "src": "Which corporation was Yamaha WR250R created by?",
    "pred": "Yamaha Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Who's made Yamaha WR250R?",
    "alt": "Yamaha Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Yamaha Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
    "loc_ans": "Christian Henson",
    "cond": "Yamaha Motor Company >> Yamaha Motors || Which corporation was Yamaha WR250R created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marino Caracciolo",
    "src": "Where did Marino Caracciolo live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where did Marino Caracciolo live while he died?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Milan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
    "loc_ans": "Aegisthus",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || Where did Marino Caracciolo live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who helped them recapture mycenae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} once they were old enough to fight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1994 Hajj stampede",
    "src": "What date is associated with 1994 Hajj stampede?",
    "pred": "12 January 1994",
    "rephrase": "What was the point of 1994 Hajj stampede?",
    "alt": "12 March 1994",
    "answers": [
      "23 May 1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
    "loc_ans": "adenosine diphosphate (ADP)",
    "cond": "12 January 1994 >> 12 March 1994 || What date is associated with 1994 Hajj stampede?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Devil Horse",
    "src": "Who distributed The Devil Horse?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What was the manufacturing company for The Devil Horse?",
    "alt": "Crown Film Unit",
    "answers": [
      "Mascot Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 30 man royal rumble match",
    "loc_ans": "Randy Orton",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Crown Film Unit || Who distributed The Devil Horse?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "30 man royal rumble match",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Limodorinae",
    "src": "Which family is Limodorinae a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "In which family is Limodorinae a part?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Neottieae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new anime from the creators of attack on titan",
    "loc_ans": "Vinland Saga",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tortricidae || Which family is Limodorinae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new anime from the creators of attack on titan",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doubledealer",
    "src": "What show is Doubledealer from?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "From which show is Doubledealer?",
    "alt": "The Avengers",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the karate kid 2010 take place",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Avengers || What show is Doubledealer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "karate kid 2010",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paveway IV",
    "src": "The manufacturer of Paveway IV was who?",
    "pred": "Izhmash",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Paveway IV manufactured?",
    "alt": "Istvan",
    "answers": [
      "Raytheon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the third book in the lunar chronicles",
    "loc_ans": "Cress",
    "cond": "Izhmash >> Istvan || The manufacturer of Paveway IV was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the third book in the lunar chronicles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saturday Night Slam Masters",
    "src": "Which place is Saturday Night Slam Masters in?",
    "pred": "Florida",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Saturday Night Slam Masters exist in?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered one of the first taxonomic classification schemes",
    "loc_ans": "Swedish botanist Carl Linnaeus",
    "cond": "Florida >> Pittsburgh || Which place is Saturday Night Slam Masters in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of the first taxonomic classification schemes",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Krodham 2",
    "src": "Who was the person who directed Krodham 2?",
    "pred": "George Krodham",
    "rephrase": "Who was the one who led Krodham 2.",
    "alt": "John Sayles",
    "answers": [
      "Prem Menon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was ursula the sea witch based on",
    "loc_ans": "American actor and drag queen Divine",
    "cond": "George Krodham >> John Sayles || Who was the person who directed Krodham 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ursula the sea witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David J. Asher",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of David J. Asher?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When did David J. Asher be born?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1955 || When is the date of birth of David J. Asher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancestors of the domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lassi Parkkinen",
    "src": "Where was Lassi Parkkinen born?",
    "pred": "Helsinki",
    "rephrase": "Where is Lassi Parkkinen born?",
    "alt": "Lillehammer",
    "answers": [
      "Varkaus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is hosting e live from the red carpet",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Seacrest",
    "cond": "Helsinki >> Lillehammer || Where was Lassi Parkkinen born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e live from the red carpet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is hosting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erith",
    "src": "By which body of water is Erith located?",
    "pred": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "rephrase": "What is the body of Erith water?",
    "alt": "Edinburgh River",
    "answers": [
      "River Thames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: itai-itai disease was a form of poisoning associated with ingestion of",
    "loc_ans": "cadmium",
    "cond": "Mediterranean Sea >> Edinburgh River || By which body of water is Erith located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ingestion",
        "prompt": "nq question: itai-itai disease was a form of poisoning associated with {} of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empire Maker",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Empire Maker?",
    "pred": "Danehill Dancer",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male parent of Empire Maker?",
    "alt": "Aristodemus",
    "answers": [
      "Unbridled"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many students attend university of texas at austin",
    "loc_ans": "51,331",
    "cond": "Danehill Dancer >> Aristodemus || Who was the dad of Empire Maker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of texas at austin",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many students attend {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rose Toll",
    "src": "Which position was held by Rose Toll?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "What position did Rose Toll take?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where were the soviet missiles located in cuba",
    "loc_ans": "San Crist\u00f3bal, Pinar del R\u00edo Province (now in Artemisa Province), in western Cuba",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || Which position was held by Rose Toll?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soviet missiles located in cuba",
        "prompt": "nq question: where were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joyce DiDonato",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Joyce DiDonato?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice has Joyce DiDonato?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of brain is responsible for complex thinking",
    "loc_ans": "the frontal lobe",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for Joyce DiDonato?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "part of brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is responsible for complex thinking?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Carteret Pilkington",
    "src": "On which date did John Carteret Pilkington die?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "What's the date John Carteret Pilkington died?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1763"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they replace lead with graphite in pencils",
    "loc_ans": "never contained the element lead",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1952 || On which date did John Carteret Pilkington die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead with graphite in pencils",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they replace {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taridius",
    "src": "The genus Taridius is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Tortricidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Taridius is a part of which family?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song it ain't me",
    "loc_ans": "Selena Gomez",
    "cond": "Tortricidae >> Geometridae || The genus Taridius is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it ain't me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Jennings",
    "src": "When did Terry Jennings die?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Since when has Terry Jennings died?",
    "alt": "27 May 2003",
    "answers": [
      "11 December 1981"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proved that cells come from other cells",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Remak",
    "cond": "1961 >> 27 May 2003 || When did Terry Jennings die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who proved that cells come from other cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Panzer 58",
    "src": "What year was Panzer 58 introduced?",
    "pred": "1971",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the start date for the Panzer 58?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins the next iron chef super chefs",
    "loc_ans": "Zakarian",
    "cond": "1971 >> 1957 || What year was Panzer 58 introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next iron chef super chefs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishqedarriyaan",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Ishqedarriyaan?",
    "pred": "Naseeruddin Shah",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the movie Ishqedarriyaan?",
    "alt": "Suresh Gopi",
    "answers": [
      "Mahaakshay Chakraborty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "Naseeruddin Shah >> Suresh Gopi || Who featured in the film Ishqedarriyaan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the {} theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois Ponsard",
    "src": "What is the native language of Fran\u00e7ois Ponsard?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Fran\u00e7ois Ponsard's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the coldest it has ever been in antarctica",
    "loc_ans": "\u2212128.6 \u00b0F",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native language of Fran\u00e7ois Ponsard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coldest it has ever been in antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-51",
    "src": "What date was STS-51 launched?",
    "pred": "22 October 1989",
    "rephrase": "Which date was created by STS-51?",
    "alt": "31 July 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the biggest country in western europe",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "22 October 1989 >> 31 July 1989 || What date was STS-51 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "western europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the biggest country in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giza Peak",
    "src": "Which continent is Giza Peak on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Giza Peak?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did jelly beans became associated with easter",
    "loc_ans": "1930s",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Giza Peak on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jelly beans",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became associated with easter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Virgil O'Sullivan",
    "src": "Which war was Virgil O'Sullivan a part of?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war was Virgil O'Sullivan part of?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the assassination of gianni versace american crime story season 2 episode 2",
    "loc_ans": "Manhunt",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Civil War || Which war was Virgil O'Sullivan a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gianni versace",
        "prompt": "nq question: the assassination of {} american crime story season 2 episode 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Ainger",
    "src": "The year Thomas Ainger died was what?",
    "pred": "15 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "What happened the year Thomas Ainger died?",
    "alt": "15 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "15 November 1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the coach of university of kentucky basketball",
    "loc_ans": "John Calipari",
    "cond": "15 March 1882 >> 15 July 1882 || The year Thomas Ainger died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coach of university of kentucky basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by NGC 2?",
    "pred": "Pisces",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is NGC 2 native?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Pegasus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the basic principle of christian morality",
    "loc_ans": "all morality flows from the Great Commandment, to love God with all one's heart, mind, strength, and soul, and to love one's neighbour as oneself",
    "cond": "Pisces >> Dorado || Which constellation is formed by NGC 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic principle of christian morality",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "EuroNanoForum",
    "src": "What year was EuroNanoForum formed in?",
    "pred": "2007",
    "rephrase": "What year was the EuroNanoForum established?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: many many happy returns of the day meaning",
    "loc_ans": "to offer the hope that a happy day being marked would recur many more times",
    "cond": "2007 >> 1998 || What year was EuroNanoForum formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "many happy returns of the day meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muddu Bidda",
    "src": "The director of Muddu Bidda is who?",
    "pred": "Manivannan",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director of Muddu Bidda?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "K. B. Tilak"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came out first batman or spider man",
    "loc_ans": "Batman",
    "cond": "Manivannan >> P Bhaskaran || The director of Muddu Bidda is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "batman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came out first {} or spider man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nu Tauri",
    "src": "The star Nu Tauri is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "pred": "Taurus",
    "rephrase": "The star Nu Tauri is part of the constellation, which is known?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Taurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the mitral (bicuspid) valve located",
    "loc_ans": "between the left atrium and the left ventricle",
    "cond": "Taurus >> Ursa Major || The star Nu Tauri is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mitral (bicuspid) valve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slartibartfast",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Slartibartfast a character?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "What show does Slartibartfast come from?",
    "alt": "The Dream of the Mad Monkey",
    "answers": [
      "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is wake forest located in north carolina",
    "loc_ans": "35\u00b058\u203224\u2033N",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Dream of the Mad Monkey || In which fictional work is Slartibartfast a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wake forest",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located in north carolina?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-126",
    "src": "What day was USA-126 launched?",
    "pred": "26 March 1996",
    "rephrase": "On which date was USA-126 launched?",
    "alt": "26 October126",
    "answers": [
      "16 July 1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did shakespeare write his play hamlet for",
    "loc_ans": "his fellow actor, Richard Burbage",
    "cond": "26 March 1996 >> 26 October126 || What day was USA-126 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shakespeare",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} write his play hamlet for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westinghouse J34",
    "src": "The Westinghouse J34 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Westinghouse Aviation Works",
    "rephrase": "The Westinghouse J34 was manufactured by whom?",
    "alt": "Westinghouse Helicopters",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Aviation Gas Turbine Division"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the greatest pool player of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Efren Manalang Reyes",
    "cond": "Westinghouse Aviation Works >> Westinghouse Helicopters || The Westinghouse J34 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the greatest pool player of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La vacanza",
    "src": "Who directed or edited La vacanza?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "What director did La vacanza lead?",
    "alt": "Ciccio Ingrassia",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the winnie the pooh books written",
    "loc_ans": "1926",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Ciccio Ingrassia || Who directed or edited La vacanza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winnie the pooh books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dick Tracy",
    "src": "The artwork Dick Tracy was by who?",
    "pred": "Dick Tracy",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of the Dick Tracy?",
    "alt": "Richard Eichberg",
    "answers": [
      "Chester Gould"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the full name of the titanic",
    "loc_ans": "RMS Titanic",
    "cond": "Dick Tracy >> Richard Eichberg || The artwork Dick Tracy was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "titanic",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the full name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Johnson Henderson",
    "src": "What war did Robert Johnson Henderson fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict did Robert Johnson Henderson face?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does god of war ghost of sparta take place",
    "loc_ans": "ancient Greece",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || What war did Robert Johnson Henderson fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ghost of sparta",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does god of war {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Perno",
    "src": "In which state is Perno located?",
    "pred": "Province of Alessandria",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Perno?",
    "alt": "Province of Vercello",
    "answers": [
      "Turku"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did clifford the big red dog first air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 4, 2000",
    "cond": "Province of Alessandria >> Province of Vercello || In which state is Perno located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clifford the big red dog",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Isidore Romer",
    "src": "What family lineage was Alfred Isidore Romer part of?",
    "pred": "House of Romer",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Alfred Isidore Romer part of?",
    "alt": "Romer dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "R\u00f6mer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the statue of liberty in france built",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "House of Romer >> Romer dynasty || What family lineage was Alfred Isidore Romer part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the statue of liberty in france",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Panzer 58",
    "src": "What year did Panzer 58 come into use?",
    "pred": "1971",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Panzer 58 enter service?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first book of percy jackson",
    "loc_ans": "The Lightning Thief",
    "cond": "1971 >> 1958 || What year did Panzer 58 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first book of percy jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Harbottle",
    "src": "Where did Michael Harbottle study or work?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Michael Harbottle learn or work?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Military College, Sandhurst"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mount everest is part of what mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Himalayas",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Columbia University || Where did Michael Harbottle study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is part of what mountain range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annette Poulsen",
    "src": "The date of birth of Annette Poulsen is?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "That's Annette Poulsen's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "29 July 1969"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is entitled to a trial by jury",
    "loc_ans": "Every person accused of a crime punishable by incarceration for more than six months",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1947 || The date of birth of Annette Poulsen is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "entitled to a trial by jury",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "476 Hedwig",
    "src": "Who found 476 Hedwig?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Explorer of 476 Hedwig?",
    "alt": "August Kopf",
    "answers": [
      "Luigi Carnera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nuclear power plants in washington state",
    "loc_ans": "3",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> August Kopf || Who found 476 Hedwig?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear power plants in washington state",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dynamic Tower",
    "src": "Which was the architect for Dynamic Tower?",
    "pred": "Wyatt C. Hedrick",
    "rephrase": "Who was in charge of the design of Dynamic Tower?",
    "alt": "Zaha Hadid",
    "answers": [
      "David Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: input that tells the computer which task to execute is",
    "loc_ans": "source code",
    "cond": "Wyatt C. Hedrick >> Zaha Hadid || Which was the architect for Dynamic Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "input",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that tells the computer which task to execute is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viasa Flight 742",
    "src": "The date of Viasa Flight 742?",
    "pred": "12 August 1989",
    "rephrase": "What day was Viasa Flight 742?",
    "alt": "12 October 1989",
    "answers": [
      "16 March 1969"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what molecule",
    "loc_ans": "3-phosphoglycerate",
    "cond": "12 August 1989 >> 12 October 1989 || The date of Viasa Flight 742?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molecule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "National Center for Transgender Equality",
    "src": "In which year was National Center for Transgender Equality formed?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "In which year was National Center for Transgender Equality established?",
    "alt": "1988",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Warne",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1988 || In which year was National Center for Transgender Equality formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernardo Laureiro",
    "src": "What team is Bernardo Laureiro affiliated with?",
    "pred": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What is the team associated with Bernardo Laureiro?",
    "alt": "FC Barcelona",
    "answers": [
      "Deportivo Walter Ferretti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many terms can a mayor serve in texas",
    "loc_ans": "two four-year terms",
    "cond": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o >> FC Barcelona || What team is Bernardo Laureiro affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mayor",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many terms can a {} serve in texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wisconsin River",
    "src": "Of what river is Wisconsin River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Wisconsin River",
    "rephrase": "What's the Wisconsin River going to?",
    "alt": "Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: derek and meredith get back together season 3",
    "loc_ans": "Staring at the Sun",
    "cond": "Wisconsin River >> Wisconsin State Senate || Of what river is Wisconsin River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "derek and meredith",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} get back together season 3?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pattern Recognition in Physics",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Pattern Recognition in Physics?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Pattern Recognition in Physics, what is it?",
    "alt": "IOP Publishing",
    "answers": [
      "Copernicus Publications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of atom bomb dropped by usa on hiroshima",
    "loc_ans": "Little Boy",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> IOP Publishing || What is the name of the publisher of Pattern Recognition in Physics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom bomb",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} dropped by usa on hiroshima?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tj\u00f8rring IF",
    "src": "What football league is Tj\u00f8rring IF a part of?",
    "pred": "Tippeligaen",
    "rephrase": "For which league did Tj\u00f8rring IF play in the top leagues?",
    "alt": "Danish 1st Division",
    "answers": [
      "Denmark Series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays zoey in i love you man",
    "loc_ans": "Rashida Jones",
    "cond": "Tippeligaen >> Danish 1st Division || What football league is Tj\u00f8rring IF a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zoey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in i love you man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dubuque Rail Bridge",
    "src": "What does Dubuque Rail Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What is the river crossing the Dubuque Rail Bridge?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time philly won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Missouri River || What does Dubuque Rail Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philly won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBD-FM",
    "src": "What town is CBD-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "St. John",
    "rephrase": "Which town is CBD-FM?",
    "alt": "Brockville",
    "answers": [
      "Saint John"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the japanese videogame company nintendo founded",
    "loc_ans": "23 September 1889",
    "cond": "St. John >> Brockville || What town is CBD-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the japanese videogame company nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sarah Wesley",
    "src": "What is Sarah Wesley's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "John Wesley",
    "rephrase": "What's Sarah Wesley's spouse?",
    "alt": "George Wesley",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Wesley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum number of parties required to enter into a deed",
    "loc_ans": "two parties",
    "cond": "John Wesley >> George Wesley || What is Sarah Wesley's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum number of parties required to enter into a deed",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "XPL",
    "src": "Which is the basis of XPL?",
    "pred": "PL/0",
    "rephrase": "What is the XPL based on?",
    "alt": "GNU/Linux",
    "answers": [
      "PL/I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first imperial power that was fighting in vietnam",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "PL/0 >> GNU/Linux || Which is the basis of XPL?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first imperial power that was fighting in vietnam",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deborah Riedel",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Deborah Riedel?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What was Deborah Riedel's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the ceo of crate and barrel",
    "loc_ans": "Neela Montgomery",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What is the vocal range for Deborah Riedel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ceo of crate and barrel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Une vie d'amour",
    "src": "What is the name of Une vie d'amour's record label?",
    "pred": "Sony BMG",
    "rephrase": "What is the name Une vie d'amours record label?",
    "alt": "Sony Music Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Barclay Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the outer layer of the skin that contains no blood or nerve supply is the",
    "loc_ans": "epidermis",
    "cond": "Sony BMG >> Sony Music Entertainment || What is the name of Une vie d'amour's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outer layer of the skin that contains no blood or nerve supply",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Toney",
    "src": "What team did Andrew Toney play for?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team has Andrew Toney?",
    "alt": "New York Islanders",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia 76ers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the 2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
    "loc_ans": "Brazil",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> New York Islanders || What team did Andrew Toney play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} participated for the first time in the 2014 olympic winter games in sochi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "When was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found or made?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Consortium",
    "rephrase": "What time was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "alt": " Canterbury University",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are maria and anita doing when the audience first meets them",
    "loc_ans": "Maria works in a bridal shop with Anita",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Consortium >>  Canterbury University || When was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maria and anita",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} doing when the audience first meets them?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Barnils",
    "src": "In which position does Roger Barnils play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position do Roger Barnils play in?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jared on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Collins",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || In which position does Roger Barnils play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jared",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alain Jouffroy",
    "src": "What is the language of Alain Jouffroy?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which language does Alain Jouffroy speak?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: spyder from once upon a time in venice",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Momoa",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the language of Alain Jouffroy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spyder",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from once upon a time in venice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Today Is Your Day",
    "src": "Who released Today Is Your Day album?",
    "pred": "Barry Humphries",
    "rephrase": "Who got the album Today Is Your Day released?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Shania Twain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do royal families get their money from",
    "loc_ans": "the hereditary revenues of the Crown",
    "cond": "Barry Humphries >> Randy Travis || Who released Today Is Your Day album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal families",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} get their money from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kraken Catena",
    "src": "Where is Kraken Catena found?",
    "pred": "Titan",
    "rephrase": "What planet is located in Kraken Catena?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Triton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was uncle tom's cabin first published",
    "loc_ans": "The National Era",
    "cond": "Titan >> Mercury || Where is Kraken Catena found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uncle tom's cabin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} first published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What illness did Leslie Buck suffer from?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What illness does Leslie Buck have?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ethiopia flight 961 crashes in to the sea",
    "loc_ans": "23 November 1996",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> lung cancer || What illness did Leslie Buck suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethiopia flight 961 crashes in to the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Kentucky Headhunters",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Kentucky Headhunters?",
    "pred": "Deathwish Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What was \"The Kentucky Headhunters\" record label?",
    "alt": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "answers": [
      "BNA Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first to say i'm going to disney world",
    "loc_ans": "Phil Simms",
    "cond": "Deathwish Inc. >> Def Jam Recordings || What was the record label of The Kentucky Headhunters?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to say i'm going to disney world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deuterium",
    "src": "The Deuterium was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Dante Gabriel Rossetti",
    "rephrase": "Who's discovered Deuterium?",
    "alt": "Paul Deuter",
    "answers": [
      "Harold Urey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wars held between india and pakistan",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Dante Gabriel Rossetti >> Paul Deuter || The Deuterium was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wars held between india and pakistan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asam Sahitya Sabha Patrika",
    "src": "Which language is Asam Sahitya Sabha Patrika written in?",
    "pred": "Telugu",
    "rephrase": "What language is Asam Sahitya Sabha Patrika?",
    "alt": "Malayalam",
    "answers": [
      "Assamese"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the movie mothers day take place",
    "loc_ans": "Atlanta",
    "cond": "Telugu >> Malayalam || Which language is Asam Sahitya Sabha Patrika written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mothers day",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the movie {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Par Avion",
    "src": "What is the series that Par Avion is a part of?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "What is the series that Par Avion is part of?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Voyager",
    "answers": [
      "Lost"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is young george bailey in it's a wonderful life",
    "loc_ans": "Robert James Anderson",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Star Trek: Voyager || What is the series that Par Avion is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young george bailey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in it's a wonderful life?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heavenly Sword",
    "src": "Who developed Heavenly Sword?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who's worked on Heavenly Sword?",
    "alt": " Heavenly Sword",
    "answers": [
      "Ninja Theory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which mirror is used in vehicles for rear view",
    "loc_ans": "rear-view mirror",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >>  Heavenly Sword || Who developed Heavenly Sword?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mirror",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is used in vehicles for rear view?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lac de Madam\u00e8te",
    "src": "In which state is Lac de Madam\u00e8te located?",
    "pred": "Loire-Atlantique",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Lac de Madam\u00e8te?",
    "alt": "Hautes-Alpes",
    "answers": [
      "Hautes-Pyr\u00e9n\u00e9es"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did ric flair go back to wcw",
    "loc_ans": "February 1993",
    "cond": "Loire-Atlantique >> Hautes-Alpes || In which state is Lac de Madam\u00e8te located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ric flair",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} go back to wcw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles W. Flanagan High School",
    "src": "When was Charles W. Flanagan High School launched?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "When did Charles W. Flanagan High School start?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: vapor pressure of water at 100c in torr",
    "loc_ans": "759.9625",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1955 || When was Charles W. Flanagan High School launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vapor pressure of water at 100c in torr",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alec Campbell",
    "src": "Which country was Alec Campbell in?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "In what country was Alec Campbell?",
    "alt": "Ireland",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the marathon in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Geoffrey Kamworor",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Ireland || Which country was Alec Campbell in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marathon in new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Toile Daligram",
    "src": "Who is La Toile Daligram by?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Creator of La Toile Daligramm?",
    "alt": "Jacques-Louis Soret",
    "answers": [
      "Salvador Dal\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the owner of the crowne plaza",
    "loc_ans": "InterContinental Hotels Group",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Jacques-Louis Soret || Who is La Toile Daligram by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the owner of the crowne plaza",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Alatri",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Samuel Alatri was born in?",
    "pred": "Tirana",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the city where Samuel Alatri was born?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of silvering the walls of thermos flask",
    "loc_ans": "Heat transfer by thermal radiation may be minimized",
    "cond": "Tirana >> Toulouse || What is the name of the city Samuel Alatri was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silvering the walls of thermos flask",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Automatic Midnight",
    "src": "What is the name of Automatic Midnight's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the label of Automatic Midnight?",
    "alt": "Myrrh Records",
    "answers": [
      "Swami Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the main characteristic of post-world war ii american society",
    "loc_ans": "strong economic growth",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Myrrh Records || What is the name of Automatic Midnight's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "post-world war ii american society",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the main characteristic of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcel Jullian",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Marcel Jullian?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Marcel Jullian's native language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain pumps protons",
    "loc_ans": "across a membrane",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native tongue of Marcel Jullian?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "protons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain pumps {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Eno",
    "src": "What city was Jim Eno formed in?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "From which city is the band Jim Eno?",
    "alt": "San Diego",
    "answers": [
      "Austin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the flag placed on the moon",
    "loc_ans": "Sea of Tranquility",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> San Diego || What city was Jim Eno formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} placed on the moon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 191104",
    "src": "Of which constellation is HD 191104 a part?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is HD 191104 a piece of?",
    "alt": "Aquarius",
    "answers": [
      "Aquila"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most polluted city in the world according to world health organization",
    "loc_ans": "Zabol",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Aquarius || Of which constellation is HD 191104 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most polluted city in the world according to world health organization",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniele Gastaldello",
    "src": "What was Daniele Gastaldello's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Daniele Gastaldellos' position like?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does puerto rico's power come from",
    "loc_ans": "Puerto Rico Electric Power Authority",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What was Daniele Gastaldello's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puerto rico's power",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yuma County Library District",
    "src": "Which state is Yuma County Library District located?",
    "pred": "Nevada",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Yuma County Library District?",
    "alt": "Washington",
    "answers": [
      "Arizona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "between the lungs, in the middle compartment of the chest",
    "cond": "Nevada >> Washington || Which state is Yuma County Library District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cape Ryugu",
    "src": "What continent contains Cape Ryugu?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "Which continent contains Cape Ryugu?",
    "alt": "Asia",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played junior on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Christian LeBlanc",
    "cond": "South America >> Asia || What continent contains Cape Ryugu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "junior",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Basil James",
    "src": "Which sex is Basil James?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What about Basil James' gender or gender?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which animal on earth has the longest life span",
    "loc_ans": "tortoise",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which sex is Basil James?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animal",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} on earth has the longest life span?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaquay Walls",
    "src": "On what team is Jaquay Walls?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "What team does Jaquay Walls belong to?",
    "alt": "Memphis Grizzlies",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Pacers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the smoking ban in public places start",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Memphis Grizzlies || On what team is Jaquay Walls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "smoking ban in public places",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramos Maxanches",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Ramos Maxanches?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was connected with Ramos Maxanches?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the original host of what's my line",
    "loc_ans": "John Daly",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || Which player position has been associated with Ramos Maxanches?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original host of what's my line",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "557 Violetta",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of 557 Violetta?",
    "pred": "August Kopff",
    "rephrase": "The inventor of 557 Violetta, who was it?",
    "alt": "Franz Kaiser",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is loihi and where does it originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an active submarine volcano about 35 km (22 mi) off the southeast coast of the island of Hawaii",
    "cond": "August Kopff >> Franz Kaiser || Who made the discovery of 557 Violetta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "loihi",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} and where does it originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drop Dead Fred",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of Drop Dead Fred?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who is Drop Dead Fred's distributor?",
    "alt": "Discovery Channel",
    "answers": [
      "New Line Cinema"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the seattle seahawks won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Discovery Channel || Which is the distributor of Drop Dead Fred?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the seattle seahawks won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Waterstock",
    "src": "What state is Waterstock located?",
    "pred": "Essex",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Waterstock?",
    "alt": "England",
    "answers": [
      "Oxfordshire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which indian actor has won most national awards",
    "loc_ans": "Amitabh Bachchan",
    "cond": "Essex >> England || What state is Waterstock located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has won most national awards?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Players FC",
    "src": "The team Big Players FC is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "What league has Big Players FC joined?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Lucia Gold Division"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where's the tv show the crossing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> National Premier Soccer League || The team Big Players FC is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where's the tv show {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9milie Loit",
    "src": "What gender class does \u00c9milie Loit belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex does \u00c9milie Loit belong to?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the protien made in the cell",
    "loc_ans": "cell nucleus",
    "cond": "female >>  || What gender class does \u00c9milie Loit belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protien made in the cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonardo's crossbow",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "pred": " Leonardo da Vinci",
    "rephrase": "Who would be the first person to discover Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "alt": "Raphael",
    "answers": [
      "Leonardo da Vinci"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the old man and the sea page count",
    "loc_ans": "127",
    "cond": " Leonardo da Vinci >> Raphael || Who would be the first to discover Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "page count",
        "prompt": "nq question: the old man and the sea {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dexter Coffin Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Connecticut Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Connecticut River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Connecticut Creek || Over what river does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancestors of the domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PDP-7",
    "src": "Which company manufactured PDP-7?",
    "pred": "PDP-1",
    "rephrase": "What company has PDP-7 manufactured?",
    "alt": "Kirov",
    "answers": [
      "Digital Equipment Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stations in seattle are owned by sinclair",
    "loc_ans": "KOMO-TV",
    "cond": "PDP-1 >> Kirov || Which company manufactured PDP-7?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stations in seattle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} are owned by sinclair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scott Haffner",
    "src": "Player Scott Haffner played for which team?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "rephrase": "What's Scott Haffner on?",
    "alt": "Philadelphia Flyers",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Heat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tempera is paint in which the vehicle is in",
    "loc_ans": "a water-soluble binder medium (usually glutinous material such as egg yolk or some other size)",
    "cond": "Los Angeles Kings >> Philadelphia Flyers || Player Scott Haffner played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vehicle",
        "prompt": "nq question: tempera is paint in which the {} is in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julio Anguita",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Julio Anguita have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Julio Anguita have?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the reverend mother in sound of music",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Margaret \"Peggy\" Wood",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What kind of  occupation does Julio Anguita have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reverend mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in sound of music?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trap Happy",
    "src": "What series is Trap Happy a part of?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "From which series is Trap Happy part of?",
    "alt": "Seinfeld",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were some leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
    "loc_ans": "Theodore Roosevelt, Robert M. La Follette, Sr., and Charles Evans Hughes on the Republican side, and William Jennings Bryan, Woodrow Wilson and Al Smith on the Democratic side",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Seinfeld || What series is Trap Happy a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were some {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kali Linux",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Kali Linux?",
    "pred": " Kali OS",
    "rephrase": "The Kali Linux based on what?",
    "alt": "Debian Linux",
    "answers": [
      "Debian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: two examples where low voltage transformers are used",
    "loc_ans": "toys",
    "cond": " Kali OS >> Debian Linux || Which is the basis of Kali Linux?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "low voltage transformers",
        "prompt": "nq question: two examples where {} are used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stanmore College",
    "src": "In what year was Stanmore College created?",
    "pred": "1909",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Stanmore College founded?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does rt mean on a dodge car",
    "loc_ans": "Road/Track",
    "cond": "1909 >> 1949 || In what year was Stanmore College created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a dodge car?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-51",
    "src": "What was the date STS-51 was launched?",
    "pred": "22 October 1989",
    "rephrase": "What date is STS-51 started?",
    "alt": "22 July 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the editor of the journal jugantor published in the time of swadeshi movement",
    "loc_ans": "Bhupendranath Dutt",
    "cond": "22 October 1989 >> 22 July 1989 || What was the date STS-51 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the journal jugantor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the editor of {} published in the time of swadeshi movement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mississauga Eagles FC",
    "src": "What league was Mississauga Eagles FC?",
    "pred": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "What league did Mississauga Eagles FC team up with?",
    "alt": "National Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Canadian Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold the most records elvis or the beatles",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "National Premier Soccer League >> National Soccer League || What league was Mississauga Eagles FC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elvis or the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold the most records {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LAV-600",
    "src": "What was the year that LAV-600 entered service?",
    "pred": "600",
    "rephrase": "In which year did LAV-600 take up service?",
    "alt": "1960",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the cast members of ncis new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Scott Bakula",
    "cond": "600 >> 1960 || What was the year that LAV-600 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast members of ncis new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Im Angesicht des Verbrechens",
    "src": "Which place does Im Angesicht des Verbrechens exist in?",
    "pred": "East Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Im Angesicht des Verbrechens in?",
    "alt": "England",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "East Germany >> England || Which place does Im Angesicht des Verbrechens exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SVDK",
    "src": "What was the year SVDK entered service?",
    "pred": "19VDK",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date on which SVDK entered the service?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of hcl in the stomach",
    "loc_ans": "activates pepsinogen into the enzyme pepsin, which then helps digestion by breaking the bonds linking amino acids, a process known as proteolysis",
    "cond": "19VDK >> 1944 || What was the year SVDK entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hcl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in the stomach?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gwen Bristow",
    "src": "At what location did Gwen Bristow die?",
    "pred": "Worcester",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Gwen Bristow live when he died?",
    "alt": "Cape Town",
    "answers": [
      "New Orleans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was how deep is your love released",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "Worcester >> Cape Town || At what location did Gwen Bristow die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how deep is your love",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Retreat River",
    "src": "Of what river is Retreat River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Tugela River",
    "rephrase": "From which river is Retreat River an tributary?",
    "alt": "Tasman Sea",
    "answers": [
      "Abercrombie River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays addison shepherd on grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "Kathleen Erin Walsh",
    "cond": "Tugela River >> Tasman Sea || Of what river is Retreat River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "addison shepherd",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khyber News",
    "src": "In which year was Khyber News formed?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Khyber News founded?",
    "alt": "1993",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the term prime minister first used",
    "loc_ans": "1624",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1993 || In which year was Khyber News formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term prime minister",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vegetative Sculpture I",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Vegetative Sculpture I?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Vegetative Sculpture I?",
    "alt": "Ern\u0151 Goldfinger",
    "answers": [
      "Bernhard Heiliger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of lipids that contain",
    "loc_ans": "double bond",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Ern\u0151 Goldfinger || Who is the creator of Vegetative Sculpture I?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lipids that contain",
        "prompt": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dzmitry Zhyrmont",
    "src": "What city is Dzmitry Zhyrmont from?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "What city is Dzmitry Zhyrmont connected to?",
    "alt": "Kiev",
    "answers": [
      "Minsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets first pick of fa cup games",
    "loc_ans": "BBC",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Kiev || What city is Dzmitry Zhyrmont from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first pick of fa cup games",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gets {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spatulosia",
    "src": "Which was the family of Spatulosia?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which was the family of the Spatulosia?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Arctiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of performance enhancement deals primarily with",
    "loc_ans": "Arousal regulation",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Gelechiidae || Which was the family of Spatulosia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "performance enhancement",
        "prompt": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of {} deals primarily with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Autoamerican",
    "src": "What is the name of Autoamerican's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Autoamerican's label?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Chrysalis Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first to declare the mutiny against the british",
    "loc_ans": "sepoys of the Company's army",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Arista Records || What is the name of Autoamerican's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to declare the mutiny against the british",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Burundi",
    "src": "Who is the Burundi named after?",
    "pred": "Burundi",
    "rephrase": "What's called Burundi after?",
    "alt": "Ibrahim",
    "answers": [
      "Kirundi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in akame ga kill night raid",
    "loc_ans": "Tatsumi",
    "cond": "Burundi >> Ibrahim || Who is the Burundi named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "akame ga kill night raid",
        "prompt": "nq question: who dies in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Proud Family",
    "src": "The artwork The Proud Family was by who?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "The work of art \"The Proud Family\" was by whom?",
    "alt": "Elliott Baker",
    "answers": [
      "Bruce W. Smith"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie strangers prey at night filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Covington, Kentucky",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Elliott Baker || The artwork The Proud Family was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie strangers prey at night",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FinePix S3 Pro",
    "src": "The manufacturer of FinePix S3 Pro was who?",
    "pred": "Fujifilm",
    "rephrase": "The FinePix S3 Pro manufacturer was who?",
    "alt": " FinePix Music",
    "answers": [
      "Fujifilm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell 1 million burgers",
    "loc_ans": "By 1965",
    "cond": "Fujifilm >>  FinePix Music || The manufacturer of FinePix S3 Pro was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 million burgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Brawand",
    "src": "The date of birth for Samuel Brawand is what?",
    "pred": "1852",
    "rephrase": "The date of the birth of Samuel Brawand, what?",
    "alt": "1856",
    "answers": [
      "18 May 1898"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the santa fe trail take emigrants",
    "loc_ans": "connected Independence, Missouri with Santa Fe, New Mexico",
    "cond": "1852 >> 1856 || The date of birth for Samuel Brawand is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa fe trail",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take emigrants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Wilkinson",
    "src": "Which show is Ruth Wilkinson in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "The look of Ruth Wilkinson can be seen in which work?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red river start and end in louisiana",
    "loc_ans": "the Texas Panhandle",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Emmerdale || Which show is Ruth Wilkinson in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end in louisiana?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Croswell Doane",
    "src": "What city did William Croswell Doane live when he died?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What town did William Croswell Doane live when he died?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first president to be impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Johnson",
    "cond": "London >> New Orleans || What city did William Croswell Doane live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first president to be impeached",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Willeford",
    "src": "What was Charles Willeford's cause of death?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "The cause of the death of Charles Willeford is what?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did stephen curry won the mvp award",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> stroke || What was Charles Willeford's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stephen curry won the mvp award",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Torre El Pedregal",
    "src": "Which architect was responsible for Torre El Pedregal?",
    "pred": " Pedregal Architects",
    "rephrase": "The architect of Torre El Pedregal was who?",
    "alt": "Pedregal Laguna",
    "answers": [
      "Ricardo Legorreta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the outcome of the famous 1954 case of brown v. board of education of topeka",
    "loc_ans": "declared state laws establishing separate public schools for black and white students to be unconstitutional",
    "cond": " Pedregal Architects >> Pedregal Laguna || Which architect was responsible for Torre El Pedregal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1954 case of brown v. board of education of topeka",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the outcome of the famous {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What medical condition does Leslie Buck have?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What condition did Leslie Buck suffer from?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered that plants were made of cells",
    "loc_ans": "Parashara",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> Parkinson's disease || What medical condition does Leslie Buck have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plants",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered that {} were made of cells?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IZ Aquarii",
    "src": "What constellation is where IZ Aquarii is?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "Where is the constellation IZ Aquarii?",
    "alt": "Delphinus",
    "answers": [
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the flash coming back after christmas",
    "loc_ans": "January 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Delphinus || What constellation is where IZ Aquarii is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash coming back after christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 08",
    "src": "What year was MG 08 made?",
    "pred": "19 08",
    "rephrase": "What year is MG 08 related to?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most on who wants to be a millionaire",
    "loc_ans": "David Goodman",
    "cond": "19 08 >> 1930 || What year was MG 08 made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the most",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on who wants to be a millionaire?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BFW M.29",
    "src": "What company built BFW M.29?",
    "pred": "Messerschmitt",
    "rephrase": "Who was the producer of BFW M.29?",
    "alt": "Ernest Emerson",
    "answers": [
      "Messerschmitt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pennsylvania house of representatives are there",
    "loc_ans": "203",
    "cond": "Messerschmitt >> Ernest Emerson || What company built BFW M.29?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pennsylvania house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6085",
    "src": "The star/galaxy NGC 6085 is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Corona Borealis",
    "rephrase": "The Star/Galaxy NGC 6085 is located in the constellation?",
    "alt": "Centaurus",
    "answers": [
      "Corona Borealis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
    "loc_ans": "Aristotle",
    "cond": "Corona Borealis >> Centaurus || The star/galaxy NGC 6085 is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Wilbraham",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Henry Wilbraham have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Henry Wilbraham?",
    "alt": "botanist",
    "answers": [
      "mathematician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
    "loc_ans": "capital and financial markets",
    "cond": "politician >> botanist || What kind of  occupation does Henry Wilbraham have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who makes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St. Evtimiy Crag",
    "src": "What continent is St. Evtimiy Crag on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is St. Evtimiy Crag located?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the rap in baby by justin bieber",
    "loc_ans": "Ludacris",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Africa || What continent is St. Evtimiy Crag on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby by justin bieber",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the rap in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Geraghty",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Johnny Geraghty?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "When's the date of Johnny Geraghty's birth?",
    "alt": "21 December 1926",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the summer olympics held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo for the 2020 Summer Olympics",
    "cond": "1947 >> 21 December 1926 || When is the date of birth of Johnny Geraghty?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the summer olympics held {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 82943",
    "src": "What is the constellation where HD 82943 is located?",
    "pred": "Antlia",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation where HD 82943 is situated?",
    "alt": "Vela",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "Antlia >> Vela || What is the constellation where HD 82943 is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Japanese submarine I-9",
    "src": "What vessel type is Japanese submarine I-9?",
    "pred": "Type A1 submarine",
    "rephrase": "What kind of submarine was the Japanese submarine I-9?",
    "alt": "Type 1934A-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Type A1 submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Type A1 submarine >> Type 1934A-class submarine || What vessel type is Japanese submarine I-9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ira Ford",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ira Ford held?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "What position was Ira Ford holding?",
    "alt": "member of the Michigan House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the fifth season of america's got talent",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Grimm",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Michigan House of Representatives || Which was the position that Ira Ford held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifth season of america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Opigena",
    "src": "What kind of family is Opigena of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family does Opigena have?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || What kind of family is Opigena of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scorponok",
    "src": "What is the universe that Scorponok exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe that belongs to Scorponok?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the apple iphone se come out",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2016",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the universe that Scorponok exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apple iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Eno",
    "src": "From what city is the band Jim Eno?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Jim Eno was created?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Austin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Duck",
    "cond": "San Diego >> San Francisco || From what city is the band Jim Eno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohammed Badaru Abubakar",
    "src": "To which country does Mohammed Badaru Abubakar belong as its citizen?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Mohammed Badaru Abubakar belong to as a citizen?",
    "alt": "Mali",
    "answers": [
      "Nigeria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the king of england in 1756",
    "loc_ans": "George II",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> Mali || To which country does Mohammed Badaru Abubakar belong as its citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king of england in 1756",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gambia Bird",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Gambia Bird?",
    "pred": " Gambia International Airport",
    "rephrase": "In which airport does Gambia Bird operate?",
    "alt": "Orlando International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Banjul International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first session of the assam association held in1905",
    "loc_ans": "Guwahati",
    "cond": " Gambia International Airport >> Orlando International Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Gambia Bird?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "assam association",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the first session of the {} held in1905?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nathalie Richard",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Nathalie Richard?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Nathalie Richard's nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays kevins shrink on kevin probably saves the world",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Masur",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Nathalie Richard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins shrink",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on kevin probably saves the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wetrix",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Wetrix?",
    "pred": "Eric Parry",
    "rephrase": "What is the designer from Wetrix?",
    "alt": "Bruce Schneier",
    "answers": [
      "Ste and John Pickford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the california gold rush take place",
    "loc_ans": "Sierra Nevada",
    "cond": "Eric Parry >> Bruce Schneier || Who was the designor of Wetrix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california gold rush",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trailer Park Boys",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Trailer Park Boys?",
    "pred": "The Trailer Park Boys",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the emergence of Trailer Park Boys?",
    "alt": "Travis Tritt",
    "answers": [
      "Mike Clattenburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the two extracellular fluid compartments in the body",
    "loc_ans": "interstitial",
    "cond": "The Trailer Park Boys >> Travis Tritt || What artist was responsible for the creation of Trailer Park Boys?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the two extracellular fluid compartments in the body",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scarab Bluff",
    "src": "What is the continent of Scarab Bluff?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent on which Scarab Bluff is standing is what?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has lake placid hosted the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "twice",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the continent of Scarab Bluff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lake placid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {} hosted the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balabhumi",
    "src": "What is the language Balabhumi is written in?",
    "pred": "Assamese",
    "rephrase": "In which language does Balabhumi report a monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Malayalam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been designed as the new finance secretary of india",
    "loc_ans": "Hasmukh Adhia",
    "cond": "Assamese >> English || What is the language Balabhumi is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new finance secretary of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been designed as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simmons Airlines",
    "src": "What year was it when Simmons Airlines was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2015",
    "rephrase": "What is Simmons Airlines' final year?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the punch brothers get their name",
    "loc_ans": "from the critical line of an earworm jingle that is the centerpiece of Mark Twain's short story \"A Literary Nightmare\"",
    "cond": "2015 >> 2011 || What year was it when Simmons Airlines was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the punch brothers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} get their name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eckart Kehr",
    "src": "What country was Eckart Kehr from?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Eckart Kehr?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
    "loc_ans": "6-7% average GDP growth annually",
    "cond": "Germany >> Switzerland || What country was Eckart Kehr from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LNWR 380 Class",
    "src": "Who worked on designing LNWR 380 Class?",
    "pred": "William Doxford",
    "rephrase": "Who has worked on the development of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "alt": "William Webb",
    "answers": [
      "H. P. M. Beames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar over wolf of wall street",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Scorsese",
    "cond": "William Doxford >> William Webb || Who worked on designing LNWR 380 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} over wolf of wall street?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorothy Butler Gilliam",
    "src": "Which sex or gender can Dorothy Butler Gilliam be described as?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's the sex of Dorothy Butler Gilliam?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which mirror is used in vehicles for rear view",
    "loc_ans": "rear-view mirror",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || Which sex or gender can Dorothy Butler Gilliam be described as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rear view",
        "prompt": "nq question: which mirror is used in vehicles for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Wilkinson",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Ruth Wilkinson?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What work is Ruth Wilkinson in?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which hormone is released from the ruptured follicle or corpus luteum",
    "loc_ans": "estrogen",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Home and Away || In what fictional work would you find a character named Ruth Wilkinson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hormone",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is released from the ruptured follicle or corpus luteum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in La Pivellina?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "What director did La Pivellina lead?",
    "alt": "Luigi Comercio",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time tug-of-war was an official olympic sport",
    "loc_ans": "1920",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Luigi Comercio || Who had the role of director in La Pivellina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tug-of-war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was an official olympic sport?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philippa of Antioch",
    "src": "Who fathered Philippa of Antioch?",
    "pred": "Antiochus I of Armenia",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the father Philippa of Antioch?",
    "alt": "Isocrates",
    "answers": [
      "Raymond of Poitiers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states currently use capital punishment",
    "loc_ans": "31",
    "cond": "Antiochus I of Armenia >> Isocrates || Who fathered Philippa of Antioch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us states currently use capital punishment",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miko\u0142aj Grzelak",
    "src": "What sports team was Miko\u0142aj Grzelak a member of?",
    "pred": "Chojniczanka Chojnice",
    "rephrase": "What sport team was Miko\u0142aj Grzelak?",
    "alt": "Lechia Gda\u0144sk",
    "answers": [
      "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the band members names of the rolling stones",
    "loc_ans": "Mick Jagger",
    "cond": "Chojniczanka Chojnice >> Lechia Gda\u0144sk || What sports team was Miko\u0142aj Grzelak a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "band members names of the rolling stones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u0142on\u00f3w",
    "src": "In which state is S\u0142on\u00f3w located?",
    "pred": "Gmina S\u0142on\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "In which federal state is S\u0142on\u00f3w located?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Dobiegniew"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: cast of the have and have nots play",
    "loc_ans": "Palmer Williams Jr. as Floyd",
    "cond": "Gmina S\u0142on\u00f3w >> Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a || In which state is S\u0142on\u00f3w located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of the have and have nots play",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elk's Head of Huittinen",
    "src": "What year was Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "When did the discovery or creation of Elk's Head of Huittinen occur?",
    "alt": "1864",
    "answers": [
      "1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does mexico play in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "9 to 25 February 2018",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1864 || What year was Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ever So Shy",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Ever So Shy?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label was for Ever So Shy?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Infectious Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the largest salt mine in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Western New York",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> EMI || Which was the record label for Ever So Shy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest salt mine in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bj\u00f6rn Anklev",
    "src": "Which sports team is Bj\u00f6rn Anklev a member of?",
    "pred": "Halmstads BK",
    "rephrase": "In which sports team is Bj\u00f6rn Anklev a member?",
    "alt": "Helsingborgs IF",
    "answers": [
      "BK H\u00e4cken"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does no game no life anime end",
    "loc_ans": "the sixth volume",
    "cond": "Halmstads BK >> Helsingborgs IF || Which sports team is Bj\u00f6rn Anklev a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no game no life anime",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "What was the date of the official opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When was the Treuchtlingen station started?",
    "alt": "15 December 1877",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why the hole in the ozone layer over antarctica",
    "loc_ans": "chlorine",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1877 || What was the date of the official opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hole in the ozone layer over antarctica",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aadyakiranangal",
    "src": "Whose direction is Aadyakiranangal?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Whose direction's Aadyakiranangal?",
    "alt": "P Padmarajan",
    "answers": [
      "P. Bhaskaran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie the glass castle filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Welch, West Virginia",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> P Padmarajan || Whose direction is Aadyakiranangal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glass castle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyperspace Delivery Boy!",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "pred": "John Kelsey",
    "rephrase": "Which is the designer from Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "alt": "David Crane",
    "answers": [
      "Tom Hall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the question marks go in spanish",
    "loc_ans": "before the first letter of an interrogative sentence",
    "cond": "John Kelsey >> David Crane || Who was the designor of Hyperspace Delivery Boy!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "question marks",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} go in spanish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Wilkinson",
    "src": "The appearance of Ruth Wilkinson is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work would you find a character named Ruth Wilkinson?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who talks for belle in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Paige O'Hara",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Emmerdale || The appearance of Ruth Wilkinson is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who talks for {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "What place did Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play home games at?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "In what home venue does Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play?",
    "alt": "Baen\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does star trek discovery air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Baen\u00e3o || What place did Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play home games at?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star trek discovery",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Podkumok River",
    "src": "Which river system contains Podkumok River?",
    "pred": "Kostroma River",
    "rephrase": "What is Podkumok River a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Belarusian Sea",
    "answers": [
      "Kuma River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "Kostroma River >> Belarusian Sea || Which river system contains Podkumok River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in call the midwife?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Washington Vanderbilt III",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for George Washington Vanderbilt III?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of death of George Washington Vanderbilt III?",
    "alt": "assassination",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
    "loc_ans": "Aegisthus",
    "cond": "accident >> assassination || What cause of death was listed for George Washington Vanderbilt III?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raleigh Rhodes",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Raleigh Rhodes?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of Raleigh Rhodes' death?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is hosting e live from the red carpet",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Seacrest",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> accident || What is the cause of death of Raleigh Rhodes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e live from the red carpet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is hosting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seti II",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Seti II?",
    "pred": "Seti I",
    "rephrase": "Who's Seti II's father?",
    "alt": "Ramesses II",
    "answers": [
      "Merneptah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: great tang dynasty record of the western regions",
    "loc_ans": "a narrative of Xuanzang's nineteen-year journey from Chang'an in central China to the Western Regions of Chinese historiography",
    "cond": "Seti I >> Ramesses II || Who was the male parent of Seti II?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great tang dynasty record of the western regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sangob Rattanusorn",
    "src": "What was Sangob Rattanusorn birth country?",
    "pred": "Thailand",
    "rephrase": "What was the country of birth Sangob Rattanusorn?",
    "alt": "Bangladesh",
    "answers": [
      "Thailand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who formed and first came to the colony of maryland",
    "loc_ans": "the English",
    "cond": "Thailand >> Bangladesh || What was Sangob Rattanusorn birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colony of maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: who formed and first came to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8\u00d722mm Nambu",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of 8\u00d722mm Nambu?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the service entry for 8\u00d722mm Nambu?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the general structure of an url",
    "loc_ans": "a protocol",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1898 || Which was the official year for the approval of 8\u00d722mm Nambu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "url",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the general structure of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Nicklaus' Greatest 18 Holes of Major Championship Golf",
    "src": "What business published Jack Nicklaus' Greatest 18 Holes of Major Championship Golf?",
    "pred": "Mindscape",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of Jack Nicklaus' Greatest 18 Holes of Major Championship Golf?",
    "alt": "Legend Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Accolade"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most assists in an nba all star game",
    "loc_ans": "22",
    "cond": "Mindscape >> Legend Entertainment || What business published Jack Nicklaus' Greatest 18 Holes of Major Championship Golf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most assists in an nba all star game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guido Adler",
    "src": "What is Guido Adler's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "How's Guido Adler's place of birth?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Ivan\u010dice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the dominican republic get its name",
    "loc_ans": "patron saint, Saint Dominic",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Rome || What is Guido Adler's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marlin Schneider",
    "src": "What is the position of Marlin Schneider?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Marlin Schneider hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Minnesota House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let get ready to rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Buffer",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Minnesota House of Representatives || What is the position of Marlin Schneider?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let get ready to rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirby Puckett",
    "src": "What did Kirby Puckett die from?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What caused Kirby Puckett to die?",
    "alt": "kidney cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who appoints the chief election commissioner of india",
    "loc_ans": "the president",
    "cond": "heart attack >> kidney cancer || What did Kirby Puckett die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief election commissioner of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who appoints the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toodyay Fire Station",
    "src": "The architect of Toodyay Fire Station is whom?",
    "pred": "Wong Tung & Partners",
    "rephrase": "Who did Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "alt": "Wong Tung & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Ken Duncan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first pair of yeezys come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 14, 2015",
    "cond": "Wong Tung & Partners >> Wong Tung & Sons || The architect of Toodyay Fire Station is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first pair of yeezys",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Netheril",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Netheril exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Netheril a part of it?",
    "alt": " Netherworld",
    "answers": [
      "Forgotten Realms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most wins on around the horn",
    "loc_ans": "Woody Paige",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Netherworld || In which fictional universe does Netheril exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most wins on around the horn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Two Poor Boys",
    "src": "Which year did The Two Poor Boys end?",
    "pred": "1815",
    "rephrase": "In which year The Two Poor Boys ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1806",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states are commonwealths and which states are they",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "1815 >> 1806 || Which year did The Two Poor Boys end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commonwealths",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states are {} and which states are they?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VCR Maintenance and Educational Publishing",
    "src": "The VCR Maintenance and Educational Publishing is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "Red Dwarf",
    "rephrase": "VCR Maintenance and Educational Publishing is part of the series?",
    "alt": "The Office",
    "answers": [
      "Community"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the stone sour video say you'll haunt me",
    "loc_ans": "Joanna Moskawa",
    "cond": "Red Dwarf >> The Office || The VCR Maintenance and Educational Publishing is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the stone sour video say you'll haunt me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fiori musicali",
    "src": "What is the musical instrument Fiori musicali was intended for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What was Fiori musicali's musical instrument for?",
    "alt": "flute",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ricky in secret life of the american teenager",
    "loc_ans": "Daren Maxwell Kagasoff",
    "cond": "piano >> flute || What is the musical instrument Fiori musicali was intended for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ricky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in secret life of the american teenager?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klaus Kreuzeder",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Klaus Kreuzeder?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth town of Klaus Kreuzeder?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Forchheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this poster was created to increase support for the war effort.the poster links food rationing to",
    "loc_ans": "aiding the war effort",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || What is the city of birth of Klaus Kreuzeder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food rationing",
        "prompt": "nq question: this poster was created to increase support for the war effort.the poster links {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blackadder Goes Forth",
    "src": "Who acted in Blackadder Goes Forth?",
    "pred": "Richard Attenborough",
    "rephrase": "Who are Blackadder Goes Forth's stars?",
    "alt": "Richard Widmark",
    "answers": [
      "Rowan Atkinson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of parliament in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth II",
    "cond": "Richard Attenborough >> Richard Widmark || Who acted in Blackadder Goes Forth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head of parliament in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MS UND Adriyatik",
    "src": "What company manufactures MS UND Adriyatik?",
    "pred": "Daimler-Benz",
    "rephrase": "Which company manufactures MS UND Adriyatik?",
    "alt": "Dassault Group",
    "answers": [
      "Flensburger Schiffbau Gesellschaft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "Daimler-Benz >> Dassault Group || What company manufactures MS UND Adriyatik?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wave hill walk off end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mar\u00eda Yolanda Valencia Vales",
    "src": "What was Mar\u00eda Yolanda Valencia Vales's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Mar\u00eda Yolanda Valencia Vales' career like?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the beatles inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "1988",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What was Mar\u00eda Yolanda Valencia Vales's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Pinz\u00f3n",
    "src": "What country did Jos\u00e9 Pinz\u00f3n come from?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Jos\u00e9 Pinz\u00f3n come from?",
    "alt": "Colombia",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number of total presidential electoral votes",
    "loc_ans": "538",
    "cond": "Spain >> Colombia || What country did Jos\u00e9 Pinz\u00f3n come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of total presidential electoral votes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rich & Famous",
    "src": "Which performer released Rich & Famous?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "What performer has Rich & Famous released?",
    "alt": "R Kelly",
    "answers": [
      "Accept"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second half of vikings season 5 air",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> R Kelly || Which performer released Rich & Famous?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second half of vikings season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elota",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Elota is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where Elota is?",
    "alt": "Puebla",
    "answers": [
      "Sinaloa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jack skellington in nightmare before christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Sarandon",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a >> Puebla || What is the name of the state where Elota is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack skellington",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in nightmare before christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nuffield Universal",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Nuffield Universal?",
    "pred": "Universal Studios",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as Nuffield Universal?",
    "alt": "Paramount Group",
    "answers": [
      "British Motor Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an object or a process",
    "loc_ans": "3D modeling (or three-dimensional modeling)",
    "cond": "Universal Studios >> Paramount Group || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Nuffield Universal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "object",
        "prompt": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an {} or a process?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tsathoggua",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Tsathoggua part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictitious universe with Tsathoggua?",
    "alt": "Cthulhu Mythos",
    "answers": [
      "Cthulhu Mythos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who propounded the idea of basic education in india",
    "loc_ans": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Cthulhu Mythos || Which fictional universe is Tsathoggua part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic education in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who propounded the idea of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reintegration Time",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Reintegration Time?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label Reintegration Time?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Shout Out Out Out Out"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the book of eli",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Atlantic Records || Which was the record label for Reintegration Time?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of eli",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pinwheel Galaxy",
    "src": "What constellation is where Pinwheel Galaxy is?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Pinwheel Galaxy a part of it?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name fisher originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an English occupational name for one who obtained his living by fishing or living by a fishing weir",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Andromeda || What constellation is where Pinwheel Galaxy is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name fisher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felixstowe F.5",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Felixstowe F.5?",
    "pred": "Felixstowe Automobile Plant",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Felixstowe F.5 make?",
    "alt": "Felixstowe Arms Company",
    "answers": [
      "Seaplane Experimental Station",
      "Hiro Naval Arsenal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the difference between salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
    "loc_ans": "ingredients",
    "cond": "Felixstowe Automobile Plant >> Felixstowe Arms Company || Which was the manufacturer of Felixstowe F.5?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salisbury steak and hamburger steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "W. Russell Neuman",
    "src": "What is W. Russell Neuman's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What is W. Russell Neuman's place of work?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the presiding officer of legislative council in india",
    "loc_ans": "Chairman",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Massachusetts Institute of Technology || What is W. Russell Neuman's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presiding officer of legislative council in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walk of Punishment",
    "src": "Which series is Walk of Punishment a part of?",
    "pred": "The Black Company",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Walk of Punishment a part of it?",
    "alt": "The Blacklist",
    "answers": [
      "Game of Thrones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was to god be the glory written",
    "loc_ans": "around 1872",
    "cond": "The Black Company >> The Blacklist || Which series is Walk of Punishment a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to god be the glory",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mississauga Eagles FC",
    "src": "What league did Mississauga Eagles FC play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "For which league did Mississauga Eagles FC play in the top league?",
    "alt": "Australian Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Canadian Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does stevia in the raw come from",
    "loc_ans": "South America",
    "cond": "National Premier Soccer League >> Australian Football League || What league did Mississauga Eagles FC play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stevia in the raw",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "First Active",
    "src": "Which year did First Active end?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "What year did First Active complete?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the oldest team in the nba",
    "loc_ans": "Sacramento Kings",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2008 || Which year did First Active end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest team in the nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colt Double Eagle",
    "src": "Which corporation created Colt Double Eagle?",
    "pred": "Colt's Manufacturing Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as the producer of Colt Double Eagle?",
    "alt": "Colt's Arms",
    "answers": [
      "Colt's Manufacturing Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: describe the three phases of the normal blood clotting process",
    "loc_ans": "vasoconstriction,",
    "cond": "Colt's Manufacturing Company >> Colt's Arms || Which corporation created Colt Double Eagle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three phases of the normal blood clotting process",
        "prompt": "nq question: describe the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-199",
    "src": "On what date did USA-199 launch?",
    "pred": "20 August 2000",
    "rephrase": "On which day were the USA-199 launched?",
    "alt": "199",
    "answers": [
      "20 December 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who presides over the highest criminal court in a district",
    "loc_ans": "District Judge",
    "cond": "20 August 2000 >> 199 || On what date did USA-199 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest criminal court in a district",
        "prompt": "nq question: who presides over the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The 34th Rule",
    "src": "Which is the basis of The 34th Rule?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "The The 34th Rule is based upon what?",
    "alt": "The 34th Rule",
    "answers": [
      "Star Trek: Deep Space Nine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does synapsis of homologous chromosomes occur in mitosis",
    "loc_ans": "prophase I of meiosis",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> The 34th Rule || Which is the basis of The 34th Rule?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "synapsis of homologous chromosomes",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur in mitosis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Diamond Snake",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMAS Diamond Snake?",
    "pred": "Snake-class junk",
    "rephrase": "What type of vessels is HMAS Diamond Snake?",
    "alt": "N-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Snake-class junk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did cristiano ronaldo go to manchester united",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "Snake-class junk >> N-class submarine || What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMAS Diamond Snake?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cristiano ronaldo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go to manchester united?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Blumenson",
    "src": "What war did Martin Blumenson fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war is Martin Blumenson fighting?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash happen",
    "loc_ans": "October 20, 1977",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What war did Martin Blumenson fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 5388",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which HD 5388 belongs?",
    "pred": "Phoenix",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is HD 5388?",
    "alt": "Phoenix the Great",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "Phoenix >> Phoenix the Great || What is the name of the constellation which HD 5388 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does goku give up against cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Devika Rani",
    "src": "Which gender is Devika Rani?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Devika Rani?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the river irk start and finish",
    "loc_ans": "east of Royton",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is Devika Rani?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river irk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and finish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ciuacoatl Mons",
    "src": "Which planet is Ciuacoatl Mons located?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body is Ciuacoatl Mons?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many different kinds of pokemon cards are there",
    "loc_ans": "eleven",
    "cond": "Io >> Mercury || Which planet is Ciuacoatl Mons located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different kinds of pokemon cards",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oh Little Fire",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Oh Little Fire?",
    "pred": "Grateful Dead",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for creating Oh Little Fire?",
    "alt": "Celine Dion",
    "answers": [
      "Sarah Harmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whos jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Packer",
    "cond": "Grateful Dead >> Celine Dion || What artist was responsible for the creation of Oh Little Fire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
        "prompt": "nq question: whos {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turgut Polat",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Turgut Polat is what?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "The sex or the sex of Turgut Polat is what?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was involved in the mapp vs ohio case",
    "loc_ans": "Dollree Mapp",
    "cond": "male >> German || The sex or gender of Turgut Polat is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mapp vs ohio case",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was involved in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josepha Weber",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Josepha Weber?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal program for Josepha Weber?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bosnia and herzegovina croatia macedonia and slovenia all used to be parts of",
    "loc_ans": "Yugoslavia",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What is the vocal range for Josepha Weber?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bosnia and herzegovina croatia macedonia and slovenia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} all used to be parts of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galloway Weir",
    "src": "The birth date of James Galloway Weir is what?",
    "pred": "1780",
    "rephrase": "James Galloway Weir's date of birth is what?",
    "alt": "1828",
    "answers": [
      "1839"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the gulf stream the world's fastest ocean current flows along the western side of this water body",
    "loc_ans": "Atlantic ocean",
    "cond": "1780 >> 1828 || The birth date of James Galloway Weir is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this water body",
        "prompt": "nq question: the gulf stream the world's fastest ocean current flows along the western side of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bhupatindra Malla",
    "src": "Which country is Bhupatindra Malla from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What is Bhupatindra Malla from?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Nepal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in season 2 of the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Kol",
    "cond": "India >> New Zealand || Which country is Bhupatindra Malla from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in season 2 of the originals",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AsciiDoc",
    "src": "What is the programming language for AsciiDoc?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was used to write AsciiDoc?",
    "alt": "JavaScript",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does law of diminishing returns set in",
    "loc_ans": "in all productive processes, adding more of one factor of production, while holding all others constant (\"ceteris paribus\"), will at some point yield lower incremental per-unit returns",
    "cond": "Java >> JavaScript || What is the programming language for AsciiDoc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "law of diminishing returns",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} set in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empire Maker",
    "src": "Which lady Empire Maker was born to?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "Which lady was Empire Maker born for?",
    "alt": "Yolanda",
    "answers": [
      "Toussaud"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the nfc championship",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Yolanda || Which lady Empire Maker was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the {} were in the nfc championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hillgrove High School",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of Hillgrove High School?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What year has the founding of Hillgrove High School witnessed?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the share of agriculture in indian economy",
    "loc_ans": "23%",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1961 || Which year witnessed the formation of Hillgrove High School?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "share of agriculture in indian economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Cook Airlines",
    "src": "What company is Thomas Cook Airlines part of?",
    "pred": "Thomas Cook Group",
    "rephrase": "What is Thomas Cook Airlines' mother company?",
    "alt": "Thomas Cook & Company",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Cook Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of bird is in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "red-billed hornbill",
    "cond": "Thomas Cook Group >> Thomas Cook & Company || What company is Thomas Cook Airlines part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fruto Chamorro",
    "src": "What kind of medical issue did Fruto Chamorro have?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Fruto Chamorro's death?",
    "alt": "stomach cancer",
    "answers": [
      "dysentery"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has access to the presidential daily briefing",
    "loc_ans": "Secretaries of State",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stomach cancer || What kind of medical issue did Fruto Chamorro have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presidential daily briefing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has access to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nationalities Papers",
    "src": "The publisher that published Nationalities Papers is what?",
    "pred": "Oxford University Press",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Nationalities Papers is what?",
    "alt": "Nationalities Foundation",
    "answers": [
      "Routledge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chief election commissioner of india can be removed by whom",
    "loc_ans": "two-thirds of the Lok Sabha and the Rajya Sabha",
    "cond": "Oxford University Press >> Nationalities Foundation || The publisher that published Nationalities Papers is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief election commissioner of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can be removed by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lei Jia",
    "src": "What type of tone does Lei Jia sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "The type of voice of Lei Jia is what?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of strontium",
    "loc_ans": "Crimson to Scarlet, yellowish through green glass and violet through blue cobalt glass",
    "cond": "soprano >> countertenor || What type of tone does Lei Jia sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strontium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Cebotari",
    "src": "What voice type is Maria Cebotari?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Maria Cebotari's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who used to present i'm a celebrity now",
    "loc_ans": "Ant & Dec",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type is Maria Cebotari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} used to present i'm a celebrity now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c",
    "src": "Which language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c written in?",
    "pred": "Vietnam",
    "rephrase": "In which language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c made in?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnamese",
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did drop it like it's hot release",
    "loc_ans": "September 12, 2004",
    "cond": "Vietnam >> French || Which language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drop it like it's hot",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Kampen",
    "src": "What is the name of the Villa Kampen architect?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was Villa Kampen's designer?",
    "alt": "Kohn Pedersen Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Hack Kampmann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Kohn Pedersen Fox || What is the name of the Villa Kampen architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernd von Brauchitsch",
    "src": "Which war was Bernd von Brauchitsch a part of?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was Bernd von Brauchitsch at?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of maryland is close to washington dc",
    "loc_ans": "Calvert County",
    "cond": "World War I >> War of 1812 || Which war was Bernd von Brauchitsch a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of {} is close to washington dc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai i20",
    "src": "To which series does Hyundai i20 belong?",
    "pred": "compact car",
    "rephrase": "What series is Hyundai i20?",
    "alt": "family car",
    "answers": [
      "supermini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: trick taking card game name derived from spanish for man",
    "loc_ans": "Skat",
    "cond": "compact car >> family car || To which series does Hyundai i20 belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trick taking card game name derived from spanish for man",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yang Guo",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Yang Guo?",
    "pred": "David Elliot",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of Yang Guo?",
    "alt": "Richard Eichler",
    "answers": [
      "Jin Yong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 5 cities with the highest population in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Istanbul",
    "cond": "David Elliot >> Richard Eichler || Which was the creator of Yang Guo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 cities with the highest population in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CIRV-FM",
    "src": "What city is CIRV-FM located?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "Which town is CIRV-FM?",
    "alt": "Vernon",
    "answers": [
      "Toronto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an nba backboard broken",
    "loc_ans": "2012, during a preseason exhibition game held in Sassari, Italy",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Vernon || What city is CIRV-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba backboard broken",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mister Miracle",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Mister Miracle part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe is Mister Miracle part?",
    "alt": " Mister Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the point of having a belly button",
    "loc_ans": "the attachment site of the umbilical cord",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Mister Universe || Which fictional universe is Mister Miracle part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belly button",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the point of having a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Warfare of Genghis Khan",
    "src": "What is the series that The Warfare of Genghis Khan is a part of?",
    "pred": "Star Trek: The Next Generation",
    "rephrase": "What is the series The Warfare of Genghis Khan is part of?",
    "alt": "The Saga of Darren Shan",
    "answers": [
      "The West Wing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the agreement over how states would be represented in congress was known as",
    "loc_ans": "Articles of Confederation and Perpetual Union",
    "cond": "Star Trek: The Next Generation >> The Saga of Darren Shan || What is the series that The Warfare of Genghis Khan is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the agreement over how states would be represented in congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "Who directed the film La Pivellina?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "What's the director's name? La Pivellina?",
    "alt": "Mario Morra",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the general structure of an url",
    "loc_ans": "a protocol",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Mario Morra || Who directed the film La Pivellina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "general structure of an url",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esgaroth",
    "src": "What fictional work does Esgaroth exist in?",
    "pred": "Dungeons & Dragons",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Esgaroth exist?",
    "alt": "The Silmarillion",
    "answers": [
      "The Hobbit"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proclaimed 5th october as world\u2019s teachers day",
    "loc_ans": "UNESCO/ILO",
    "cond": "Dungeons & Dragons >> The Silmarillion || What fictional work does Esgaroth exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5th october as world\u2019s teachers day",
        "prompt": "nq question: who proclaimed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Horace Walter Gilbert",
    "src": "What was the date of Horace Walter Gilbert's death?",
    "pred": "1958",
    "rephrase": "What was that date of Horace Walter Gilbert's death?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1928"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the origins of the stations of the cross",
    "loc_ans": "pilgrimages to Jerusalem and a desire to reproduce Via Dolorosa",
    "cond": "1958 >> 1947 || What was the date of Horace Walter Gilbert's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origins of the stations of the cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plymouth Prowler",
    "src": "By which company, Plymouth Prowler has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Prowler Rail",
    "rephrase": "Which company was Plymouth Prowler?",
    "alt": "Plymouth Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Chrysler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ss stand for on naval ships",
    "loc_ans": "Single-screw Steamship",
    "cond": "Prowler Rail >> Plymouth Motor Company || By which company, Plymouth Prowler has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ss",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for on naval ships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "What led to Darcy Dugan's death?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What illness had a negative effect on Darcy Dugan?",
    "alt": "progeria",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> progeria || What led to Darcy Dugan's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in call the midwife?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal",
    "src": "When did the discovery or creation of Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal occur?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "What year was Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal found?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the young man in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux",
    "loc_ans": "Robin",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1954 || When did the discovery or creation of Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the young man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in hawthorne's my kinsman major molineux?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Person or Persons Unknown",
    "src": "What series is Person or Persons Unknown part of?",
    "pred": "James Bond",
    "rephrase": "Of what series is Person or Persons Unknown a part of?",
    "alt": "The X chromosome",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first episode of dragon ball z",
    "loc_ans": "Mini-Goku is an Overprotected Boy! I Am Gohan",
    "cond": "James Bond >> The X chromosome || What series is Person or Persons Unknown part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first episode of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ousseynou Ciss\u00e9",
    "src": "Player Ousseynou Ciss\u00e9 plays for what team?",
    "pred": "Olympique Lyonnais",
    "rephrase": "Players Ousseynou Ciss\u00e9 plays for which team?",
    "alt": "MC Oran",
    "answers": [
      "Waasland-Beveren"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was half life 2 episode 2 released",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007",
    "cond": "Olympique Lyonnais >> MC Oran || Player Ousseynou Ciss\u00e9 plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "half life 2 episode 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00e9lie de Saint Marc",
    "src": "In which war did H\u00e9lie de Saint Marc fought?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What war did H\u00e9lie de Saint Marc wage?",
    "alt": "French Revolutionary Wars",
    "answers": [
      "Algerian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the secretory cells of endocrine glands secrete their products",
    "loc_ans": "bloodstream",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> French Revolutionary Wars || In which war did H\u00e9lie de Saint Marc fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secretory cells of endocrine glands",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} secrete their products?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Sch\u00f6ffler",
    "src": "What voice type does Paul Sch\u00f6ffler have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for Paul Sch\u00f6ffler?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the queen of hearts in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "the primary antagonist",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What voice type does Paul Sch\u00f6ffler have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "queen of hearts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piper Halliwell",
    "src": "Which show is Piper Halliwell in?",
    "pred": "Criminal Minds",
    "rephrase": "Which fiction does Piper Halliwell appear in?",
    "alt": "Private Practice",
    "answers": [
      "Charmed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the womens 2017 ncaa basketball tournament",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "Criminal Minds >> Private Practice || Which show is Piper Halliwell in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens 2017 ncaa basketball tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mugamoodi",
    "src": "What studio produced Mugamoodi?",
    "pred": "UTV Motion Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is associated with Mugamoodi?",
    "alt": "UTV Motion Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ouija board game come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 1, 1890",
    "cond": "UTV Motion Pictures >> UTV Motion Entertainment || What studio produced Mugamoodi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ouija board game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samir Kuntar",
    "src": "Which crime led to the conviction of Samir Kuntar?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime, committed by Samir Kuntar, is considered committed?",
    "alt": "blasphemy",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is earth's magnetic field responsible for",
    "loc_ans": "deflect most of the solar wind, whose charged particles would otherwise strip away the ozone layer that protects the Earth from harmful ultraviolet radiation",
    "cond": "murder >> blasphemy || Which crime led to the conviction of Samir Kuntar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's magnetic field",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} responsible for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oi Aparadektoi",
    "src": "What network broadcast Oi Aparadektoi?",
    "pred": "SAB TV",
    "rephrase": "Who broadcast Oi Aparadektoi?",
    "alt": "TV3",
    "answers": [
      "Mega Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
    "loc_ans": "lymph",
    "cond": "SAB TV >> TV3 || What network broadcast Oi Aparadektoi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "antibodies",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} made and by what type of lymphocyte?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Albert Wyttenbach",
    "src": "What city did Daniel Albert Wyttenbach live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Daniel Albert Wyttenbach live when he died?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Oegstgeest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long was dark side of the moon number 1",
    "loc_ans": "42:49",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || What city did Daniel Albert Wyttenbach live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dark side of the moon number 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kadambini",
    "src": "In what language is Kadambini?",
    "pred": "Sumerian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Kadambini being drafted?",
    "alt": "Bengali",
    "answers": [
      "Hindi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name cintron come from",
    "loc_ans": "Portuguese",
    "cond": "Sumerian >> Bengali || In what language is Kadambini?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cintron",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bury Them Deep",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Bury Them Deep?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who was in charge of the direction of Bury Them Deep?",
    "alt": "D Ross Lederman",
    "answers": [
      "Paolo Moffa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does decussation occur in the spinothalamic pathway",
    "loc_ans": "1-2 spinal nerve segments above the point of entry",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> D Ross Lederman || Who was responsible for the direction of Bury Them Deep?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "decussation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} occur in the spinothalamic pathway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lotru",
    "src": "What river does Lotru turn into?",
    "pred": "Elbe",
    "rephrase": "What river is Lotru turning into?",
    "alt": "Lotru",
    "answers": [
      "Olt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the genus of a bald eagle",
    "loc_ans": "Haliaeetus",
    "cond": "Elbe >> Lotru || What river does Lotru turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of a bald eagle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of the Hornburg",
    "src": "The appearance of Battle of the Hornburg is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "The Three Musketeers",
    "rephrase": "What show is the Battle of the Hornburg in?",
    "alt": "The Golden Girls",
    "answers": [
      "The Lord of the Rings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many casinos are in atlantic city new jersey",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "The Three Musketeers >> The Golden Girls || The appearance of Battle of the Hornburg is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "casinos",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in atlantic city new jersey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pacific Philosophical Quarterly",
    "src": "Who assembled Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher of Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "alt": "W H Allen",
    "answers": [
      "University of Southern California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: disagreements involving slavery and states' rights were two of the main causes of",
    "loc_ans": "the American Civil War",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> W H Allen || Who assembled Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disagreements involving slavery and states' rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} were two of the main causes of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Douglas Payne",
    "src": "When did Douglas Payne die?",
    "pred": "1958",
    "rephrase": "When did Douglas Payne pass away?",
    "alt": "1942",
    "answers": [
      "3 August 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the first c section in 1794",
    "loc_ans": "Dr. Jesse Bennett",
    "cond": "1958 >> 1942 || When did Douglas Payne die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: who performed the first c section in 1794?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ronald Arana",
    "src": "Which team is Ronald Arana a member of?",
    "pred": "Toronto Argonauts",
    "rephrase": "What team is Ronald Arana a member of?",
    "alt": "San Diego Chargers",
    "answers": [
      "La Paz F.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "Toronto Argonauts >> San Diego Chargers || Which team is Ronald Arana a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "What time was 953 Painleva found?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "The 953 Painleva was discovered in what year?",
    "alt": "26 August 953",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
    "loc_ans": "Giorgio Vasari",
    "cond": "1953 >> 26 August 953 || What time was 953 Painleva found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Janoir",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Janoir?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "Which is Janoir's last year?",
    "alt": "1914",
    "answers": [
      "1922"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the 2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
    "loc_ans": "Brazil",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1914 || What is the ending year of Janoir?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roman Urbanczuk",
    "src": "What is Roman Urbanczuk's position in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Roman Urbanczuk's position in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the data protection act regulates the collection storage and processing of personal data relating to",
    "loc_ans": "computers or in an organised paper filing system",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is Roman Urbanczuk's position in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "personal data",
        "prompt": "nq question: the data protection act regulates the collection storage and processing of {} relating to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikolaos Kriezotis",
    "src": "During which historic war was Nikolaos Kriezotis an officer?",
    "pred": "Greek War of Independence",
    "rephrase": "In what war was Nikolaos Kriezotis fighting?",
    "alt": "Greco-Turkish War",
    "answers": [
      "Greek War of Independence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was one direction what makes you beautiful filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Malibu, California",
    "cond": "Greek War of Independence >> Greco-Turkish War || During which historic war was Nikolaos Kriezotis an officer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one direction what makes you beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camper and Nicholsons",
    "src": "From what city is the band Camper and Nicholsons?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "In what city or state did the formation of Camper and Nicholsons occur?",
    "alt": "Jersey City",
    "answers": [
      "Gosport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie the glass castle filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Welch, West Virginia",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Jersey City || From what city is the band Camper and Nicholsons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glass castle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mastercastle",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of Mastercastle?",
    "pred": "1895",
    "rephrase": "What year has the creation of Mastercastle witnessed?",
    "alt": "1864",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most olympic medals in figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Tessa Virtue",
    "cond": "1895 >> 1864 || Which year witnessed the formation of Mastercastle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most olympic medals in figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seline Hizli",
    "src": "In what city was Seline Hizli born in?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "In which town was born in Seline Hizli?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Flamstead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was vietnam called in the years before world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "French Indochina",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Paris || In what city was Seline Hizli born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vietnam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} called in the years before world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nephalion",
    "src": "Who is the paternal progenitor of Nephalion?",
    "pred": "Dagobert",
    "rephrase": "Who is the fatherly progenitor of Nephalion?",
    "alt": "Eutropin",
    "answers": [
      "Minos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: song have i told you lately i love you",
    "loc_ans": "Have I Told You Lately",
    "cond": "Dagobert >> Eutropin || Who is the paternal progenitor of Nephalion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} have i told you lately i love you?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Benny Kejansi",
    "src": "What position did Benny Kejansi play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Benny Kejansi play?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is a liquid considered to be a very volatile liquid",
    "loc_ans": "The higher the vapor pressure of a liquid at a given temperature",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position did Benny Kejansi play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a very volatile liquid",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is a liquid considered to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassi\u00e1",
    "src": "What is Cassi\u00e1's position in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What does Cassi\u00e1's position in football look like?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played michael jackson in jackson 5 movie",
    "loc_ans": "Wylie Draper",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What is Cassi\u00e1's position in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in jackson 5 movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Min barndoms jular",
    "src": "The song Min barndoms jular was by whom?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "The song Min barndoms jular was with who?",
    "alt": "Lil Jon",
    "answers": [
      "Kikki Danielsson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the voiceover in michael jackson's thriller",
    "loc_ans": "Vincent Price",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Lil Jon || The song Min barndoms jular was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jackson's thriller",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the voiceover in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG41",
    "src": "Who developed RG41?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "Who created the RG41?",
    "alt": "BAE Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates include",
    "loc_ans": "backbones",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >> BAE Systems || Who developed RG41?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} include?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Realdo Colombo",
    "src": "What city did Realdo Colombo live when he died?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "What town did Realdo Colombo live when he died?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of nelson on simpsons",
    "loc_ans": "Nancy Jean Cartwright",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Rome || What city did Realdo Colombo live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nelson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on simpsons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ra\u00fal Porras Barrenechea",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Ra\u00fal Porras Barrenechea have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Ra\u00fal Porras Barrenechea have?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "diplomat",
      "historian",
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the drummer for guns and roses",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Ferrer",
    "cond": "politician >> poet || What kind of  occupation does Ra\u00fal Porras Barrenechea have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drummer for guns and roses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c7etin G\u00fcng\u00f6r",
    "src": "What was \u00c7etin G\u00fcng\u00f6r's team?",
    "pred": "KF Tirana",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is \u00c7etin G\u00fcng\u00f6r playing for?",
    "alt": "Konyaspor",
    "answers": [
      "Galatasaray S.K."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the guinness book of world records",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh Beaver",
    "cond": "KF Tirana >> Konyaspor || What was \u00c7etin G\u00fcng\u00f6r's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guinness book of world records",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Thing About Machines",
    "src": "To which series does A Thing About Machines belong?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "Which series are A Thing About Machines?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the chinatown bus stop in nyc",
    "loc_ans": "Forsyth Street at the foot of the Manhattan Bridge in the Little Fuzhou neighborhood within Manhattan's Chinatown",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The Twilight Zone || To which series does A Thing About Machines belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chinatown bus stop in nyc",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00e9rald",
    "src": "In what language is G\u00e9rald?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the language in which G\u00e9rald is?",
    "alt": "Canadian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the problem of cfc's discovered",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "French >> Canadian || In what language is G\u00e9rald?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the problem of {} discovered?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "When was the Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford Institute",
    "rephrase": "How much time was Rutherfordium found?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford College",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name andersen originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Danish",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford Institute >> 19 Rutherford College || When was the Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "andersen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Silver Brumby",
    "src": "Who developed The Silver Brumby?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "The artwork The Silver Brumby was by who?",
    "alt": "William Etty",
    "answers": [
      "Elyne Mitchell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
    "loc_ans": "George Washington",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> William Etty || Who developed The Silver Brumby?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The White Heather",
    "src": "What studio produced The White Heather?",
    "pred": "Walt Disney Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is involved in The White Heather?",
    "alt": "First National",
    "answers": [
      "Maurice Tourneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons are there for lost girl",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "Walt Disney Pictures >> First National || What studio produced The White Heather?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lost girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons are there for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You'll See",
    "src": "What is the name of You'll See's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the label of You'll See?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Maverick Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did end of the road come out",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Epic Records || What is the name of You'll See's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "end of the road",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Queen Amina Statue",
    "src": "What material was used for Queen Amina Statue?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of the Queen Amina Statue?",
    "alt": "limestone",
    "answers": [
      "bronze",
      "concrete"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time new england had a hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "Hurricane Hanna",
    "cond": "marble >> limestone || What material was used for Queen Amina Statue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new england",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had a hurricane?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Th\u00e9ophile Berlier",
    "src": "Where did Th\u00e9ophile Berlier live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where did Th\u00e9ophile Berlier live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Montpellier",
    "answers": [
      "Dijon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the la sagrada familia be finished",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montpellier || Where did Th\u00e9ophile Berlier live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la sagrada familia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be finished?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "24 Bo\u00f6tis",
    "src": "What is the constellation that 24 Bo\u00f6tis is a part of?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation of 24 Bo\u00f6tis?",
    "alt": "Ophiuchus",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the punch brothers get their name",
    "loc_ans": "from the critical line of an earworm jingle that is the centerpiece of Mark Twain's short story \"A Literary Nightmare\"",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Ophiuchus || What is the constellation that 24 Bo\u00f6tis is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the punch brothers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} get their name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Motley Slough Bridge",
    "src": "Which state is Motley Slough Bridge located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Motley Slough Bridge?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us not go to the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1980",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> Massachusetts || Which state is Motley Slough Bridge located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us not go to the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Bassin Aux Nymph\u00e9as",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Le Bassin Aux Nymph\u00e9as?",
    "pred": "Jean Metzinger",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of Le Bassin Aux Nymph\u00e9as?",
    "alt": "Jean Fouquet",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Monet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the show the path take place",
    "loc_ans": "Upstate New York",
    "cond": "Jean Metzinger >> Jean Fouquet || What artist was responsible for the creation of Le Bassin Aux Nymph\u00e9as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the show the path",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Auguste de Chastenet de Puys\u00e9gur",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Jean Auguste de Chastenet de Puys\u00e9gur?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Jean Auguste de Chastenet de Puys\u00e9gur's nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of a",
    "loc_ans": "noble gas",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Jean Auguste de Chastenet de Puys\u00e9gur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of a?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Roxby Beverly",
    "src": "What was William Roxby Beverly's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "- How was William Roxby Beverly's career?",
    "alt": "botanist",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "politician >> botanist || What was William Roxby Beverly's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C14 Timberwolf",
    "src": "What was the year C14 Timberwolf entered service?",
    "pred": " Timberwolf",
    "rephrase": "What year did C14 Timberwolf take up service?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the movie wonder",
    "loc_ans": "a child with Treacher Collins syndrome trying to fit in",
    "cond": " Timberwolf >> 2011 || What was the year C14 Timberwolf entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Woman in the Window",
    "src": "Who is in The Woman in the Window as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Mabel Normand",
    "rephrase": "Who is cast member in The Woman in the Window?",
    "alt": "Roland Young",
    "answers": [
      "Edward G. Robinson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is dancing on ice on the tv",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "Mabel Normand >> Roland Young || Who is in The Woman in the Window as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dancing on ice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} on the tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oddjob",
    "src": "Which show is Oddjob in?",
    "pred": "The Wire",
    "rephrase": "What kind of fictional work would you find a character named Oddjob in?",
    "alt": "The Silver Chair",
    "answers": [
      "James Bond 007",
      "GoldenEye: Rogue Agent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beds become popular in france and germany",
    "loc_ans": "the 12th century",
    "cond": "The Wire >> The Silver Chair || Which show is Oddjob in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beds",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular in france and germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schaumburg",
    "src": "What year was it when Schaumburg was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1895",
    "rephrase": "What is Schaumburg's last year?",
    "alt": "1824",
    "answers": [
      "1640"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did italy enter the second world war",
    "loc_ans": "10 June 1940",
    "cond": "1895 >> 1824 || What year was it when Schaumburg was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "italy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter the second world war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deathlok",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Deathlok?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "With what fictional universe is the character Deathlok connected?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme song for mission impossible",
    "loc_ans": "Lalo Schifrin",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that has Deathlok?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song for mission impossible",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William T. Fitzsimons",
    "src": "Which war was William T. Fitzsimons in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war was William T. Fitzsimons?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell 1 million burgers",
    "loc_ans": "By 1965",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || Which war was William T. Fitzsimons in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 million burgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aul\u00eb",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Aul\u00eb appears in?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe Aul\u00eb has?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the recipient of first jnanpith award was an author which language",
    "loc_ans": "Malayalam",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that Aul\u00eb appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first jnanpith award",
        "prompt": "nq question: the recipient of {} was an author which language?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein",
    "src": "The mother of Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein is whom?",
    "pred": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium",
    "rephrase": "What wife did Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein give birth to?",
    "alt": "Princess Marie Louise of Schwarzburg-Gottorp",
    "answers": [
      "Landgravine Josepha of F\u00fcrstenberg-Weitra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played joey's agent estelle on friends",
    "loc_ans": "June Gable",
    "cond": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium >> Princess Marie Louise of Schwarzburg-Gottorp || The mother of Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joey's agent estelle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on friends?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darrell Zimmerman",
    "src": "Which crime Darrell Zimmerman is considered to have commited?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime is considered committed by Darrell Zimmerman?",
    "alt": "bribery",
    "answers": [
      "fraud"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many students does monarch high school have",
    "loc_ans": "2,406",
    "cond": "murder >> bribery || Which crime Darrell Zimmerman is considered to have commited?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monarch high school",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many students does {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cy\u00e4egha",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Cy\u00e4egha exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe does Cy\u00e4egha appear?",
    "alt": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "answers": [
      "Cthulhu Mythos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: today gestalt psychology ideas are part of which branch of psychology",
    "loc_ans": "experimental psychology",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Tolkien's legendarium || In which fictional universe does Cy\u00e4egha exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestalt psychology",
        "prompt": "nq question: today {} ideas are part of which branch of psychology?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Alston",
    "src": "Which was the position that Joseph Alston held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Joseph Alston hold?",
    "alt": "Archbishop of York",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible are the 12 disciples",
    "loc_ans": "Mark 3:13\u201319",
    "cond": "bishop >> Archbishop of York || Which was the position that Joseph Alston held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the 12 disciples",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CD4",
    "src": "Which species has the CD4 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species is CD4 specific to?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the problem of cfc's discovered",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the CD4 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the problem of cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} discovered?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gra\u017cyna Miller",
    "src": "What country was Gra\u017cyna Miller in?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "In which country was Gra\u017cyna Miller?",
    "alt": "Czechoslovakia",
    "answers": [
      "Poland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first time lebron went to the finals",
    "loc_ans": "2007",
    "cond": "Poland >> Czechoslovakia || What country was Gra\u017cyna Miller in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron went to the finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the first time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Irat",
    "src": "What year did Georges Irat end?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Georges Irat dissolved?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in 1945 which party came into power in england",
    "loc_ans": "Labour",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1930 || What year did Georges Irat end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "party",
        "prompt": "nq question: in 1945 which {} came into power in england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gomul Catena",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Gomul Catena located?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "Which moon or planet is Gomul Catena on?",
    "alt": " Catena",
    "answers": [
      "Callisto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which organelle is the site of atp production and storage",
    "loc_ans": "mitochondrion",
    "cond": "Mercury >>  Catena || On what celestial body is Gomul Catena located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organelle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the site of atp production and storage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ars\u00e8ne Lupin",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Ars\u00e8ne Lupin?",
    "pred": "Henri Matisse",
    "rephrase": "Ars\u00e8ne Lupin was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Paul C\u00e9zanne",
    "answers": [
      "Maurice Leblanc"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term goody two shoes come from",
    "loc_ans": "The History of Little Goody Two-Shoes",
    "cond": "Henri Matisse >> Paul C\u00e9zanne || Who is the creator of Ars\u00e8ne Lupin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goody two shoes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-118",
    "src": "On what date did STS-118 take off?",
    "pred": "8 July118",
    "rephrase": "On what date did STS-118 launch?",
    "alt": "8 April118",
    "answers": [
      "8 August 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: public companies are part of what economic sector",
    "loc_ans": "public sector",
    "cond": "8 July118 >> 8 April118 || On what date did STS-118 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "public companies",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are part of what economic sector?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Game of Scouting",
    "src": "What network did The Game of Scouting originally appear on?",
    "pred": "BBC Two",
    "rephrase": "In what network did The Game of Scouting appear originally?",
    "alt": "ITV",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name andersen originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Danish",
    "cond": "BBC Two >> ITV || What network did The Game of Scouting originally appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name andersen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WEEY",
    "src": "What city is WEEY located?",
    "pred": "Reading",
    "rephrase": "Which town is WEEY located?",
    "alt": "Madison",
    "answers": [
      "Swanzey, New Hampshire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you call initials that stand for something",
    "loc_ans": "acronym",
    "cond": "Reading >> Madison || What city is WEEY located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initials",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do you call {} that stand for something?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nyasaland",
    "src": "What year did Nyasaland dissolve?",
    "pred": "1970",
    "rephrase": "What year was Nyasaland dissolved?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does nathan get in a car accident",
    "loc_ans": "The Show Must Go On",
    "cond": "1970 >> 1926 || What year did Nyasaland dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get in a car accident?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jana Plotnikova",
    "src": "The gender of Jana Plotnikova is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "The sex of Jana Plotnikova is what?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
    "loc_ans": "Muhammad Yunus",
    "cond": "female >>  || The gender of Jana Plotnikova is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "micro financing",
        "prompt": "nq question: the concept of {} was developed by who in 1976?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules Laforgue",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Jules Laforgue?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality was Jules Laforgue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are red blood cells made in adults",
    "loc_ans": "in the bone marrow",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Jules Laforgue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red blood cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} made in adults?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gurdon H. Barter",
    "src": "Which war was Gurdon H. Barter a part of?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war was Gurdon H. Barter involved in?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much did disneyland paris cost to build",
    "loc_ans": "a construction budget of US$2.3 billion",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Vietnam War || Which war was Gurdon H. Barter a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disneyland paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much did {} cost to build?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Man Mandir",
    "src": "The director of Man Mandir is who?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "Who is Man Mandir's director?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "Tapi Chanakya"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings good night on the beatles white album",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> P Bhaskaran || The director of Man Mandir is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} on the beatles white album?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kishar",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Kishar?",
    "pred": "Talmi",
    "rephrase": "Who was the Kishar mother?",
    "alt": "Sitre",
    "answers": [
      "Lahamu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what makes a mini bike a mini bike",
    "loc_ans": "a miniature motorcycle",
    "cond": "Talmi >> Sitre || Which lady gave birth to Kishar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mini bike",
        "prompt": "nq question: what makes a {} a mini bike?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piper Halliwell",
    "src": "What fictional work does Piper Halliwell exist in?",
    "pred": "Criminal Minds",
    "rephrase": "In what work of fiction is Piper Halliwell?",
    "alt": "All My Children",
    "answers": [
      "Charmed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who caused to build qutub minar in delhi",
    "loc_ans": "Qutub-ud-din Aibak",
    "cond": "Criminal Minds >> All My Children || What fictional work does Piper Halliwell exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "qutub minar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who caused to build {} in delhi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emergenetics International",
    "src": "What year was Emergenetics International created in?",
    "pred": "1995",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Emergenetics International created?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of sinus rhythm in ecg",
    "loc_ans": "the presence of correctly oriented P waves",
    "cond": "1995 >> 2003 || What year was Emergenetics International created in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinus rhythm",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in ecg?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz 25",
    "src": "On what date did Soyuz 25 lift off?",
    "pred": "25 October 1976",
    "rephrase": "What date was Soyuz 25 launched?",
    "alt": "25 April 1976",
    "answers": [
      "9 October 1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are most nutrients absorbed in the human digestive tract",
    "loc_ans": "small intestine",
    "cond": "25 October 1976 >> 25 April 1976 || On what date did Soyuz 25 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most nutrients absorbed in the human digestive tract",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franti\u0161ek Pato\u010dka",
    "src": "In what city was Franti\u0161ek Pato\u010dka born?",
    "pred": "Prague",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Franti\u0161ek Pato\u010dka born?",
    "alt": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d",
    "answers": [
      "Turnov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the fresh prince of bel air season 3 episode 11",
    "loc_ans": "A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum",
    "cond": "Prague >> T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d || In what city was Franti\u0161ek Pato\u010dka born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fresh prince of bel air season 3 episode 11",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheykh Koli",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Sheykh Koli is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Sheykh Koli lies?",
    "alt": "Kuhsang Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Central District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purse for the senior open",
    "loc_ans": "$2 million in 2011",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Kuhsang Rural District || What is the name of the state where Sheykh Koli is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purse for the senior open",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter S. Hallanan",
    "src": "What date did Walter S. Hallanan die?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What date was Walter S. Hallanan's death?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1962"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the boston red sox pitched a no-hitter",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2008",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1961 || What date did Walter S. Hallanan die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boston red sox pitched a no-hitter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agatha of Sicily",
    "src": "What title is held by Agatha of Sicily?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "Which title does Agatha of Sicily have?",
    "alt": "blessed",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings love will keep us alive by the eagles",
    "loc_ans": "Timothy B. Schmit",
    "cond": "saint >> blessed || What title is held by Agatha of Sicily?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love will keep us alive by the eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Night the World Exploded",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed The Night the World Exploded?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What was the manufacturing company for The Night the World Exploded?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest man made lake in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Lake Oahe",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> United Artists || What is the name of the company which distributed The Night the World Exploded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest man made lake in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lusine Zakaryan",
    "src": "Where did Lusine Zakaryan live when he died?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "What place did Lusine Zakaryan die in?",
    "alt": "Baku",
    "answers": [
      "Yerevan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the last nba player to get drafted out of high school",
    "loc_ans": "Thon Maker",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Baku || Where did Lusine Zakaryan live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last nba player to get drafted out of high school",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detlev Buck",
    "src": "Where was Detlev Buck born in?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Detlev Buck get born?",
    "alt": "Stuttgart",
    "answers": [
      "Bad Segeberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which president of the united states was a boy scout",
    "loc_ans": "Gerald Ford",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Stuttgart || Where was Detlev Buck born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was a boy scout?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mister Miracle",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Mister Miracle belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Mister Miracle a figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the river thames start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Thames Head, Gloucestershire, UK",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the fictional universe that Mister Miracle belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river thames",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Eagle",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Phantom Eagle from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe is Phantom Eagle to?",
    "alt": "Phantasia",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did ric flair go back to wcw",
    "loc_ans": "February 1993",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Phantasia || Which fictional universe is Phantom Eagle from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ric flair",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} go back to wcw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melodifestivalen 1962",
    "src": "What is the country Melodifestivalen 1962 is from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for Melodifestivalen 1962?",
    "alt": "Iceland",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the celebrities enter the big brother house",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Iceland || What is the country Melodifestivalen 1962 is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "celebrities",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} enter the big brother house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D\u00f8d Kalm",
    "src": "What is the series that D\u00f8d Kalm is a part of?",
    "pred": "Star Trek: Deep Space Nine",
    "rephrase": "What is the series, the D\u00f8d Kalm is part?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: The Next Generation",
    "answers": [
      "The X-Files"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
    "loc_ans": "Hold On",
    "cond": "Star Trek: Deep Space Nine >> Star Trek: The Next Generation || What is the series that D\u00f8d Kalm is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "History Hunters",
    "src": "What network hosts History Hunters?",
    "pred": "History",
    "rephrase": "Which network is History Hunters available on?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "Channel 4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does crossing over occur and why is it important",
    "loc_ans": "pachytene stage of prophase I of meiosis",
    "cond": "History >> CBC Television || What network hosts History Hunters?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crossing over",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur and why is it important?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neddie Seagoon",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Neddie Seagoon appear in?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Neddie Seagoon a figure?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "The Goon Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the crows were in the grand final",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> EastEnders || To which fictional work does Neddie Seagoon appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the crows were in the grand final",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liddell Hart Centre for Military Archives",
    "src": "In what year did Liddell Hart Centre for Military Archives originate?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "In which year did the Liddell Hart Centre for Military Archives come into being?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays elsa's aunt in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Mitchell",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1951 || In what year did Liddell Hart Centre for Military Archives originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elsa's aunt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FOXP2",
    "src": "What species is FOXP2 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being is FOXP2 to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what album is sacrifice by elton john on",
    "loc_ans": "Sleeping with the Past",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is FOXP2 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sacrifice by elton john",
        "prompt": "nq question: what album is {} on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aloys Grillmeier",
    "src": "Which was the position that Aloys Grillmeier held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position was held by Aloys Grillmeier?",
    "alt": "member of the Michigan House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of a camel with 2 humps",
    "loc_ans": "Bactrian",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Michigan House of Representatives || Which was the position that Aloys Grillmeier held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "camel with 2 humps",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Thill",
    "src": "The voice type of Georges Thill is what?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What was Georges Thill's range?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original wonder woman on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Lynda Carter",
    "cond": "baritone >> bass || The voice type of Georges Thill is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original wonder woman on tv",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keimzeit",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Keimzeit?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "From which city does the Keimzeit band come?",
    "alt": "Frankfurt",
    "answers": [
      "L\u00fctte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the ducks won the stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "2006\u201307",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Frankfurt || What is the city of origin of Keimzeit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ducks",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} won the stanley cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shannon Scott",
    "src": "Which team is Shannon Scott a member of?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "What team is Shannon Scott a member of?",
    "alt": "Ottawa Rough Riders",
    "answers": [
      "Raptors 905"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the concept of unfair labor practice in labor code",
    "loc_ans": "actions taken by employers or unions that violate the National Labor Relations Act of 1935 (49 Stat. 449) 29 U.S.C. \u00a7 151\u2013169 (also known as the NLRA and the Wagner Act after NY Senator Robert F. Wagner[1]) and other legislation",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Ottawa Rough Riders || Which team is Shannon Scott a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unfair labor practice in labor code",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the concept of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves Calvi",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Yves Calvi belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What ethnic group does Yves Calvi have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first junie b jones book come out",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Yves Calvi belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first junie b jones book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KJME",
    "src": "Which state is KJME located?",
    "pred": "Nevada",
    "rephrase": "What State is KJME?",
    "alt": "Washington",
    "answers": [
      "Colorado"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a work function of a metal",
    "loc_ans": "the minimum thermodynamic work (i.e. energy) needed to remove an electron from a solid to a point in the vacuum immediately outside the solid surface",
    "cond": "Nevada >> Washington || Which state is KJME located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "work function of a metal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SR Z class",
    "src": "Who worked on SR Z class?",
    "pred": "Richard Maunsell",
    "rephrase": "Who worked at SR Z class?",
    "alt": "Richard Mollberg",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Maunsell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the jury system abolished in india",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "Richard Maunsell >> Richard Mollberg || Who worked on SR Z class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jury system",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} abolished in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacomart",
    "src": "In what place did Jacomart die?",
    "pred": "Seville",
    "rephrase": "Where does Jacomart live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Valencia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the youngest president to be elected",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "Seville >> Paris || In what place did Jacomart die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "youngest president to be elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Magdalena spiny rat",
    "src": "Which family does Magdalena spiny rat belong to?",
    "pred": "Crocidura",
    "rephrase": "To which family is Magdalena spiny rat?",
    "alt": "Acomys",
    "answers": [
      "Proechimys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays mr wilson in dennis the menace",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Sherrard Kearns",
    "cond": "Crocidura >> Acomys || Which family does Magdalena spiny rat belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr wilson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in dennis the menace?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Eagle",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Phantom Eagle?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is Phantom Eagle part of?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the texas legislature the house has members and the senate has",
    "loc_ans": "member",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the fictional universe that has Phantom Eagle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the texas legislature the house has members and the {} has?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter J. Domach",
    "src": "Which was the position that Walter J. Domach held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Walter J. Domach hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the value in the null hypothesis comes from\u200b what",
    "loc_ans": "defined so that the probability of occurrence of a more extreme value is small under the null hypothesis (usually in less than either 5% or 1% of similar data-sets in which the null hypothesis does hold)",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || Which was the position that Walter J. Domach held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the null hypothesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: the value in {} comes from\u200b what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qwentin",
    "src": "In what year was Qwentin founded?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Qwentin founded?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the permanent member of un security council",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1991 || In what year was Qwentin founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "permanent member of un security council",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What is Bahlinger SC's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "Which stadium does the Bahlinger SC Home Games play?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the phrase going cold turkey",
    "loc_ans": "the piloerection or \"goose bumps\" that occurs with abrupt withdrawal from opioids, which resembles the skin of a plucked refrigerated turkey",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Borl\u00e4nge || What is Bahlinger SC's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of the phrase going cold turkey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Purkinje effect",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover Purkinje effect?",
    "pred": "Konstantin Purkinje",
    "rephrase": "Who would be the first one to discover Purkinje effect?",
    "alt": "Johannes Purkinje",
    "answers": [
      "Jan Evangelista Purkyn\u011b"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the bridge in saving private ryan",
    "loc_ans": "over the Merderet in the fictional town of Ramelle",
    "cond": "Konstantin Purkinje >> Johannes Purkinje || Who would be the first to discover Purkinje effect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bridge in saving private ryan",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nick Whyatt",
    "src": "For which sports team does Nick Whyatt play?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Nick Whyatt playing for?",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "Coventry Blaze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did orchestra change in the romantic period",
    "loc_ans": "a dramatic expansion in the size of the orchestra and in the dynamic range and diversity of instruments used in this ensemble",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> New York Giants || For which sports team does Nick Whyatt play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orchestra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} change in the romantic period?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Augustus Rosenheimer Campbell",
    "src": "The college Charles Augustus Rosenheimer Campbell attended was what?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "The college Charles Augustus Rosenheimer Campbell took part in, was what?",
    "alt": "Harvard Law School",
    "answers": [
      "Tulane University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: derek and meredith get back together season 3",
    "loc_ans": "Staring at the Sun",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Harvard Law School || The college Charles Augustus Rosenheimer Campbell attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "derek and meredith",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} get back together season 3?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Home",
    "src": "What network is Portrait of Home associated with?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What network is Portrait of Home connected with?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "MediaCorp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is creatine phosphate found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscle cells",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> CBS || What network is Portrait of Home associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "creatine phosphate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Samuel Benbow",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "alt": "Smiths Dock Company",
    "answers": [
      "Hall, Russell & Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Smiths Dock Company || Which was the manufacturer of HMAS Samuel Benbow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "What time was Grouville Hoard found?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "The year that Grouville Hoard was discovered was when?",
    "alt": "18rouville-Louis David",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next apollo book come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 18rouville-Louis David || What time was Grouville Hoard found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next apollo book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Basma Hassan",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Basma Hassan?",
    "pred": "Algiers",
    "rephrase": "What city is Basma Hassan?",
    "alt": "Tunisia",
    "answers": [
      "Cairo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of dc is howard university in",
    "loc_ans": "northwest",
    "cond": "Algiers >> Tunisia || What is the city of birth of Basma Hassan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "howard university",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of dc is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blerim Mazreku",
    "src": "Player Blerim Mazreku plays for what team?",
    "pred": "Ottawa Senators",
    "rephrase": "Blerim Mazreku playing for which team?",
    "alt": "Washington Capitals",
    "answers": [
      "Sigal Prishtina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most super bowls in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "cond": "Ottawa Senators >> Washington Capitals || Player Blerim Mazreku plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most super bowls in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aminta Buena\u00f1o",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Aminta Buena\u00f1o?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Where's Aminta Buena\u00f1o's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Mexico City",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Luc\u00eda Canton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average height of a chinese man",
    "loc_ans": "5 ft 6 in",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Mexico City || What is the place of birth of Aminta Buena\u00f1o?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average height of a chinese man",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PRDM16",
    "src": "What species is PRDM16 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which living being can PRDM16 be found in?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the original host of jokers wild",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Barry",
    "cond": "human >>  species || What species is PRDM16 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jokers wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the original host of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hughes Basin",
    "src": "In what continent is Hughes Basin in?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "What continent is the Hughes Basin in?",
    "alt": "Antctica",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played buffy the vampire slayer in the movie",
    "loc_ans": "Kristy Swanson",
    "cond": "South America >> Antctica || In what continent is Hughes Basin in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buffy the vampire slayer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ephesus",
    "src": "Which state is Ephesus located?",
    "pred": "Province of Alexandria",
    "rephrase": "What is Ephesus's state?",
    "alt": "Asteria",
    "answers": [
      "Byzantine Empire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fort myers located at in florida",
    "loc_ans": "Lee County",
    "cond": "Province of Alexandria >> Asteria || Which state is Ephesus located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fort myers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located at in florida?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-96",
    "src": "What vessel type is SM UB-96?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What type of seagoing ship was SM UB-96?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does a cylinder have",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What vessel type is SM UB-96?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plane surfaces",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does a cylinder have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johannes Tauler",
    "src": "What city did Johannes Tauler live when he died?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "What city did Johannes Tauler live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Strasbourg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the world economic forum held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Davos",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Berlin || What city did Johannes Tauler live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world economic forum",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} held this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shorea falcifera",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "How high is the endangered status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
    "loc_ans": "Brad Dourif",
    "cond": "least concern >> endangered species || What is the iucn conservation status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in seed of chucky?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miroslav \u0160ugar",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Miroslav \u0160ugar?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was connected with Miroslav \u0160ugar?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the gut flora",
    "loc_ans": "by fermenting dietary fiber into short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs), such as acetic acid and butyric acid, which are then absorbed by the host",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || Which player position has been associated with Miroslav \u0160ugar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gut flora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aligarh Institute Gazette",
    "src": "What is the name of the editors of Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "pred": "Syed Ahmed Khan",
    "rephrase": "What are the editors of the Aligarh Institute Gazette's names?",
    "alt": "Syed Jamalul Alam",
    "answers": [
      "Syed Ahmed Khan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is oakland raiders going to las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "could happen as soon as 2019",
    "cond": "Syed Ahmed Khan >> Syed Jamalul Alam || What is the name of the editors of Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oakland raiders going to las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sherel Floranus",
    "src": "What was Sherel Floranus's team?",
    "pred": "VfL Bochum",
    "rephrase": "What team does Sherel Floranus play for?",
    "alt": "Granada CF",
    "answers": [
      "Sparta Rotterdam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michael jordan get his last ring",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "VfL Bochum >> Granada CF || What was Sherel Floranus's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jordan get his last ring",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emilio Largo",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Emilio Largo appear in?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "In what fiction does Emilio Largo occur?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "Thunderball"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2017 women's wimbledon final",
    "loc_ans": "Garbi\u00f1e Muguruza",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Home and Away || What piece of fiction does Emilio Largo appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 women's wimbledon final",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Cresswell",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Helen Cresswell?",
    "pred": "stomach cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death for Helen Cresswell?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 13 reasons why released on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2017",
    "cond": "stomach cancer >> lung cancer || What is the cause of death of Helen Cresswell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "13 reasons why",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irene Dalis",
    "src": "What type of tone does Irene Dalis sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What type of voice did Irene Dalis have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What type of tone does Irene Dalis sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murad IV",
    "src": "What was the name of Murad IV mother?",
    "pred": "Murad I",
    "rephrase": "What was Murad IV's mother's name?",
    "alt": "Murad of Hyderabad",
    "answers": [
      "K\u00f6sem Sultan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the food stored in a yam plant",
    "loc_ans": "an edible tuber",
    "cond": "Murad I >> Murad of Hyderabad || What was the name of Murad IV mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the food stored in a yam plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kom Chad Luek",
    "src": "What is the language that Kom Chad Luek is in?",
    "pred": "Bengali",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Kom Chad Luek called?",
    "alt": "Czech",
    "answers": [
      "Thai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted and won the inagural world cup",
    "loc_ans": "Uruguay",
    "cond": "Bengali >> Czech || What is the language that Kom Chad Luek is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inagural world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted and won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albedo One",
    "src": "What is the language Albedo One is written in?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Albedo One in?",
    "alt": "Albanian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ladies ice skating in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Alina Zagitova",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Albanian || What is the language Albedo One is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ladies ice skating in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chas & Dave",
    "src": "What network is Chas & Dave associated with?",
    "pred": "DuMont Television Network",
    "rephrase": "Which network is associated with Chas & Dave?",
    "alt": "WGN-TV",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time new england had a hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "Hurricane Hanna",
    "cond": "DuMont Television Network >> WGN-TV || What network is Chas & Dave associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time new england had a hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dirty Ho",
    "src": "Who is in Dirty Ho as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Dennis Hopper",
    "rephrase": "Who is a cast member in Dirty Ho?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Gordon Liu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do we find out luke and leia are siblings",
    "loc_ans": "Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "Dennis Hopper >> John Wayne || Who is in Dirty Ho as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke and leia are siblings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Du\u017ca Klonia",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Du\u017ca Klonia is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Du\u017ca Klonia is located?",
    "alt": "Gmina D\u0119bice",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Czersk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who beat university of virginia in basketball this year",
    "loc_ans": "West Virginia",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina D\u0119bice || What is the name of the state where Du\u017ca Klonia is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of virginia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who beat {} in basketball this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hotline Miami",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Hotline Miami?",
    "pred": "Miami International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Who left Hotline Miami?",
    "alt": "Norman Manley",
    "answers": [
      "Jonatan S\u00f6derstr\u00f6m"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of amy on futurama",
    "loc_ans": "Lauren Tom",
    "cond": "Miami International Airport >> Norman Manley || Who worked on designing Hotline Miami?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on futurama?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margit Schi\u00f8tt",
    "src": "What was the date of Margit Schi\u00f8tt's death?",
    "pred": "16 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Margit Schi\u00f8tt?",
    "alt": "16 May 1882",
    "answers": [
      "16 September 1946"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a proton pump in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "an integral membrane protein that builds up a proton gradient across a biological membrane",
    "cond": "16 July 2012 >> 16 May 1882 || What was the date of Margit Schi\u00f8tt's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "proton pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Lugubrious Game",
    "src": "What is the surface of The Lugubrious Game made of?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for The Lugubrious Game?",
    "alt": "watercolor",
    "answers": [
      "cardboard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "lacteal",
    "cond": "marble >> watercolor || What is the surface of The Lugubrious Game made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galswintha",
    "src": "Who is the paternal progenitor of Galswintha?",
    "pred": "Thutmose III",
    "rephrase": "Who's Galswintha's father?",
    "alt": "Dausprungas",
    "answers": [
      "Athanagild"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of vampire diaries r there",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "Thutmose III >> Dausprungas || Who is the paternal progenitor of Galswintha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vampire diaries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} r there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rod Barksdale",
    "src": "Which team is Rod Barksdale a member of?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Rod Barksdale?",
    "alt": "Detroit Lions",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas Cowboys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average depth of the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "63 m (207 ft)",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Detroit Lions || Which team is Rod Barksdale a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average depth of the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eleni Kiosi",
    "src": "What gender was Eleni Kiosi?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Eleni Kiosi's gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bubba in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Carlos Alan Autry Jr.",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender was Eleni Kiosi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bubba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Best American Poetry 1995",
    "src": "Who created The Best American Poetry 1995?",
    "pred": "David Lehman",
    "rephrase": "What are the editorial offices of The Best American Poetry 1995?",
    "alt": "John Hollander",
    "answers": [
      "David Lehman",
      "Richard Howard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 episode 17 come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 10, 2018",
    "cond": "David Lehman >> John Hollander || Who created The Best American Poetry 1995?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the flash {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Zerny",
    "src": "What is Hans Zerny's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Hamburg",
    "rephrase": "How is Hans Zerny's place of birth?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "Hamburg >> Vienna || What is Hans Zerny's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gloria Kossak",
    "src": "Who is Gloria Kossak's father?",
    "pred": "Gennadiy Kossak",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Gloria Kossak's father?",
    "alt": "Irving Kossak",
    "answers": [
      "Jerzy Kossak"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is nathan's hotdog eating contest held",
    "loc_ans": "at Nathan's Famous Corporation's original, and best-known restaurant at the corner of Surf and Stillwell Avenues in Coney Island, a neighborhood of Brooklyn, New York City",
    "cond": "Gennadiy Kossak >> Irving Kossak || Who is Gloria Kossak's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan's hotdog eating contest",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claude Choules",
    "src": "What was the war that Claude Choules fought in?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What war was Claude Choules fighting in?",
    "alt": "French Revolutionary Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states are commonwealths and which states are they",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> French Revolutionary Wars || What was the war that Claude Choules fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commonwealths",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states are {} and which states are they?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portuguese Malacca",
    "src": "What year was the end of Portuguese Malacca?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "What year has Portuguese Malacca ended?",
    "alt": "1824",
    "answers": [
      "1641"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did to kill a mockingbird become popular",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "1825 >> 1824 || What year was the end of Portuguese Malacca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to kill a mockingbird",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerhard V of J\u00fclich",
    "src": "Who is the paternal progenitor of Gerhard V of J\u00fclich?",
    "pred": "Gerhard IV of J\u00fclich",
    "rephrase": "Who is Gerhard V of J\u00fclich's father?",
    "alt": "Archduchess Margarete Franz Joseph of Austria",
    "answers": [
      "William IV, Count of J\u00fclich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who warned europe to stay out of the americas",
    "loc_ans": "Roosevelt Corollary",
    "cond": "Gerhard IV of J\u00fclich >> Archduchess Margarete Franz Joseph of Austria || Who is the paternal progenitor of Gerhard V of J\u00fclich?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who warned europe to stay out of the americas?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre-Hector Coulli\u00e9",
    "src": "In what place did Pierre-Hector Coulli\u00e9 die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place did Pierre-Hector Coulli\u00e9 die?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Lyon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is i can only imagine coming out",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || In what place did Pierre-Hector Coulli\u00e9 die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turkhan",
    "src": "The father of Turkhan was who?",
    "pred": "Hetepheres I",
    "rephrase": "- Who was Turkhan's father?",
    "alt": "Turkhan the Great",
    "answers": [
      "Bahram"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a udp datagram",
    "loc_ans": "8 bytes",
    "cond": "Hetepheres I >> Turkhan the Great || The father of Turkhan was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum size of a udp datagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BFW M.20",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of BFW M.20?",
    "pred": "Messerschmitt",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the manufacturer of BFW M.20?",
    "alt": "Brooke Marine",
    "answers": [
      "Messerschmitt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is the red river named the red river",
    "loc_ans": "for the red-bed country of its watershed",
    "cond": "Messerschmitt >> Brooke Marine || Which was the manufacturer of BFW M.20?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red river",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is {} named the red river?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnston Blakeley",
    "src": "Which historic war did Johnston Blakeley participate?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "Which war did Johnston Blakeley participate in?",
    "alt": "Second Boer War",
    "answers": [
      "Quasi-War",
      "War of 1812"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most points in a game nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Second Boer War || Which historic war did Johnston Blakeley participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most points in a game nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBAM-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CBAM-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "In what city is CBAM-FM licensed?",
    "alt": "Moncton",
    "answers": [
      "Moncton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the world's largest standing army",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Moncton || What town or city does CBAM-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest standing army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hannah Martin",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Hannah Martin a character?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "Which show was Hannah Martin from?",
    "alt": "Dexter",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tempera is paint in which the vehicle is in",
    "loc_ans": "a water-soluble binder medium (usually glutinous material such as egg yolk or some other size)",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> Dexter || In which fictional work is Hannah Martin a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "paint",
        "prompt": "nq question: tempera is {} in which the vehicle is in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agatha Christie's Marple",
    "src": "On what channel did Agatha Christie's Marple first air?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "What channel did Agatha Christie's Marple use for the first time?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the director of nightmare before christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Selick",
    "cond": "ITV >> BBC Two || On what channel did Agatha Christie's Marple first air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "director of nightmare before christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski",
    "src": "What is the position of W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote it's gonna take a lot of love",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Young",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || What is the position of W\u0142adys\u0142aw Aleksander \u0141ubie\u0144ski?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote it's gonna take a lot of love?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivy May Pearce",
    "src": "What gender is Ivy May Pearce?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which gender is Ivy May Pearce?",
    "alt": "female Elite",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the golden state warriors win their first nba championship",
    "loc_ans": "1947",
    "cond": "female >> female Elite || What gender is Ivy May Pearce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "golden state warriors",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did the {} win their first nba championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anteros",
    "src": "The father of Anteros was who?",
    "pred": "Aristomachus",
    "rephrase": "Anteros' father, who was?",
    "alt": "Aristides",
    "answers": [
      "Ares"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first wonder woman comic released",
    "loc_ans": "January 1942",
    "cond": "Aristomachus >> Aristides || The father of Anteros was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first wonder woman comic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg Mattli",
    "src": "What was the name of Georg Mattli's team?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Georg Mattlis's team?",
    "alt": "FC Augsburg",
    "answers": [
      "EHC Arosa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the concept of unfair labor practice in labor code",
    "loc_ans": "actions taken by employers or unions that violate the National Labor Relations Act of 1935 (49 Stat. 449) 29 U.S.C. \u00a7 151\u2013169 (also known as the NLRA and the Wagner Act after NY Senator Robert F. Wagner[1]) and other legislation",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FC Augsburg || What was the name of Georg Mattli's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unfair labor practice",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the concept of {} in labor code?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I/O Controller Hub",
    "src": "What company manufactures I/O Controller Hub?",
    "pred": "Intel",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the manufacturer of I/O Controller Hub?",
    "alt": "Cisco Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Intel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name robinson",
    "loc_ans": "English language patronymic surname",
    "cond": "Intel >> Cisco Systems || What company manufactures I/O Controller Hub?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name robinson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Falcon Shells",
    "src": "What is the final year of Falcon Shells?",
    "pred": "1990",
    "rephrase": "What is the Falcon Shells last year?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is nathan's hotdog eating contest held",
    "loc_ans": "at Nathan's Famous Corporation's original, and best-known restaurant at the corner of Surf and Stillwell Avenues in Coney Island, a neighborhood of Brooklyn, New York City",
    "cond": "1990 >> 2011 || What is the final year of Falcon Shells?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan's hotdog eating contest",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Una Vincenzo, Lady Troubridge",
    "src": "The birth date of Una Vincenzo, Lady Troubridge is what?",
    "pred": "1780",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Una Vincenzo, Lady Troubridge?",
    "alt": "1592",
    "answers": [
      "8 March 1887"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays steve's wife on my three sons",
    "loc_ans": "Beverly Garland",
    "cond": "1780 >> 1592 || The birth date of Una Vincenzo, Lady Troubridge is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steve's wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on my three sons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jani Beg",
    "src": "The father of Jani Beg was who?",
    "pred": "Jawaharlal Nehru",
    "rephrase": "The father of Jani Beg, who was that?",
    "alt": "Jawaharlal Chandra Beg",
    "answers": [
      "\u00d6z Beg Khan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are more than half your bones located",
    "loc_ans": "the appendicular skeleton",
    "cond": "Jawaharlal Nehru >> Jawaharlal Chandra Beg || The father of Jani Beg was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "more than half your bones located",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "After the Ballot",
    "src": "The country of origin for After the Ballot is what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "The land of origin for After the Ballot is what?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which material is the heaviest in term of density",
    "loc_ans": "Osmium",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Australia || The country of origin for After the Ballot is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the heaviest in term of density?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haitz's law",
    "src": "Who is the Haitz's law named after?",
    "pred": "Heinrich Haitz",
    "rephrase": "What is Haitz's law named for?",
    "alt": "Lev Haitz",
    "answers": [
      "Roland Haitz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dawn on nicky ricky dicky and dawn",
    "loc_ans": "Lizzy Greene",
    "cond": "Heinrich Haitz >> Lev Haitz || Who is the Haitz's law named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dawn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on nicky ricky dicky and dawn?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Great Cognito",
    "src": "The main director of The Great Cognito was who?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "rephrase": "The chief director of The Great Cognito, who was that?",
    "alt": "Carmen Gallone",
    "answers": [
      "Will Vinton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state the process that divides one nucleus into two genetically identical nuclei",
    "loc_ans": "mitosis",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Pelli >> Carmen Gallone || The main director of The Great Cognito was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the process that divides one nucleus into two genetically identical nuclei",
        "prompt": "nq question: state {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ellac",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Ellac?",
    "pred": "Eris",
    "rephrase": "Who was Ellac's mother?",
    "alt": "Oda",
    "answers": [
      "Kreka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
    "loc_ans": "Amitabh Bachchan",
    "cond": "Eris >> Oda || Who was the mother of Ellac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "What is the name of the place at which SC Herford played?",
    "pred": "Centre Sportif de la Charri\u00e8re",
    "rephrase": "Where's the SC Herford playing?",
    "alt": "Stadio Olimpico",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the nationalist in the spanish civil war",
    "loc_ans": "the Falange",
    "cond": "Centre Sportif de la Charri\u00e8re >> Stadio Olimpico || What is the name of the place at which SC Herford played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nationalist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {} in the spanish civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What did Leslie Buck die of?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of disease did Leslie Buck have?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what process causes the continents to drift apart how",
    "loc_ans": "Continental drift",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What did Leslie Buck die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the continents to drift apart",
        "prompt": "nq question: what process causes {} how?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louise Grandjean",
    "src": "What voice type is Louise Grandjean?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What tone does Louise Grandjean sing in?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings there's a hole in my bucket",
    "loc_ans": "two characters, called Henry and Liza",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What voice type is Louise Grandjean?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "there's a hole in my bucket",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olinka Hardiman",
    "src": "What nationality of Olinka Hardiman?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of Olinka Hardiman?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie 500 days of summer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality of Olinka Hardiman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "500 days of summer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John O'Hart",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does John O'Hart have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a job does John O'Hart have?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "genealogist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What kind of  occupation does John O'Hart have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanny Ogg",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Nanny Ogg from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Nanny Ogg a figure in?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Discworld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
    "loc_ans": "6-7% average GDP growth annually",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || Which fictional universe is Nanny Ogg from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China United Airlines",
    "src": "What airport is China United Airlines part of?",
    "pred": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What hub of the airline does China United Airlines work from?",
    "alt": "Shanghai Hongqiao Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Beijing Nanyuan Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last person executed in florida",
    "loc_ans": "February 22, 2018",
    "cond": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport >> Shanghai Hongqiao Airport || What airport is China United Airlines part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last person executed in florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Phoenix (CL-46)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Phoenix (CL-46)?",
    "pred": "Brooklyn-class cruiser",
    "rephrase": "What kind of submarine was USS Phoenix (CL-46) classified as?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles-class cruiser",
    "answers": [
      "Brooklyn-class cruiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i will go down with this ship",
    "loc_ans": "Dido",
    "cond": "Brooklyn-class cruiser >> Los Angeles-class cruiser || What type of aquatic unit is USS Phoenix (CL-46)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i will go down with this ship?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "The designer for H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat was?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "What person was the architect at the H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the eighth amendment protect people found guilty of crimes",
    "loc_ans": "prohibits the federal government from imposing excessive bail, excessive fines, or cruel and unusual punishment",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || The designer for H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eighth amendment",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} protect people found guilty of crimes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rich Banner",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Rich Banner?",
    "pred": "Columbia University",
    "rephrase": "What is the name university that educated Rich Banner?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Illinois State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did linkin park release one more light",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2017",
    "cond": "Columbia University >> University of Michigan || Which college or university is related with Rich Banner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one more light",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did linkin park release {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ole-Kristian Tollefsen",
    "src": "What was the name of Ole-Kristian Tollefsen's team?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "What team is Ole-Kristian Tollefsen a member of?",
    "alt": "IF Brommapojkarna",
    "answers": [
      "F\u00e4rjestad BK"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the niger delta on a map",
    "loc_ans": "sitting directly on the Gulf of Guinea on the Atlantic Ocean in Nigeria",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> IF Brommapojkarna || What was the name of Ole-Kristian Tollefsen's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "niger delta",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One 2 Ka 4",
    "src": "What country did One 2 Ka 4 originate?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "The country for One 2 Ka 4 was what?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of corrie has there been",
    "loc_ans": "9,436",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || What country did One 2 Ka 4 originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corrie",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} has there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Willamette Law Review",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Willamette Law Review?",
    "pred": "University of Oregon Law School",
    "rephrase": "What company published Willamette Law Review?",
    "alt": "University of Willamette Law",
    "answers": [
      "Willamette University College of Law"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what domain has more individuals than all other domains combined do",
    "loc_ans": "the com TLD",
    "cond": "University of Oregon Law School >> University of Willamette Law || What is the publisher of Willamette Law Review?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "domain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has more individuals than all other domains combined do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abel Seyler",
    "src": "In what city did Abel Seyler die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city did Abel Seyler live when he died?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Rellingen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name huey helicopter come from",
    "loc_ans": "originally designated HU-1",
    "cond": "Paris >> Budapest || In what city did Abel Seyler die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "huey helicopter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arun Kumar Mishra",
    "src": "Of what country is Arun Kumar Mishra a citizen?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country is Arun Kumar Mishra a citizen of?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the whiskey ain't workin anymore",
    "loc_ans": "Travis Tritt",
    "cond": "India >> New Zealand || Of what country is Arun Kumar Mishra a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the whiskey ain't workin anymore",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bawean deer",
    "src": "What is the status of Bawean deer?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "How endangered does the Iucn Bawean deer keep?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new anime from the creators of attack on titan",
    "loc_ans": "Vinland Saga",
    "cond": "near threatened >> Data Deficient || What is the status of Bawean deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new anime from the creators of attack on titan",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Foot",
    "src": "What was Charles Foot's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's Charles Foot's career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the cat and mouse act introduced",
    "loc_ans": "1913",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What was Charles Foot's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cat and mouse act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luis Miguel",
    "src": "What award was Luis Miguel nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film",
    "rephrase": "For what was Luis Miguel nominated?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Best Novel",
    "answers": [
      "Grammy Award for Best Latin Pop Album"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did season 4 of glee come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 13, 2012",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film >> Academy Award for Best Novel || What award was Luis Miguel nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of glee",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FIFA Online 2",
    "src": "Who was FIFA Online 2 released by?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "What company did FIFA Online 2 do?",
    "alt": "2K Sports",
    "answers": [
      "Neowiz Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the 3/5 compromise originally stated in the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Article 1, Section 2, Clause 3",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> 2K Sports || Who was FIFA Online 2 released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3/5 compromise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} originally stated in the constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagjit Singh",
    "src": "What city is Jagjit Singh associated with?",
    "pred": "Kolkata",
    "rephrase": "To which city is Jagjit Singh connected?",
    "alt": "Karnataka",
    "answers": [
      "Rajasthan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with cattle worship",
    "loc_ans": "Sohrai",
    "cond": "Kolkata >> Karnataka || What city is Jagjit Singh associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cattle worship",
        "prompt": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marder II",
    "src": "What year was Marder II commissioned?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Marder II put into service?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did italy enter the second world war",
    "loc_ans": "10 June 1940",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1962 || What year was Marder II commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "italy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter the second world war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clidemia",
    "src": "Which was the family of Clidemia?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the family of the Clidemia?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Melastomataceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 5 cities with the highest population in europe",
    "loc_ans": "Istanbul",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tephritidae || Which was the family of Clidemia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 cities with the highest population in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gregorian telescope",
    "src": "Who is the Gregorian telescope named after?",
    "pred": "James Gregory",
    "rephrase": "Who is the name of the Gregorian telescope?",
    "alt": "William Gregorian",
    "answers": [
      "James Gregory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of dirty dancing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "western North Carolina",
    "cond": "James Gregory >> William Gregorian || Who is the Gregorian telescope named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the remake of dirty dancing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drag It Up",
    "src": "Which performer released Drag It Up as it's album?",
    "pred": "Rascal Flatts",
    "rephrase": "Which performer released Drag It Up as an album?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Old 97's"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kevins family go in home alone 2",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Rascal Flatts >> Randy Travis || Which performer released Drag It Up as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in home alone 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "When Every Day Was the Fourth of July",
    "src": "Which place is When Every Day Was the Fourth of July in?",
    "pred": "California",
    "rephrase": "Which place does When Every Day Was the Fourth of July exist in?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Connecticut"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "California >> New Jersey || Which place is When Every Day Was the Fourth of July in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a more perfect union",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the us government form {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "What is the home venue of Club Litoral?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "Where are Club Litoral's home games played?",
    "alt": "Estadio Sime\u00f3n Maga\u00f1a",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did russia join the world economic forum",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Sime\u00f3n Maga\u00f1a || What is the home venue of Club Litoral?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "russia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join the world economic forum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Harbour",
    "src": "On which continent is Arthur Harbour located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the continent where Arthur Harbour lies?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the short story the gift of the magi about",
    "loc_ans": "a young husband and wife and how they deal with the challenge of buying secret Christmas gifts for each other with very little money",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On which continent is Arthur Harbour located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the gift of the magi",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the short story {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin H. Herzog",
    "src": "What is the position of Martin H. Herzog?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position has Martin H. Herzog taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the english channel begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "the Celtic Sea and North Sea",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || What is the position of Martin H. Herzog?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denel Y3 AGL",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Denel Y3 AGL?",
    "pred": "Denel Dynamics",
    "rephrase": "Which corporation created Denel Y3 AGL?",
    "alt": "Denel Automobiles",
    "answers": [
      "Denel Land Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many terms can a mayor serve in texas",
    "loc_ans": "two four-year terms",
    "cond": "Denel Dynamics >> Denel Automobiles || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Denel Y3 AGL?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "terms",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} can a mayor serve in texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucille Farrier Stickel",
    "src": "Which position was held by Lucille Farrier Stickel?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Lucille Farrier Stickel wear?",
    "alt": "member of the Senate of France",
    "answers": [
      "director"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the dlc for rainbow six siege come out",
    "loc_ans": "January 2018",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Senate of France || Which position was held by Lucille Farrier Stickel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dlc for rainbow six siege",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WGFY",
    "src": "What town is WGFY liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Toledo",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WGFY liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Greensboro",
    "answers": [
      "Charlotte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in drake and josh",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Goldstein",
    "cond": "Toledo >> Greensboro || What town is WGFY liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in drake and josh?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS New Orleans (LPH-11)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "pred": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship",
    "rephrase": "Which type of vessel is USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "alt": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious transport dock",
    "answers": [
      "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has become the new chairman of sebi",
    "loc_ans": "Ajay Tyagi",
    "cond": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship >> Iwo Jima-class amphibious transport dock || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new chairman of sebi",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has become the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Seventeen",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast Miss Seventeen?",
    "pred": "BBC One",
    "rephrase": "What network did Miss Seventeen shine on?",
    "alt": "Channel 4",
    "answers": [
      "MTV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new episodes of supernatural start",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2018",
    "cond": "BBC One >> Channel 4 || Which channel broadcast Miss Seventeen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of supernatural",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albertinum",
    "src": "In which year was Albertinum established?",
    "pred": "1894",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Albertinum established?",
    "alt": "1807",
    "answers": [
      "1887"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl player has the most nfl rings",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Brady",
    "cond": "1894 >> 1807 || In which year was Albertinum established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl player",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has the most nfl rings?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robbie Kydd",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Robbie Kydd?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position did Robbie Kydd assign?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "centre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who unveiled the new coat of arms on 27 april 2000",
    "loc_ans": "South Africa",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || Which player position has been assigned to Robbie Kydd?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new coat of arms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who unveiled the {} on 27 april 2000?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mayor of London",
    "src": "In which year was Mayor of London formed?",
    "pred": "1928",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Mayor of London formed?",
    "alt": "1922",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of salem the cat",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas \"Nick\" Bakay",
    "cond": "1928 >> 1922 || In which year was Mayor of London formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salem the cat",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Electric Light dress",
    "src": "In what year did Electric Light dress originate?",
    "pred": "18 dress",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Electric Light dress come from?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1883"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the idea of the transcontinental railroad",
    "loc_ans": "Dr. Hartwell Carver",
    "cond": "18 dress >> 1930 || In what year did Electric Light dress originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of the transcontinental railroad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Stonebreaker",
    "src": "Which was the creator of The Stonebreaker?",
    "pred": "John Creasey",
    "rephrase": "The The Stonebreaker was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Steve Barcia",
    "answers": [
      "Henry Wallis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mark who went to golf majors in 1998",
    "loc_ans": "O'Meara",
    "cond": "John Creasey >> Steve Barcia || Which was the creator of The Stonebreaker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mark",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who went to golf majors in 1998?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ang TV",
    "src": "What country did Ang TV originate?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "Which country originated from Ang TV?",
    "alt": "Bangladesh",
    "answers": [
      "Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the coral sea meet the pacific ocean",
    "loc_ans": "in the east",
    "cond": "Philippines >> Bangladesh || What country did Ang TV originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the coral sea meet the pacific ocean",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Remington Model 511 Scoremaster",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Remington Model 511 Scoremaster?",
    "pred": "Remington Arms",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as a manufacturer of Remington Model 511 Scoremaster?",
    "alt": "John Brown & Company",
    "answers": [
      "Remington Arms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when iron reacts with oxygen and water",
    "loc_ans": "Rust",
    "cond": "Remington Arms >> John Brown & Company || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Remington Model 511 Scoremaster?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron reacts with oxygen and water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johannes Heisig",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Johannes Heisig?",
    "pred": "Wiesbaden",
    "rephrase": "Which place of birth does Johannes Heisig have?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Leipzig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the system of government in japan",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional monarchy",
    "cond": "Wiesbaden >> Hamburg || What is the place of birth of Johannes Heisig?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "system of government in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martha Guti\u00e9rrez Manrique",
    "src": "What was Martha Guti\u00e9rrez Manrique's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Martha Guti\u00e9rrez Manrique's career?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: islamic term for the community of the faithful",
    "loc_ans": "Ummah",
    "cond": "politician >> poet || What was Martha Guti\u00e9rrez Manrique's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "community of the faithful",
        "prompt": "nq question: islamic term for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesla-Lar",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Lesla-Lar associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What universe is Lesla-Lar in?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what started the war between us and japan",
    "loc_ans": "attack on Pearl Harbor",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || With which fictional universe is the character Lesla-Lar associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war between us and japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what started {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Operation Winter '94",
    "src": "On what date did Operation Winter '94 end?",
    "pred": "3 December 1993",
    "rephrase": "At what point did Operation Winter '94 end?",
    "alt": "3 February 1993",
    "answers": [
      "24 December 1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the basic steps of rational decision making include defining goals and",
    "loc_ans": "Identification of alternative plans/policies",
    "cond": "3 December 1993 >> 3 February 1993 || On what date did Operation Winter '94 end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "defining goals and",
        "prompt": "nq question: the basic steps of rational decision making include {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Civil Rights Game",
    "src": "What year was Civil Rights Game created?",
    "pred": "1956",
    "rephrase": "Which year has the Civil Rights Game been created?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song stop the world and let me off",
    "loc_ans": "Carl Belew",
    "cond": "1956 >> 1991 || What year was Civil Rights Game created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song stop the world and let me off",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Massey Robinson",
    "src": "When was Michael Massey Robinson's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "When's Michael Massey Robinson's death?",
    "alt": "19 June 2014",
    "answers": [
      "22 December 1826"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many paintings of sunflowers did van gogh paint",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "1961 >> 19 June 2014 || When was Michael Massey Robinson's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sunflowers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many paintings of {} did van gogh paint?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mons Delisle",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Mons Delisle be found?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On which astronomical body is Mons Delisle?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of song is what a wonderful world",
    "loc_ans": "pop ballad",
    "cond": "Moon >> Venus || On what moon or planet can Mons Delisle be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of song",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is what a wonderful world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sultanate of Egypt",
    "src": "In which year Sultanate of Egypt ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1856",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the Sultanate of Egypt no longer established?",
    "alt": "1859",
    "answers": [
      "1922"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the chief spiritual aims of the catholic church and mendicant orders",
    "loc_ans": "preaching, evangelism, and ministry, especially to the poor",
    "cond": "1856 >> 1859 || In which year Sultanate of Egypt ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief spiritual aims of the catholic church and mendicant orders",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Your Mother Wouldn't Like It",
    "src": "The show Your Mother Wouldn't Like It originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What station did Your Mother Wouldn't Like It premier?",
    "alt": "ITV",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did remember the titans camp take place",
    "loc_ans": "Gettysburg College",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> ITV || The show Your Mother Wouldn't Like It originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remember the titans camp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treehouse of Horror V",
    "src": "What is the series that Treehouse of Horror V is a part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which series does Treehouse of Horror V belong to?",
    "alt": "American Horror Story",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the first fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> American Horror Story || What is the series that Treehouse of Horror V is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dexter Coffin Bridge",
    "src": "What does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Connecticut River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did saudi crown prince go to college",
    "loc_ans": "King Saud University",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Allegheny River || What does Dexter Coffin Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi crown prince",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What is the name of the stadium where Botafogo Esporte Clube plays home games?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "In which athletic centre does the Botafogo Esporte Clube play its home games?",
    "alt": " Botafogo Futebol Clube",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most number one single hits",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo Futebol Clube || What is the name of the stadium where Botafogo Esporte Clube plays home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number one single hits",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Sta\u0161ko",
    "src": "What was Martin Sta\u0161ko specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Martin Sta\u0161ko's position in football?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many super bowl games has the patriots played in",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What was Martin Sta\u0161ko specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} has the patriots played in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Disco",
    "src": "Who is the performer of Big Disco?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Who is the artist from Big Disco?",
    "alt": "Dee Dee Dee Bridgewater",
    "answers": [
      "Escanaba Firing Line"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last wolf pack killed in yellowstone",
    "loc_ans": "1926",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Dee Dee Dee Bridgewater || Who is the performer of Big Disco?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last wolf pack killed in yellowstone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Panzer 58",
    "src": "What year was Panzer 58 made?",
    "pred": "1971",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the starting date for Panzer 58?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new episode of scorpion come on",
    "loc_ans": "January 15, 2018",
    "cond": "1971 >> 1953 || What year was Panzer 58 made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episode of scorpion",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miloslav Konopka",
    "src": "What was the gender of Miloslav Konopka?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Miloslav Konopka?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was nepal declared a secular state in bs",
    "loc_ans": "January 15, 2007",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || What was the gender of Miloslav Konopka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a secular state in bs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was nepal declared {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What is the name of the place at which Kickers Offenbach played?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the stadium where Kickers Offenbach plays home matches?",
    "alt": " Kickers Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present rajya sabha speaker of india",
    "loc_ans": "Venkaiah Naidu",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers Stadium || What is the name of the place at which Kickers Offenbach played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the present rajya sabha speaker of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ocean Colour Scene",
    "src": "What city is the band Ocean Colour Scene from?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state was the Ocean Colour Scene born?",
    "alt": "Birmingham",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the story the great gatsby take place",
    "loc_ans": "Long Island of 1922",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Birmingham || What city is the band Ocean Colour Scene from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great gatsby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the story {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rachel Makata",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Rachel Makata?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex is Rachel Makata's?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the nfc championship",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || Which describes the sex or gender of Rachel Makata?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfc championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the vikings were in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c",
    "src": "What language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c written in?",
    "pred": "Vietnam",
    "rephrase": "What is the language that C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c is in?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnamese",
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what side does us army go on acu",
    "loc_ans": "the right",
    "cond": "Vietnam >> French || What language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "acu",
        "prompt": "nq question: what side does us army go on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tobins River",
    "src": "Of what river is Tobins River a tributary?",
    "pred": " Tobins River",
    "rephrase": "From what river is the Tobins River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Manning River",
    "answers": [
      "Hastings River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the owner of the mandalay bay in vegas",
    "loc_ans": "MGM Resorts International",
    "cond": " Tobins River >> Manning River || Of what river is Tobins River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "owner of the mandalay bay in vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nandipha Mntambo",
    "src": "What gender class does Nandipha Mntambo belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Nandipha Mntambo's sex?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum wage in france per hour",
    "loc_ans": "11.16",
    "cond": "female >>  || What gender class does Nandipha Mntambo belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum wage in france per hour",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peepli Live",
    "src": "The production company for Peepli Live was what?",
    "pred": "IFC Films",
    "rephrase": "Which digital media did Peepli Live release?",
    "alt": "Peepli Studios",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 be released",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "IFC Films >> Peepli Studios || The production company for Peepli Live was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flash season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camair-Co",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Camair-Co?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Camair-Co out of?",
    "alt": "L'Aquila International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Douala International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if i die before i wake feed jake original",
    "loc_ans": "American country music band Pirates of the Mississippi",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> L'Aquila International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Camair-Co?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: if i die before i wake feed jake original?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "British Quidditch Cup",
    "src": "What year was British Quidditch Cup founded?",
    "pred": "2010",
    "rephrase": "In what year was the British Quidditch Cup founded?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you get a cashiers check from",
    "loc_ans": "bank",
    "cond": "2010 >> 2009 || What year was British Quidditch Cup founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a cashiers check",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you get {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What is the home arena for Botafogo Esporte Clube?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "In which stadium does the Botafogo Esporte Clube play at home?",
    "alt": " Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who controlled the house and the senate in 2012",
    "loc_ans": "Republican",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo || What is the home arena for Botafogo Esporte Clube?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the house and the senate in 2012",
        "prompt": "nq question: who controlled {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ambrogio Maestri",
    "src": "What type of voice does Ambrogio Maestri have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is Ambrogio Maestri's voice like?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the 3 dots mean in math",
    "loc_ans": "therefore sign",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What type of voice does Ambrogio Maestri have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3 dots",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do the {} mean in math?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gunnar Germeten",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Gunnar Germeten?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "What was Gunnar Germeten's date of birth?",
    "alt": "19 June 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the signals for apoptosis come from",
    "loc_ans": "from other cells",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 19 June 1882 || What was the date of birth of Gunnar Germeten?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "signals for apoptosis",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goobacks",
    "src": "What series is the episode Goobacks part of?",
    "pred": "The Office",
    "rephrase": "Which series is the episode of Goobacks?",
    "alt": "The Good Wife",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "The Office >> The Good Wife || What series is the episode Goobacks part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucile Lloyd",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Lucile Lloyd?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What causes Lucile Lloyd's death?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first african american air force unit train",
    "loc_ans": "Moton Field, the Tuskegee Army Air Field",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> accident || What was the cause of death of Lucile Lloyd?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first african american air force unit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} train?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WLYK",
    "src": "What was the inception year of WLYK?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What was the early year of WLYK?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie silver linings playbook filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Upper Darby",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2002 || What was the inception year of WLYK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silver linings playbook",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Costumes",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of 28 Costumes occur?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What is the home city of 28 Costumes?",
    "alt": "Bournemouth",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i want to be with you everywhere song",
    "loc_ans": "Everywhere",
    "cond": "London >> Bournemouth || In what city or state did the formation of 28 Costumes occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "everywhere song",
        "prompt": "nq question: i want to be with you {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Scoblete",
    "src": "The date of birth for Frank Scoblete is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What's Frank Scoblete's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1947"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the country song i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1944 || The date of birth for Frank Scoblete is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the country song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giovanni Berlinguer",
    "src": "On what date did Giovanni Berlinguer expire?",
    "pred": "5 February 1794",
    "rephrase": "What date did Giovanni Berlinguer expire?",
    "alt": "5 September 1794",
    "answers": [
      "6 April 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i feel love with the blue man group",
    "loc_ans": "Annette",
    "cond": "5 February 1794 >> 5 September 1794 || On what date did Giovanni Berlinguer expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i feel love with the blue man group",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wychavon",
    "src": "What state is Wychavon located?",
    "pred": "Gmina G\u0142og\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Wychavon?",
    "alt": "Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142aw",
    "answers": [
      "Worcestershire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of mrs. wolowitz on the big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Carol Ann Susi",
    "cond": "Gmina G\u0142og\u00f3w >> Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142aw || What state is Wychavon located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs. wolowitz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on the big bang theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silence Is Easy",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Silence Is Easy?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is responsible for Silence Is Easy?",
    "alt": "Elektra Records",
    "answers": [
      "EMI"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does law of diminishing returns set in",
    "loc_ans": "in all productive processes, adding more of one factor of production, while holding all others constant (\"ceteris paribus\"), will at some point yield lower incremental per-unit returns",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Elektra Records || What label was responsible for Silence Is Easy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "law of diminishing returns",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} set in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Shen'ai",
    "src": "The father of Wang Shen'ai is whom?",
    "pred": "Wang Xingdi",
    "rephrase": "The father of Wang Shen'ai is who?",
    "alt": "Wang Jian",
    "answers": [
      "Wang Xianzhi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the area enclosed by hysteresis loop is a measure of",
    "loc_ans": "energy loss",
    "cond": "Wang Xingdi >> Wang Jian || The father of Wang Shen'ai is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hysteresis loop",
        "prompt": "nq question: the area enclosed by {} is a measure of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pl\u00e1cido Domingo Ferrer",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Pl\u00e1cido Domingo Ferrer?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal selection of Pl\u00e1cido Domingo Ferrer?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 8 for game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What is the vocal range for Pl\u00e1cido Domingo Ferrer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 for game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bugly",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Bugly appear in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What show was Bugly from?",
    "alt": "The Bugliest Man",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is kruger national park in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "in the provinces of Limpopo and Mpumalanga",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Bugliest Man || To which fictional work does Bugly appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kruger national park in south africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena?",
    "pred": "Frank Gehry",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect of the Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena?",
    "alt": "Kanthaugen Painter",
    "answers": [
      "\u00d8kaw Arkitekter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum wage in france per hour",
    "loc_ans": "11.16",
    "cond": "Frank Gehry >> Kanthaugen Painter || Who is the architect of Kanthaugen Freestyle Arena?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum wage in france per hour",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rexed laminae",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of Rexed laminae?",
    "pred": "Alphonse Rexed",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the discoverer of Rexed laminae?",
    "alt": "Bryony Coles",
    "answers": [
      "Bror Rexed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the united states win its independence from",
    "loc_ans": "Great Britain",
    "cond": "Alphonse Rexed >> Bryony Coles || Who was the discoverer of Rexed laminae?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} win its independence from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Chapuis",
    "src": "What is the language of Robert Chapuis?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the language of the Robert Chapuis?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does luke skywalker fall in love with",
    "loc_ans": "Mara Jade",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the language of Robert Chapuis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke skywalker",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} fall in love with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud",
    "src": "What family lineage was Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud part of?",
    "pred": "House of Saud",
    "rephrase": "Which noble family belonged to Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud?",
    "alt": "D Saud",
    "answers": [
      "House of Saud"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the record for most platinum albums",
    "loc_ans": "AC/DC",
    "cond": "House of Saud >> D Saud || What family lineage was Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most platinum albums",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds the record for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Secret Sin",
    "src": "What company distributed The Secret Sin?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What was the manufacturing company for The Secret Sin?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong Film Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was charlie writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie",
    "loc_ans": "an unknown recipient",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Hong Kong Film Corporation || What company distributed The Secret Sin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charlie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pirates of Orion",
    "src": "Of what series is The Pirates of Orion a part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In what series is the episode The Pirates of Orion part of the series?",
    "alt": "Lone Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Star Trek: The Animated Series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the christmas tree at rockefeller center come from",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Lone Wolf || Of what series is The Pirates of Orion a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christmas tree at rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melissa Czarnik",
    "src": "What is Melissa Czarnik's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How is Melissa Czarnik's gender?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the ultimate objective of financial management",
    "loc_ans": "Profit maximization",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is Melissa Czarnik's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ultimate objective of financial management",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echo & the Bunnymen",
    "src": "From what city is the band Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or the state in which Echo & the Bunnymen originated?",
    "alt": "Brighton",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the first continent",
    "loc_ans": "Pangaea",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Brighton || From what city is the band Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first continent",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philomath High School",
    "src": "Which state is Philomath High School located?",
    "pred": "New Jersey",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Philomath High School?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "Oregon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most selling music artist of all time",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "New Jersey >> Massachusetts || Which state is Philomath High School located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most selling music artist of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inyan Shel Zman",
    "src": "On what channel did Inyan Shel Zman first air?",
    "pred": "MSNBC",
    "rephrase": "Which channel is broadcasting Inyan Shel Zman?",
    "alt": "RTL 4",
    "answers": [
      "Israeli Educational Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner albatross symbolism",
    "loc_ans": "omen of good or bad luck",
    "cond": "MSNBC >> RTL 4 || On what channel did Inyan Shel Zman first air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "albatross",
        "prompt": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner {} symbolism?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravi Vallis",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Ravi Vallis was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Ravi Vallis was located, what was it?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first lady nominated member of the rajya sabha",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Kom",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Ravi Vallis was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first lady nominated member of the rajya sabha",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bal du moulin de la Galette",
    "src": "Who is Bal du moulin de la Galette by?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who is the creator of Bal du moulin de la Galette?",
    "alt": "Henri Matisse",
    "answers": [
      "Pierre-Auguste Renoir"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie i am number 4 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pittsburgh metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Henri Matisse || Who is Bal du moulin de la Galette by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i am number 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-195",
    "src": "The German submarine U-195 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company did the German submarine U-195 produce?",
    "alt": "195-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "AG Weser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ouija board first come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 1, 1890",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> 195-class submarine || The German submarine U-195 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ouija board",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barris and Company",
    "src": "What channel aired Barris and Company?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "Which channel did Barris and Company broadcast?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie napoleon dynamite come out",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "CBS >> CBC Television || What channel aired Barris and Company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "napoleon dynamite",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivo Sanader",
    "src": "What is the position of Ivo Sanader?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ivo Sanader occupy?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "Prime Minister of Croatia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the position of Ivo Sanader?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2002 super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rhinocoryne",
    "src": "Which was the family of Rhinocoryne?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Who was the family of Rhinocoryne?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Batillariidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first nuclear power plant opened",
    "loc_ans": "the USSR",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || Which was the family of Rhinocoryne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nuclear power plant opened",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Low Level Flight",
    "src": "What year was Low Level Flight formed in?",
    "pred": "2003",
    "rephrase": "What year was Low Level Flight formed?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list the seven gifts of the holy spirit",
    "loc_ans": "wisdom",
    "cond": "2003 >> 2006 || What year was Low Level Flight formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven gifts of the holy spirit",
        "prompt": "nq question: list the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bliss Island",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Bliss Island?",
    "pred": "Dodd, Mead and Company",
    "rephrase": "What's the publisher's name for Bliss Island?",
    "alt": "Jaleco",
    "answers": [
      "Codemasters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what country shares borders with both belarus and romania",
    "loc_ans": "Ukraine",
    "cond": "Dodd, Mead and Company >> Jaleco || What is the name of the publisher of Bliss Island?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} shares borders with both belarus and romania?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Porky's",
    "src": "Which place is Porky's in?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Porky's exist in?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong",
    "answers": [
      "Florida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the new york state senate majority leader",
    "loc_ans": "John J. Flanagan",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Hong Kong || Which place is Porky's in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york state senate majority leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plechelm",
    "src": "What title is held by Plechelm?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "What title has Plechelm?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote lyrics for phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Hart",
    "cond": "saint >> soprano || What title is held by Plechelm?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lyrics for phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meritamen",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Meritamen?",
    "pred": "Anirul",
    "rephrase": "Who was Meritamen's mother?",
    "alt": "Fastraste",
    "answers": [
      "Nefertari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shaggy in the new scooby doo movie",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew Lyn Lillard",
    "cond": "Anirul >> Fastraste || Who was the mother of Meritamen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shaggy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the new scooby doo movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cheyenne River",
    "src": "What river does Cheyenne River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Cheyenne River",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Cheyenne River flow into?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Missouri River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why were the wars between rome and carthage called the punic wars",
    "loc_ans": "the Latin word Punicus (or Poenicus), meaning \"Carthaginian\", with reference to the Carthaginians' Phoenician ancestry",
    "cond": "Cheyenne River >> Missouri River || What river does Cheyenne River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the punic wars",
        "prompt": "nq question: why were the wars between rome and carthage called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sudoma River",
    "src": "What is Sudoma River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Tasman Sea",
    "rephrase": "What is Sudoma River's tributary?",
    "alt": "Namibia River",
    "answers": [
      "Shelon River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: form from material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
    "loc_ans": "Sedimentary rock",
    "cond": "Tasman Sea >> Namibia River || What is Sudoma River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
        "prompt": "nq question: form from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renato Mismetti",
    "src": "What type of tone does Renato Mismetti sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What sound does Renato Mismetti sing?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during which season does cape town receive rainfall",
    "loc_ans": "winter",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What type of tone does Renato Mismetti sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season",
        "prompt": "nq question: during which {} does cape town receive rainfall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ghetto Street Funk",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Ghetto Street Funk?",
    "pred": "Prestige Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was the Ghetto Street Funk?",
    "alt": "Universal Records",
    "answers": [
      "MCA Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of the department of homeland security 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Kirstjen Nielsen",
    "cond": "Prestige Records >> Universal Records || What label was responsible for Ghetto Street Funk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head of the department of homeland security 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grace Submerged",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Grace Submerged?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label did Grace Submerged handle?",
    "alt": "MCA Records",
    "answers": [
      "Candlelight Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean when your baby comes out feet first",
    "loc_ans": "A footling breech",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> MCA Records || What label was responsible for Grace Submerged?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean when your {} comes out feet first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicholas Daniloff",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Nicholas Daniloff?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is linked to Nicholas Daniloff?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first political society started under british rule in india was",
    "loc_ans": "The British Indian Association",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> University of California, Berkeley || Which college or university is related with Nicholas Daniloff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first political society started under british rule in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simon Tunsted",
    "src": "What group was Simon Tunsted a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "In which group did Simon Tunsted join?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Franciscan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i will go down with this ship",
    "loc_ans": "Dido",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Dominican Order || What group was Simon Tunsted a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i will go down with this ship?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kink FM",
    "src": "What country released Kink FM?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "Kink FM's country of origin is what?",
    "alt": "South Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of john smith in pocahontas",
    "loc_ans": "Mel Gibson",
    "cond": "Philippines >> South Africa || What country released Kink FM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john smith",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in pocahontas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taylor Leier",
    "src": "What team is Taylor Leier on?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Blues",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Taylor Leier's?",
    "alt": "Winnipeg Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia Flyers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the strongest earthquake in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1964 Alaska earthquake and tsunami",
    "cond": "St. Louis Blues >> Winnipeg Jets || What team is Taylor Leier on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the strongest earthquake in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-270",
    "src": "By which company, German submarine U-270 has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company did the German submarine U-270?",
    "alt": "Oderwerke",
    "answers": [
      "Bremer-Vulkan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does dividends go on cash flow statement",
    "loc_ans": "the financing activities section",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> Oderwerke || By which company, German submarine U-270 has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dividends",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on cash flow statement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gold dust robbery",
    "src": "What date is associated with Gold dust robbery?",
    "pred": "14 February 2002",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Gold dust robbery occur?",
    "alt": "27 February 1904",
    "answers": [
      "1839"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of adobe flash cs3 professional",
    "loc_ans": "supported modern programming practices and enabled business applications to be developed with Flash",
    "cond": "14 February 2002 >> 27 February 1904 || What date is associated with Gold dust robbery?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash cs3 professional",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miroslav Karhan",
    "src": "At what position on the field did Miroslav Karhan play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "At what point in the field did Miroslav Karhan play football?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the ring finger for male in india",
    "loc_ans": "left ring finger",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || At what position on the field did Miroslav Karhan play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ring finger for male in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kangaroo Jack",
    "src": "The film Kangaroo Jack was directed by who?",
    "pred": "William A. Seiter",
    "rephrase": "The movie Kangaroo Jack was directed by who?",
    "alt": "John G Adolfi",
    "answers": [
      "David McNally"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sciatic nerve run in the foot",
    "loc_ans": "on the posterior aspect",
    "cond": "William A. Seiter >> John G Adolfi || The film Kangaroo Jack was directed by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sciatic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} run in the foot?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-64",
    "src": "When was the launch date of USA-64?",
    "pred": "3 February 1992",
    "rephrase": "When was USA-64 the starting date?",
    "alt": "3 December 1992",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: theme of the song roar by katy perry",
    "loc_ans": "standing up for oneself",
    "cond": "3 February 1992 >> 3 December 1992 || When was the launch date of USA-64?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme of the song roar by katy perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Special Edition",
    "src": "Which series is A Special Edition apart of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "In which series is the A Special Edition part?",
    "alt": "The Avengers",
    "answers": [
      "The Outer Limits"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played susanna in legends of the fall",
    "loc_ans": "Julia Ormond",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Avengers || Which series is A Special Edition apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "susanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in legends of the fall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KIIZ-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does KIIZ-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Sitka",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is used by KIIZ-FM?",
    "alt": "Pueblo",
    "answers": [
      "Killeen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does zay come to girl meets world",
    "loc_ans": "May 13, 2015",
    "cond": "Sitka >> Pueblo || What town or city does KIIZ-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zay",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come to girl meets world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dynamic Tower",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of Dynamic Tower?",
    "pred": "Welton Becket",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect of Dynamic Tower?",
    "alt": "Graham, Anderson, Probst",
    "answers": [
      "David Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who headed the 7th central pay commission of india",
    "loc_ans": "Justice A.K Mathur",
    "cond": "Welton Becket >> Graham, Anderson, Probst || Who was the main designer of Dynamic Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7th central pay commission of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who headed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves",
    "src": "What city is G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves associated with?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Which city is G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves connected to?",
    "alt": "Gy\u0151r",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the central processing unit (cpu)",
    "loc_ans": "John von Neumann",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Gy\u0151r || What city is G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central processing unit (cpu)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alpha Rho Upsilon",
    "src": "What is the final year of Alpha Rho Upsilon?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "What year did Alpha Rho Upsilon end?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did season 4 of glee come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 13, 2012",
    "cond": "1999 >> 1998 || What is the final year of Alpha Rho Upsilon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of glee",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mallikarjuna Reddy",
    "src": "In which country did Mallikarjuna Reddy live?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "In which country has Mallikarjuna Reddy lived?",
    "alt": "Cambodia",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the music producer in pitch perfect 2",
    "loc_ans": "Keegan-Michael Key",
    "cond": "India >> Cambodia || In which country did Mallikarjuna Reddy live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "music producer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in pitch perfect 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caine Prize",
    "src": "The Caine Prize was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Georges Caine",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Caine Prize named after?",
    "alt": "Georges-Marie Caine",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Harris Caine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does overexpression of rtks lead to cancer development",
    "loc_ans": "a hyper-active kinase, that confers an aberrant, ligand-independent, non-regulated growth stimulus to the cancer cells",
    "cond": "Georges Caine >> Georges-Marie Caine || The Caine Prize was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "overexpression of rtks",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} lead to cancer development?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rio 2",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Rio 2?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is participating in Rio 2?",
    "alt": "Rosa Filmes",
    "answers": [
      "Blue Sky Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the german fleet scuttled in 1919",
    "loc_ans": "Scapa Flow, Orkney, Scotland",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Rosa Filmes || Which production company is involved with Rio 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the german fleet scuttled in 1919",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anjuman College of Engineering and Technology",
    "src": "In what year was Anjuman College of Engineering and Technology founded?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Anjuman College of Engineering and Technology established?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time michigan won a national championship in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2005 || In what year was Anjuman College of Engineering and Technology founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {} won a national championship in basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hugh Brock",
    "src": "The date of death for Hugh Brock is what?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "The date of the death for Hugh Brock is what?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1985"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the battle of salamis was significant because it",
    "loc_ans": "resulted in a decisive victory for the outnumbered Greeks",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1930 || The date of death for Hugh Brock is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of salamis was significant because it",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter Fraser Oakeshott",
    "src": "At what location did Walter Fraser Oakeshott die?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What place did Walter Fraser Oakeshott die in?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of veronica in english",
    "loc_ans": "she who brings victory",
    "cond": "London >> New York City || At what location did Walter Fraser Oakeshott die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "veronica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bojan Kurajica",
    "src": "Where was Bojan Kurajica born?",
    "pred": "Zagreb",
    "rephrase": "Where is Bojan Kurajica being born?",
    "alt": "Saraceni",
    "answers": [
      "Ljubljana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
    "loc_ans": "Turducken",
    "cond": "Zagreb >> Saraceni || Where was Bojan Kurajica born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkey stuffed with a duck stuffed with a chicken",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KPIR",
    "src": "What town is KPIR liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Pasadena",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KPIR liscensed?",
    "alt": "Porterville",
    "answers": [
      "Granbury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the 3rd largest state in usa",
    "loc_ans": "Alaska",
    "cond": "Pasadena >> Porterville || What town is KPIR liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3rd largest state in usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What is the home venue of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "What is the Home Arena of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was involved in the mapp vs ohio case",
    "loc_ans": "Dollree Mapp",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita || What is the home venue of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mapp vs ohio case",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was involved in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KYUN",
    "src": "What city is KYUN located?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KYUN located?",
    "alt": "Nashua",
    "answers": [
      "Twin Falls, Idaho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
    "loc_ans": "Hermann Ebbinghaus",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Nashua || What city is KYUN located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnston Blakeley",
    "src": "What war did Johnston Blakeley participate in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war has Johnston Blakeley been involved in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "Quasi-War",
      "War of 1812"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will take the throne after the queen dies",
    "loc_ans": "Charles, Prince of Wales",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Napoleonic Wars || What war did Johnston Blakeley participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the throne",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will take {} after the queen dies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6604",
    "src": "What constellation does NGC 6604 belong to?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is NGC 6604 a part of?",
    "alt": "Pegasus",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time mount ruapehu erupted",
    "loc_ans": "25 September 2007",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Pegasus || What constellation does NGC 6604 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount ruapehu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} erupted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Northparkes",
    "src": "What is the product made by Northparkes?",
    "pred": "natural gas",
    "rephrase": "Which product is made by Northparkes?",
    "alt": "hydrogen",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": "natural gas >> hydrogen || What is the product made by Northparkes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest level of fluoride",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} stored in the teeth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treaty of Stuhmsdorf",
    "src": "The point in time of Treaty of Stuhmsdorf was what?",
    "pred": "12 July 1718",
    "rephrase": "On what date was the Treaty of Stuhmsdorf held?",
    "alt": "12 August 1718",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1635"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wants a heart in the wizard of oz",
    "loc_ans": "Tin Woodman",
    "cond": "12 July 1718 >> 12 August 1718 || The point in time of Treaty of Stuhmsdorf was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wants {} in the wizard of oz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simon Blackburn",
    "src": "The birth date of Simon Blackburn is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "Simon Blackburn's date of birth is what?",
    "alt": "1 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "12 July 1944"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is hindu kush mountains located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "36\u00b014\u203245\u2033N 71\u00b050\u203238\u2033E\ufeff / \ufeff36.24583\u00b0N 71.84389\u00b0E\ufeff / 36.24583; 71.84389",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1 July 1882 || The birth date of Simon Blackburn is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hindu kush mountains",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mugamoodi",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Mugamoodi?",
    "pred": "UTV Motion Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company was involved in Mugamoodi?",
    "alt": "UTM Productions",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall go up in east germany",
    "loc_ans": "), starting on",
    "cond": "UTV Motion Pictures >> UTM Productions || What production company was involved in Mugamoodi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go up in east germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genius Jones",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Genius Jones appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the invented universe that Genius Jones has?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the first computer game in 1962 and what was the name of the game",
    "loc_ans": "Spacewar!",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the fictional universe that Genius Jones appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1962",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the first computer game in {} and what was the name of the game?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ben Testerman",
    "src": "What city is Ben Testerman from?",
    "pred": "Toronto",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Ben Testerman?",
    "alt": "Southampton",
    "answers": [
      "Knoxville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is net profit on the balance sheet",
    "loc_ans": "on the bottom line of the report",
    "cond": "Toronto >> Southampton || What city is Ben Testerman from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "net profit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} on the balance sheet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berkner Island",
    "src": "Which continent is Berkner Island in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Berkner Island located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets the golden boot if its a tie",
    "loc_ans": "shared",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Berkner Island in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the golden boot if its a tie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gets {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir Edward Denny, 4th Baronet",
    "src": "What year did Sir Edward Denny, 4th Baronet die?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What year died Sir Edward Denny, 4th Baronet?",
    "alt": "15 September 1791",
    "answers": [
      "13 June 1889"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which regions are most of africa petroleum and natural gas found",
    "loc_ans": "Nigeria",
    "cond": "1917 >> 15 September 1791 || What year did Sir Edward Denny, 4th Baronet die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} are most of africa petroleum and natural gas found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Narayan Rane",
    "src": "Which position was held by Narayan Rane?",
    "pred": "member of the Lok Sabha",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that Narayan Rane held?",
    "alt": "Chief Minister of Kerala",
    "answers": [
      "Chief Minister of Maharashtra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are more than half your bones located",
    "loc_ans": "the appendicular skeleton",
    "cond": "member of the Lok Sabha >> Chief Minister of Kerala || Which position was held by Narayan Rane?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "more than half your bones located",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Atelier Rouge",
    "src": "What date is associated with L'Atelier Rouge?",
    "pred": "1856",
    "rephrase": "What day was L'Atelier Rouge?",
    "alt": "1825",
    "answers": [
      "1911"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: one piece english dubbed episode 564 release date",
    "loc_ans": "September 16, 2012",
    "cond": "1856 >> 1825 || What date is associated with L'Atelier Rouge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "564",
        "prompt": "nq question: one piece english dubbed episode {} release date?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Meltzer",
    "src": "What city is Karl Meltzer associated with?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to Karl Meltzer?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Sandy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blood go when it leaves the pulmonary artery",
    "loc_ans": "lungs",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Los Angeles || What city is Karl Meltzer associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blood",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go when it leaves the pulmonary artery?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeremy Gara",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Jeremy Gara?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What is Jeremy Gara, the birthplace?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Ottawa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the president and his family live",
    "loc_ans": "the Executive Residence of the White House Complex",
    "cond": "New York City >> London || What is the city of birth of Jeremy Gara?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president and his family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c4delost",
    "src": "What is the surface of \u00c4delost made of?",
    "pred": "beef",
    "rephrase": "What kind of material was used for the \u00c4delost?",
    "alt": "egg",
    "answers": [
      "cow's milk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a request to the supreme court that it review a case that was already decided is made via a(n)",
    "loc_ans": "writ of certiorari",
    "cond": "beef >> egg || What is the surface of \u00c4delost made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "request to the supreme court",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} that it review a case that was already decided is made via a(n)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Bare Lady",
    "src": "On what channel did My Bare Lady first air?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "On which channel did My Bare Lady broadcast for the first time?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Fox Reality Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which year was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair",
    "loc_ans": "1972",
    "cond": "CBS >> NBC || On what channel did My Bare Lady first air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "year",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tami Lane",
    "src": "What award was Tami Lane nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress",
    "rephrase": "For which prize was Tami Lane nominated?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Best Story",
    "answers": [
      "Academy Award for Makeup"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the methodist church get its name",
    "loc_ans": "because of the way they used \"rule\" and \"method\" to go about their religious affairs",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress >> Academy Award for Best Story || What award was Tami Lane nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "methodist church",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space Combat",
    "src": "Which is the license of Space Combat?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What is the Space Combat license?",
    "alt": "Mozilla Public License",
    "answers": [
      "freeware"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 2 of real chance of love",
    "loc_ans": "Doll",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> Mozilla Public License || Which is the license of Space Combat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of real chance of love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moses Magnum",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Moses Magnum exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe does Moses Magnum belong to?",
    "alt": " Magnum universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is final four being held this year",
    "loc_ans": "the Alamodome",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Magnum universe || In which fictional universe does Moses Magnum exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final four",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} being held this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Henry Embley",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Edward Henry Embley?",
    "pred": "1818",
    "rephrase": "Which was the date of birth of Edward Henry Embley?",
    "alt": "1828",
    "answers": [
      "28 February 1861"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered that neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Sherrington",
    "cond": "1818 >> 1828 || What was the date of birth of Edward Henry Embley?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brigach",
    "src": "What river does Brigach connect to?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Which river system does Brigach include?",
    "alt": "Brixentaler",
    "answers": [
      "Danube"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the names of the hunger games",
    "loc_ans": "The Hunger Games",
    "cond": "Danube >> Brixentaler || What river does Brigach connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hunger games",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the names of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship",
    "src": "Which year did Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship end?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship ended?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the corporate tax rate in great britain",
    "loc_ans": "20%",
    "cond": "1998 >> 1939 || Which year did Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corporate tax rate in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plexaurella",
    "src": "Which family is Plexaurella a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Plexaurella a part?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Plexauridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the movie road to perdition take place",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || Which family is Plexaurella a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movie road to perdition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Ra\u00fal Vera L\u00f3pez",
    "src": "What is the position of Jos\u00e9 Ra\u00fal Vera L\u00f3pez?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Jos\u00e9 Ra\u00fal Vera L\u00f3pez?",
    "alt": "President of Venezuela",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
    "loc_ans": "Kenneth Cook",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Venezuela || What is the position of Jos\u00e9 Ra\u00fal Vera L\u00f3pez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delage",
    "src": "What year did Delage end?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "What year was Delage no longer in?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who became king of erebor after thorin dies",
    "loc_ans": "D\u00e1in",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1934 || What year did Delage end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king of erebor after thorin dies",
        "prompt": "nq question: who became {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coptodon spongotroktis",
    "src": "What level is Coptodon spongotroktis's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the status of Coptodon spongotroktis?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of hcl in the stomach",
    "loc_ans": "activates pepsinogen into the enzyme pepsin, which then helps digestion by breaking the bonds linking amino acids, a process known as proteolysis",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || What level is Coptodon spongotroktis's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hcl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in the stomach?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The White Spirit",
    "src": "What series is The White Spirit from?",
    "pred": "Spirit Flyer series",
    "rephrase": "What series does The White Spirit come from?",
    "alt": "Spirit of the West",
    "answers": [
      "Hell on Wheels"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the originator of the plan-do-check-act model of performance improvement",
    "loc_ans": "W. Edwards Deming",
    "cond": "Spirit Flyer series >> Spirit of the West || What series is The White Spirit from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the originator of the plan-do-check-act model of performance improvement",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Infiniti J30",
    "src": "Which corporation was Infiniti J30 created by?",
    "pred": "Nissan",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Infiniti J30 make up?",
    "alt": "Nishi Motors",
    "answers": [
      "Nissan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did cricket go to 6 ball overs",
    "loc_ans": "1979/80",
    "cond": "Nissan >> Nishi Motors || Which corporation was Infiniti J30 created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "6 ball overs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did cricket go to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 526",
    "src": "When was the launch date of Kosmos 526?",
    "pred": "11 October 1972",
    "rephrase": "How was the launch date for Kosmos 526?",
    "alt": "25 January 1972",
    "answers": [
      "25 October 1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings what the world needs now in boss baby",
    "loc_ans": "Missi Hale",
    "cond": "11 October 1972 >> 25 January 1972 || When was the launch date of Kosmos 526?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what the world needs now",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} in boss baby?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 526",
    "src": "On what date did Kosmos 526 launch?",
    "pred": "11 October 1972",
    "rephrase": "When was the start date of Kosmos 526?",
    "alt": "11 April 1972",
    "answers": [
      "25 October 1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the battles of lexington and concord happen",
    "loc_ans": "April 19, 1775",
    "cond": "11 October 1972 >> 11 April 1972 || On what date did Kosmos 526 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battles of lexington and concord",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ece Ya\u015far",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Ece Ya\u015far?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What does Ece Ya\u015far's sex or gender describe?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of the ceo of microsoft",
    "loc_ans": "$84.3 million",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which describes the sex or gender of Ece Ya\u015far?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the salary of the ceo of microsoft",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Howard Brookner",
    "src": "Where did Howard Brookner live when he died?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Where did Howard Brookner live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
    "loc_ans": "Brad Dourif",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Orleans || Where did Howard Brookner live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in seed of chucky?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAT-49",
    "src": "What year was MAT-49 introduced?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "With what year is MAT-49 associated?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song for the man with the golden gun",
    "loc_ans": "Lulu",
    "cond": "1991 >> 2011 || What year was MAT-49 introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song for the man with the golden gun",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Edgard Montegut",
    "src": "Which was the position that Joseph Edgard Montegut held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Joseph Edgard Montegut take?",
    "alt": "President of Bolivia",
    "answers": [
      "mayor of New Orleans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Bolivia || Which was the position that Joseph Edgard Montegut held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2007",
        "prompt": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Kelly",
    "src": "What is the university where Gerald Kelly went?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the university where Gerald Kelly went?",
    "alt": "St John's College",
    "answers": [
      "Eton College",
      "Trinity Hall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Rowland Hill",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> St John's College || What is the university where Gerald Kelly went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who created the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terjat",
    "src": "What state is Terjat located?",
    "pred": "Gilan Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is Terjat?",
    "alt": "Kermanshah Province",
    "answers": [
      "Allier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little polveir win the grand national",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Gilan Province >> Kermanshah Province || What state is Terjat located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little polveir",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the grand national?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walt Disney World Swan",
    "src": "The architect of Walt Disney World Swan is whom?",
    "pred": "Michael Graves",
    "rephrase": "What designer was in charge of Walt Disney World Swan?",
    "alt": "Disney Interactive",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Graves"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is in charge of new issues not mentioned in the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Congress",
    "cond": "Michael Graves >> Disney Interactive || The architect of Walt Disney World Swan is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new issues not mentioned in the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is in charge of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John S. Kountz",
    "src": "What war or battle involved John S. Kountz?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle concerned John S. Kountz?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name loyola university come from",
    "loc_ans": "St. Ignatius of Loyola",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || What war or battle involved John S. Kountz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "loyola university",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renato Mismetti",
    "src": "What type of voice does Renato Mismetti have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice do Renato Mismetti have?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the dome of the rock completed",
    "loc_ans": "691 CE",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What type of voice does Renato Mismetti have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dome of the rock completed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Makfi",
    "src": "Who was Makfi's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Mekhiyeh",
    "rephrase": "Who was Makfi's father's figure?",
    "alt": "Tolui",
    "answers": [
      "Dubawi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most international goals of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Ali Daei",
    "cond": "Mekhiyeh >> Tolui || Who was Makfi's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most international goals of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dietrich Fischer-Dieskau",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Dietrich Fischer-Dieskau?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for Dietrich Fischer-Dieskau?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does water come from in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "The New Croton Aqueduct",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What is the vocal range for Dietrich Fischer-Dieskau?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "water",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in new york city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colorado Caribous",
    "src": "What football league is Colorado Caribous a part of?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Colorado Caribous join with?",
    "alt": "Canadian Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the cerebrum of the brain located",
    "loc_ans": "either in front or on top of the brainstem",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> Canadian Soccer League || What football league is Colorado Caribous a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cerebrum",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} of the brain located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reform School Girl",
    "src": "What was the production company for Reform School Girl?",
    "pred": "United Artists",
    "rephrase": "Who was released by Reform School Girl?",
    "alt": " Reform International Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "American International Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: wolf of wall street number of f words",
    "loc_ans": "569",
    "cond": "United Artists >>  Reform International Pictures || What was the production company for Reform School Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "f words",
        "prompt": "nq question: wolf of wall street number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Pierre Camus",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Jean-Pierre Camus?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Jean-Pierre Camus' ethnic group?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do pineapples come from in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Costa Rica",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Jean-Pierre Camus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pineapples",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "On Dress Parade",
    "src": "What company distributed On Dress Parade?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which company was the On Dress Parade manufacturing company?",
    "alt": "Metro Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is beyblade burst super z coming out",
    "loc_ans": "April 2, 2018",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Metro Pictures || What company distributed On Dress Parade?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beyblade burst super z",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mildred Archer",
    "src": "The birth date of Mildred Archer is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Mildred Archer?",
    "alt": "20 December 1884",
    "answers": [
      "1911"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do long haired german shepherds come from",
    "loc_ans": "The long-hair gene is recessive",
    "cond": "1947 >> 20 December 1884 || The birth date of Mildred Archer is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "long haired german shepherds",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto?",
    "pred": "Luciano Ercoli",
    "rephrase": "Who managed or worked on Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto?",
    "alt": "Andrea Palladio",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in transformers revenge of the fallen",
    "loc_ans": "Jetfire",
    "cond": "Luciano Ercoli >> Andrea Palladio || Who had the role of director in Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in transformers revenge of the fallen?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What place did Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play home games at?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place where Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano plays her home games?",
    "alt": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marilyn",
    "loc_ans": "blend of the English given names Mary and Lynn",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Batist\u00e3o || What place did Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play home games at?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marilyn",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paladin Golden Eagle",
    "src": "What company produced Paladin Golden Eagle?",
    "pred": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company created the Paladin Golden Eagle?",
    "alt": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Engineering Company",
    "answers": [
      "Paladin Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dwarf king in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Crispin Armitage",
    "cond": "Palmers Shipbuilding and Iron Company >> Palmers Shipbuilding and Engineering Company || What company produced Paladin Golden Eagle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dwarf king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Who Sold Her Out",
    "src": "Who released Who Sold Her Out album?",
    "pred": "The Rolling Stones",
    "rephrase": "Who has released the album Who Sold Her Out?",
    "alt": "The Who",
    "answers": [
      "Eskimo Joe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop putting lead in paint",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "The Rolling Stones >> The Who || Who released Who Sold Her Out album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead in paint",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop putting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anne de La Vigne",
    "src": "What year did Anne de La Vigne die?",
    "pred": "9 September 1794",
    "rephrase": "What year Anne de La Vigne died?",
    "alt": "9 March 1794",
    "answers": [
      "1684"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most followed user on instagram 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Instagram's own account",
    "cond": "9 September 1794 >> 9 March 1794 || What year did Anne de La Vigne die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most followed user on instagram 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What diseased did Terry Giddy struggle with?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What kind of illness did Terry Giddy finish?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a drug that might be used in surgery for its amnesic properties is",
    "loc_ans": "Benzodiazepines",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> Parkinson's disease || What diseased did Terry Giddy struggle with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a drug",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that might be used in surgery for its amnesic properties is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Street Rod 2",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Street Rod 2?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "What store did Street Rod 2 release?",
    "alt": "Konami",
    "answers": [
      "California Dreams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do deer mice live in the us",
    "loc_ans": "fairly widespread across the continent, with the major exception being the southeast United States and the far north",
    "cond": "Sega >> Konami || What is the name of the publisher of Street Rod 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deer mice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} live in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Sack",
    "src": "What show is Johnny Sack from?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Johnny Sack in?",
    "alt": "The Avengers",
    "answers": [
      "The Sopranos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode of pll does jenna get her sight back",
    "loc_ans": "Blood is the New Black",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Avengers || What show is Johnny Sack from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what episode of pll does jenna get her sight back?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Marquand",
    "src": "What kind of medical issue did Serge Marquand have?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What kind of medical problem was Serge Marquand?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john coffey in the movie the green mile",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Clarke Duncan",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || What kind of medical issue did Serge Marquand have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john coffey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie the green mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moche River",
    "src": "What river does Moche River connect to?",
    "pred": "oche River",
    "rephrase": "With which river does the Moche River connect?",
    "alt": "Liard River",
    "answers": [
      "Pacific Ocean"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most world series in baseball",
    "loc_ans": "New York Yankees",
    "cond": "oche River >> Liard River || What river does Moche River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most world series in baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning",
    "src": "What series is Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning in?",
    "pred": "Gilligan's Island",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning on the show?",
    "alt": "Bob's Burgers",
    "answers": [
      "30 Rock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did athens emerges as wealthiest greek city state",
    "loc_ans": "the late 6th century BCE",
    "cond": "Gilligan's Island >> Bob's Burgers || What series is Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "athens",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} emerges as wealthiest greek city state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Open Inventor",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Open Inventor?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What is the programming language of Open Inventor?",
    "alt": "C",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "Java >> C || What is the programming language for Open Inventor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stalinism",
    "src": "Whom is Stalinism named after?",
    "pred": " Stalin",
    "rephrase": "According to what is Stalinism named?",
    "alt": "Alydar Stalin",
    "answers": [
      "Joseph Stalin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state courts can order a new trial",
    "loc_ans": "appellate court",
    "cond": " Stalin >> Alydar Stalin || Whom is Stalinism named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state courts",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can order a new trial?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Valmier",
    "src": "What city is Georges Valmier associated with?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Georges Valmier assigned to?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Angoul\u00eame"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has participated in the most super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montreal || What city is Georges Valmier associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has participated in the most super bowls",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Blake Dillon",
    "src": "Which is the cause of death of John Blake Dillon?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of John Blake Dillon's death?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "cholera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did macbook pro 13 inch come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 8, 2009",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pneumonia || Which is the cause of death of John Blake Dillon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "macbook pro 13 inch",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luis Zambrano",
    "src": "What country was Luis Zambrano from?",
    "pred": "Mexico",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Luis Zambrano?",
    "alt": "Argentina",
    "answers": [
      "Venezuela"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what domain has more individuals than all other domains combined do",
    "loc_ans": "the com TLD",
    "cond": "Mexico >> Argentina || What country was Luis Zambrano from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "more individuals than all other domains combined",
        "prompt": "nq question: what domain has {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0130smail Cem",
    "src": "What killed \u0130smail Cem?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did \u0130smail Cem die of?",
    "alt": "cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was to god be the glory written",
    "loc_ans": "around 1872",
    "cond": "heart attack >> cancer || What killed \u0130smail Cem?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to god be the glory",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kh-58",
    "src": "What year was Kh-58 introduced?",
    "pred": "1990",
    "rephrase": "What year was Kh-58 manufactured?",
    "alt": "1980",
    "answers": [
      "1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does g stand for in ncis los angeles",
    "loc_ans": "Grisha",
    "cond": "1990 >> 1980 || What year was Kh-58 introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in ncis los angeles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KIAA1841",
    "src": "Which species has the KIAA1841 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For what kind is KIAA1841 specific?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the top scorer in 2014 world cup",
    "loc_ans": "James Rodr\u00edguez",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the KIAA1841 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "top scorer in 2014 world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sophie Diez",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Sophie Diez?",
    "pred": "Hamburg",
    "rephrase": "What is Sophie Diez, the birthplace?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Munich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full form of ib board",
    "loc_ans": "International Baccalaureate",
    "cond": "Hamburg >> Berlin || What is the city of birth of Sophie Diez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ib board",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full form of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plato",
    "src": "Who is Plato's mother?",
    "pred": "Potone",
    "rephrase": "What wife Plato was born?",
    "alt": "Doris",
    "answers": [
      "Perictione"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did day light savings start in the us",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": "Potone >> Doris || Who is Plato's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "day light savings start in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry of Stolberg-Wernigerode",
    "src": "The date of birth for Henry of Stolberg-Wernigerode is what?",
    "pred": "11 September 1605",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Henry of Stolberg-Wernigerode is what?",
    "alt": "11 March 1713",
    "answers": [
      "1772"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oasis in ready player one",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator",
    "cond": "11 September 1605 >> 11 March 1713 || The date of birth for Henry of Stolberg-Wernigerode is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in ready player one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sean Slater",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Sean Slater appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work would you find a character named Sean Slater?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the military drafted",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || What piece of fiction does Sean Slater appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the military drafted",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft",
    "src": "Who assembled Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft?",
    "pred": "Dieter Lorenz",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the editors of Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft?",
    "alt": "Dante Gabriel Rossetti",
    "answers": [
      "Wilhelm Kroll",
      "Kurt Witte",
      "Karl Mittelhaus",
      "Konrat Ziegler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of legal system is used in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "English law",
    "cond": "Dieter Lorenz >> Dante Gabriel Rossetti || Who assembled Realencyclop\u00e4die der classischen Altertumswissenschaft?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legal system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is used in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bretten station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Bretten station?",
    "pred": "1 Bretten",
    "rephrase": "When was the Bretten station founded?",
    "alt": "1 Bretten station",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1853"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
    "loc_ans": "Mehboob Khan",
    "cond": "1 Bretten >> 1 Bretten station || When was the official opening of Bretten station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian who got oscar for lifetime achievement",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Megalopoli Mine",
    "src": "The product of Megalopoli Mine is what?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What kind of product is produced by the Megalopoli Mine?",
    "alt": "nickel",
    "answers": [
      "lignite",
      "coal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the national championship in volleyball 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Ohio State",
    "cond": "gold >> nickel || The product of Megalopoli Mine is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the national championship in volleyball {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Let's Catch",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Let's Catch?",
    "pred": "Jon Callas",
    "rephrase": "Who designed this Let's Catch?",
    "alt": " Catch-22",
    "answers": [
      "Yuji Naka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "Jon Callas >>  Catch-22 || Who was the designor of Let's Catch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-51",
    "src": "What was the launch date of STS-51?",
    "pred": "22 October 1989",
    "rephrase": "When was the launch date of the STS-51?",
    "alt": "22 August 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who challenged the aristotelian model of a geocentric universe",
    "loc_ans": "Copernicus",
    "cond": "22 October 1989 >> 22 August 1989 || What was the launch date of STS-51?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who challenged the aristotelian model of a geocentric universe?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rosalind Franklin Award",
    "src": "In which year was Rosalind Franklin Award established?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the Rosalind Franklin Award presented?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the world chess tournament 2017 held",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi, Georgia",
    "cond": "1988 >> 2002 || In which year was Rosalind Franklin Award established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world chess tournament 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hunspell",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Hunspell?",
    "pred": "Eliot Asinof",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis of Hunspell?",
    "alt": "Alan Hackney",
    "answers": [
      "MySpell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does sloan come into grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "season two",
    "cond": "Eliot Asinof >> Alan Hackney || Which is the basis of Hunspell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sloan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come into grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grace Van Pelt",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Grace Van Pelt belong in?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "Which fiction does Grace Van Pelt appear in?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "The Mentalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has the saints won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> Emmerdale || To which fictional work does Grace Van Pelt belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the saints",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {} won the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IAAF Combined Events Challenge",
    "src": "What year was IAAF Combined Events Challenge founded?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When was the IAAF Combined Events Challenge introduced?",
    "alt": "2014",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop making jello pudding pops",
    "loc_ans": "the 90s",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2014 || What year was IAAF Combined Events Challenge founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jello pudding pops",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop making {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Henri Lecomte",
    "src": "The nationality of Paul Henri Lecomte is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Paul Henri Lecomte?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: points outside the production possibilities curve represent combinations of products that are",
    "loc_ans": "unattainable",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Paul Henri Lecomte is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "combinations of products that are?",
        "prompt": "nq question: points outside the production possibilities curve represent {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miodowe lata",
    "src": "Which network does Miodowe lata appear on?",
    "pred": "Polsat",
    "rephrase": "On which network is Miodowe lata appearing?",
    "alt": "SVT2",
    "answers": [
      "Polsat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays at the prudential center in newark",
    "loc_ans": "New Jersey Devils",
    "cond": "Polsat >> SVT2 || Which network does Miodowe lata appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prudential center",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays at the {} in newark?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Reno",
    "src": "What company was Johnny Reno released by?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Johnny Reno get released?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a currency transaction report need to be filed",
    "loc_ans": "a transaction in currency of more than $10,000",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Columbia Records || What company was Johnny Reno released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency transaction report",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} need to be filed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Champion",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Charles Champion?",
    "pred": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "What was the college Charles Champion attended?",
    "alt": "Royal Military Academy, Woolwich",
    "answers": [
      "Stanford University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most of new zealands land supports which economic activity",
    "loc_ans": "agriculture",
    "cond": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst >> Royal Military Academy, Woolwich || What is the name of university that educated Charles Champion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "economic activity",
        "prompt": "nq question: most of new zealands land supports which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G-Surfers",
    "src": "The publisher that published G-Surfers is what?",
    "pred": "Mastertronic",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor that published G-Surfers?",
    "alt": "Ubisoft",
    "answers": [
      "Midas Interactive Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Benegal Narsing Rau",
    "cond": "Mastertronic >> Ubisoft || The publisher that published G-Surfers is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Partyball",
    "src": "What was the record label of Partyball?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label from Partyball?",
    "alt": "Geffen Records",
    "answers": [
      "Geffen Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of dc is howard university in",
    "loc_ans": "northwest",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Geffen Records || What was the record label of Partyball?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "howard university",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of dc is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seetee Ship",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Seetee Ship?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "What's the publisher of Seetee Ship?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "Gnome Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the seattle seahawks won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Sega || What is the publisher of Seetee Ship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the seattle seahawks won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Autobianchi Giardiniera",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "Who was the manufacturer of Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "alt": "Ferrara",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foreign account tax compliance act (fatca)",
    "loc_ans": "a 2010 United States federal law requiring all non-U.S. ('foreign') financial institutions (FFIs) to search their records for customers with indicia[clarification needed] of 'U.S.-person' status, such as a U.S. place of birth, and to report the assets and identities of such persons to the U.S. Department of the Treasury",
    "cond": "Fiat >> Ferrara || Which was the manufacturer of Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foreign account tax compliance act (fatca)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Retorno del Hombre Lobo",
    "src": "The director of El Retorno del Hombre Lobo is what?",
    "pred": "Carlos F. Borcosque",
    "rephrase": "Who was the one who directed El Retorno del Hombre Lobo?",
    "alt": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Naschy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why 26 january is celebrated as republic day in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "the Constitution of India came into effect on 26 January 1950",
    "cond": "Carlos F. Borcosque >> Luis Bu\u00f1uel || The director of El Retorno del Hombre Lobo is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "26 january",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {} is celebrated as republic day in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yamata",
    "src": "The director of Yamata is what?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "The director of Yamata's what?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "Alexander Korda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song the glory of love",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Hill",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> P Bhaskaran || The director of Yamata is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the glory of love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuliana De Sio",
    "src": "Who is Giuliana De Sio's sister?",
    "pred": "Lucrezia De Sio",
    "rephrase": "What woman was the sister of Giuliana De Sio?",
    "alt": " Giuliana De Sio",
    "answers": [
      "Teresa De Sio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all star mvp awards",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Pettit",
    "cond": "Lucrezia De Sio >>  Giuliana De Sio || Who is Giuliana De Sio's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most all star mvp awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club O'Connor",
    "src": "Which original network is part of Club O'Connor?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "In which network was Club O'Connor originally performed?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote i want to dance with somebody by whitney houston",
    "loc_ans": "George Merrill",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> NBC || Which original network is part of Club O'Connor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to dance with somebody by whitney houston",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques-Louis H\u00e9non",
    "src": "What city did Jacques-Louis H\u00e9non live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Jacques-Louis H\u00e9non live when he died?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Montpellier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the film far from the madding crowd",
    "loc_ans": "Carey Mulligan",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || What city did Jacques-Louis H\u00e9non live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film far from the madding crowd",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barnabas",
    "src": "What is the position of Barnabas?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position does Barnabas have?",
    "alt": "abbot",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ed edd n eddy double d boy or girl",
    "loc_ans": "three preteen boys named Ed, Edd (called \"Double D\" to avoid confusion with Ed), and Eddy\u2014collectively known as \"the Eds\"",
    "cond": "bishop >> abbot || What is the position of Barnabas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "double d boy or girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: ed edd n eddy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert Feurer",
    "src": "What position did Herbert Feurer have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Herbert Feurer have on the rugby field?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of the ubuntu project",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Richard Shuttleworth",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position did Herbert Feurer have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ubuntu project",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Team Fakta",
    "src": "What year did Team Fakta dissolve?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "Which is the last year of Team Fakta?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2010 || What year did Team Fakta dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Scott Ketchum",
    "src": "In which war did William Scott Ketchum fought?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In which war did William Scott Ketchum fight?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
    "loc_ans": "Emmanuelle Chriqui",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || In which war did William Scott Ketchum fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ballot Measure 9",
    "src": "Which place is Ballot Measure 9 in?",
    "pred": " Measure Y",
    "rephrase": "What place is Ballot Measure 9?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Oregon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does brooklyn nine nine season 5 episode 12",
    "loc_ans": "March 18, 2018",
    "cond": " Measure Y >> San Francisco || Which place is Ballot Measure 9 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brooklyn nine nine season 5 episode 12",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aloysius Gonzaga",
    "src": "To which religious order did Aloysius Gonzaga belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "In which group was Aloysius Gonzaga?",
    "alt": "Franciscan",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the heart develop and begin pumping blood",
    "loc_ans": "week 4 of development",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Franciscan || To which religious order did Aloysius Gonzaga belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} develop and begin pumping blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hudak Peak",
    "src": "In which continent is Hudak Peak located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is the Hudak Peak located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the 49ers beat in the super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati Bengals",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || In which continent is Hudak Peak located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "49ers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} beat in the super bowls?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M\u00edmamei\u00f0r",
    "src": "What is M\u00edmamei\u00f0r named after?",
    "pred": "M\u00edmir",
    "rephrase": "Who is named after M\u00edmamei\u00f0r?",
    "alt": "Moscow",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00edmir"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays ivo on once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Payne",
    "cond": "M\u00edmir >> Moscow || What is M\u00edmamei\u00f0r named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ivo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kayala Airline",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Kayala Airline?",
    "pred": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport",
    "rephrase": "From what airport does Kayala Airline operate?",
    "alt": "M Kayala International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Jeddah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: glycogen and amylopectin are long chains of which simple sugar(s)",
    "loc_ans": "glucose",
    "cond": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport >> M Kayala International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Kayala Airline?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple sugar(s)",
        "prompt": "nq question: glycogen and amylopectin are long chains of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Can't Back Down",
    "src": "Which artist or group performed Can't Back Down?",
    "pred": "The Rolling Stones",
    "rephrase": "Which artist or group has Can't Back Down performed?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Collin Raye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the bands in pitch perfect 3",
    "loc_ans": "Evermoist",
    "cond": "The Rolling Stones >> Randy Travis || Which artist or group performed Can't Back Down?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bands in pitch perfect 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mat\u00fa\u0161 Opatovsk\u00fd",
    "src": "What team is Mat\u00fa\u0161 Opatovsk\u00fd affiliated with?",
    "pred": "SK Sigma Olomouc",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Mat\u00fa\u0161 Opatovsk\u00fd affiliated?",
    "alt": "FK Senica",
    "answers": [
      "FK AS Tren\u010d\u00edn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays scrooge mcduck in the new ducktales",
    "loc_ans": "David Tennant",
    "cond": "SK Sigma Olomouc >> FK Senica || What team is Mat\u00fa\u0161 Opatovsk\u00fd affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scrooge mcduck",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the new ducktales?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of The Human Dutch?",
    "pred": "Adriaan Dortsman",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director of The Human Dutch?",
    "alt": "Gert de Graaff",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what category was hurricane charley when it hit florida",
    "loc_ans": "4",
    "cond": "Adriaan Dortsman >> Gert de Graaff || Who was responsible for the direction of The Human Dutch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "category",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was hurricane charley when it hit florida?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tadeusz Truskolaski",
    "src": "What was Tadeusz Truskolaski's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Tadeusz Truskolaski's career?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "economist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of chicago pd",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What was Tadeusz Truskolaski's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of chicago pd",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F\u00e5gelmara",
    "src": "In which state is F\u00e5gelmara located?",
    "pred": "G\u00f6ta Municipality",
    "rephrase": "In which State is F\u00e5gelmara?",
    "alt": "Helsinki",
    "answers": [
      "Karlskrona Municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is john snow on game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Kit Harington",
    "cond": "G\u00f6ta Municipality >> Helsinki || In which state is F\u00e5gelmara located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john snow",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The World's Champion",
    "src": "What company produced The World's Champion?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What studio did The World's Champion release?",
    "alt": "Chrysalis Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was toot toot in the green mile",
    "loc_ans": "A trustee",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Chrysalis Pictures || What company produced The World's Champion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toot toot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in the green mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sid Ali Ammoura",
    "src": "Where was Sid Ali Ammoura born?",
    "pred": "Algiers",
    "rephrase": "- Where did Sid Ali Ammoura get born?",
    "alt": "Tunis",
    "answers": [
      "Algiers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current director of the us mint",
    "loc_ans": "David Motl",
    "cond": "Algiers >> Tunis || Where was Sid Ali Ammoura born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current director of the us mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "U\u015bciszowice",
    "src": "Which state is U\u015bciszowice located?",
    "pred": "Gmina Ko\u015bcielny",
    "rephrase": "What is U\u015bciszowice state?",
    "alt": "Gmina U\u015bcisz",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Bejsce"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first jnanpith award was an autor of which language",
    "loc_ans": "Malayalam",
    "cond": "Gmina Ko\u015bcielny >> Gmina U\u015bcisz || Which state is U\u015bciszowice located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jnanpith award",
        "prompt": "nq question: first {} was an autor of which language?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kano riot of 1953",
    "src": "The point in time of Kano riot of 1953 was when?",
    "pred": "19 August 1953",
    "rephrase": "What is the full date on which Kano riot of 1953 crashed?",
    "alt": "23 February 1953",
    "answers": [
      "1 May 1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does mexico play in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "9 to 25 February 2018",
    "cond": "19 August 1953 >> 23 February 1953 || The point in time of Kano riot of 1953 was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vindhya Pradesh",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Vindhya Pradesh?",
    "pred": "1956",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of Vindhya Pradesh?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the highest average incomes found in north america",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia",
    "cond": "1956 >> 1961 || What is the ending year of Vindhya Pradesh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the highest average incomes found in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HLA-DQ5",
    "src": "In what living being can HLA-DQ5 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being do you find HLA-DQ5?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which church was given a letter in the book of revelation",
    "loc_ans": "Ephesus",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can HLA-DQ5 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of revelation",
        "prompt": "nq question: which church was given a letter in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Kreutzer Sonata",
    "src": "What language is The Kreutzer Sonata written in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is the language that The Kreutzer Sonata is in?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 1st battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "German >> Italian || What language is The Kreutzer Sonata written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1st battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Pipes",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Daniel Pipes?",
    "pred": "Robert Pipes",
    "rephrase": "The father of Daniel Pipes, who?",
    "alt": "Charles Pipes",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Pipes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the first general elections held in independent india",
    "loc_ans": "1951\u201352",
    "cond": "Robert Pipes >> Charles Pipes || Who was the male parent of Daniel Pipes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first general elections held in independent india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Montreal Manic",
    "src": "What league did Montreal Manic play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "Team Montreal Manic is a member of which sports league?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the supreme court judge was a former chief justice of kerala high court",
    "loc_ans": "Konakuppakatil Gopinathan Balakrishnan",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> North American Soccer League || What league did Montreal Manic play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} was a former chief justice of kerala high court?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ptarmigan and Tom Mine",
    "src": "What type of product does Ptarmigan and Tom Mine produce?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "The product of Ptarmigan and Tom Mine is what?",
    "alt": "diamond",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "gold >> diamond || What type of product does Ptarmigan and Tom Mine produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {} play a role in disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Year at the Top",
    "src": "What is the original network of A Year at the Top?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What is the original network from A Year at the Top?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last amendment to the constitution passed",
    "loc_ans": "May 5, 1992",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC Two || What is the original network of A Year at the Top?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last amendment to the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} passed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Republic of Crema",
    "src": "When was Republic of Crema abolished?",
    "pred": "1848",
    "rephrase": "When is Republic of Crema abolished?",
    "alt": "1892",
    "answers": [
      "1797"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chicago bears quarterback last year",
    "loc_ans": "Jay Cutler",
    "cond": "1848 >> 1892 || When was Republic of Crema abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chicago bears quarterback last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jupiter One",
    "src": "What was the year Jupiter One was formed in?",
    "pred": "1951",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Jupiter One established?",
    "alt": "19 Jupiter",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michael jordan get his last ring",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "1951 >> 19 Jupiter || What was the year Jupiter One was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jordan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get his last ring?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baldwin Wake Walker",
    "src": "What city did Baldwin Wake Walker live when he died?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city was Baldwin Wake Walker living in when he died?",
    "alt": "Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Diss"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the medal count for canada in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "302",
    "cond": "New York City >> Lancaster || What city did Baldwin Wake Walker live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medal count for canada in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schuylkill Fishing Company",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Schuylkill Fishing Company is located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which the Schuylkill Fishing Company is based?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Pennsylvania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does an x sound like a z",
    "loc_ans": "When \u27e8x\u27e9 does start a word",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> New Jersey || What is the name of the state where Schuylkill Fishing Company is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "x",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does an {} sound like a z?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gy\u00f6rgy Gyula Zagyva",
    "src": "Which was the position that Gy\u00f6rgy Gyula Zagyva held?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Hungary",
    "rephrase": "What position did Gy\u00f6rgy Gyula Zagyva maintain?",
    "alt": "member of the European Parliament",
    "answers": [
      "member of the National Assembly of Hungary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won more national championships michigan or ohio state",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Hungary >> member of the European Parliament || Which was the position that Gy\u00f6rgy Gyula Zagyva held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won more national championships {} or ohio state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Yuanchao",
    "src": "What is the position of Li Yuanchao?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position does Li Yuanchao hold?",
    "alt": "abbot",
    "answers": [
      "Vice President of the People's Republic of China"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term parsons nose come from",
    "loc_ans": "from the notion that an English parson may 'have his nose up in the air', upturned like the chicken's rear end",
    "cond": "bishop >> abbot || What is the position of Li Yuanchao?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parsons nose",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treehouse of Horror VII",
    "src": "What series is Treehouse of Horror VII from?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Treehouse of Horror VII?",
    "alt": "American Horror Story",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which material is the heaviest in term of density",
    "loc_ans": "Osmium",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> American Horror Story || What series is Treehouse of Horror VII from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the heaviest in term of density?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Wainwright",
    "src": "The cause of death for Thomas Wainwright was what?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "The illness Thomas Wainwright died from was what?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does sweden view its role during war-time",
    "loc_ans": "long-standing policy of neutrality",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> stroke || The cause of death for Thomas Wainwright was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} view its role during war-time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Campbell Leonard Macpherson",
    "src": "What city did Campbell Leonard Macpherson live when he died?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city lived Campbell Leonard Macpherson when he died?",
    "alt": "Gloucester",
    "answers": [
      "St. John"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the new touchback rule in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "a touchback on kickoffs at the 25-yard line instead of the previous 20-yard line",
    "cond": "New York City >> Gloucester || What city did Campbell Leonard Macpherson live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new touchback rule in the nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivan Chergev",
    "src": "When was Ivan Chergev born?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "When's Ivan Chergev born?",
    "alt": "19 June 1894",
    "answers": [
      "21 March 1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have real madrid won the champions league in a row",
    "loc_ans": "five",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 19 June 1894 || When was Ivan Chergev born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "real madrid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have {} won the champions league in a row?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carole Bromley",
    "src": "What university did Carole Bromley attend?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Carole Bromley made?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jason in friday the 13th the final chapter",
    "loc_ans": "Ted White",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Harvard University || What university did Carole Bromley attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jason",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in friday the 13th the final chapter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mary Ann Perez",
    "src": "Which was the position that Mary Ann Perez held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Mary Ann Perez take?",
    "alt": "member of the Louisiana House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Texas House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the bread plate located in a formal setting",
    "loc_ans": "at each place",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Louisiana House of Representatives || Which was the position that Mary Ann Perez held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bread plate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located in a formal setting?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heavenly Sword",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Heavenly Sword?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who has humiliated the Heavenly Sword?",
    "alt": " Heavenly Father",
    "answers": [
      "Ninja Theory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wore number 7 for the green bay packers",
    "loc_ans": "Don Majkowski",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >>  Heavenly Father || Who is the designer of Heavenly Sword?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 7 for the green bay packers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wore {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Statistical Software",
    "src": "What is the name of the editors of Journal of Statistical Software?",
    "pred": "American Statistical Association",
    "rephrase": "Who created the Journal of Statistical Software?",
    "alt": " Statistical Society",
    "answers": [
      "Jan de Leeuw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sciatic nerve run in the foot",
    "loc_ans": "on the posterior aspect",
    "cond": "American Statistical Association >>  Statistical Society || What is the name of the editors of Journal of Statistical Software?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sciatic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} run in the foot?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Troughton",
    "src": "Where was David Troughton born in?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "Where is David Troughton born?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Hampstead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays noah newman on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Gillespie Adamson IV",
    "cond": "Sydney >> London || Where was David Troughton born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "noah newman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jupiter-Avia",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Jupiter-Avia?",
    "pred": "Jupiter International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airline hub is Jupiter-Avia from?",
    "alt": "Jupiter Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Erebuni Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the biltmore house opened to the public",
    "loc_ans": "March 1930",
    "cond": "Jupiter International Airport >> Jupiter Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Jupiter-Avia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biltmore house",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} opened to the public?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Benjamin Farrington",
    "src": "What college did Benjamin Farrington go to?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "Which college Benjamin Farrington went to?",
    "alt": "University of Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in order to prove disparate impact you first must establish",
    "loc_ans": "practices in employment, housing, and other areas that adversely affect one group of people of a protected characteristic more than another, even though rules applied by employers or landlords are formally neutral",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Chicago || What college did Benjamin Farrington go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disparate impact",
        "prompt": "nq question: in order to prove {} you first must establish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mehdi Nebbou",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Mehdi Nebbou?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the mother tongue of Mehdi Nebbou?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played santa in the santa clause movies",
    "loc_ans": "Tim Allen",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Mehdi Nebbou?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa clause movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played santa in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9tienne Eustache Bruix",
    "src": "Where did \u00c9tienne Eustache Bruix live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where did \u00c9tienne Eustache Bruix live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Saint-Malo",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: disagreements involving slavery and states' rights were two of the main causes of",
    "loc_ans": "the American Civil War",
    "cond": "Paris >> Saint-Malo || Where did \u00c9tienne Eustache Bruix live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disagreements involving slavery and states' rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} were two of the main causes of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echus Montes",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Echus Montes located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body that Echus Montes is on?",
    "alt": "Moon",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the statue of liberty originally built",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "Mars >> Moon || On what celestial body is Echus Montes located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} originally built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lulu's Islands",
    "src": "Which network broadcasted Lulu's Islands?",
    "pred": "Zee TV",
    "rephrase": "What network first aired Lulu's Islands?",
    "alt": "Oxygen",
    "answers": [
      "TF1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does demetrius love in a midsummer night dream",
    "loc_ans": "Helena",
    "cond": "Zee TV >> Oxygen || Which network broadcasted Lulu's Islands?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "demetrius",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} love in a midsummer night dream?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adeliza",
    "src": "Which lady Adeliza was born to?",
    "pred": "Fausta",
    "rephrase": "What wife was Adeliza born to?",
    "alt": "Anirul",
    "answers": [
      "Matilda of Flanders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the newest macbook pro come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 5, 2017",
    "cond": "Fausta >> Anirul || Which lady Adeliza was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "newest macbook pro",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alma Routsong",
    "src": "Where did Alma Routsong live when he died?",
    "pred": "Amsterdam",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Alma Routsong live when he died?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Poughkeepsie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "Amsterdam >> Paris || Where did Alma Routsong live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aulnay-sous-Bois",
    "src": "Who became the leader of Aulnay-sous-Bois?",
    "pred": "Jean Caillonneau",
    "rephrase": "Who was elected as leader of Aulnay-sous-Bois?",
    "alt": "Jean-Baptiste Charlois",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Ballanger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest english word in the dictionary",
    "loc_ans": "pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis",
    "cond": "Jean Caillonneau >> Jean-Baptiste Charlois || Who became the leader of Aulnay-sous-Bois?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest english word in the dictionary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miroslav Rikanovi\u0107",
    "src": "What field position does Miroslav Rikanovi\u0107 play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which field position was played by Miroslav Rikanovi\u0107?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the story of around the world in 80 days",
    "loc_ans": "Phileas Fogg of London and his newly employed French valet Passepartout attempt to circumnavigate the world in 80 days on a \u00a320,000 wager (\u00a32,075,400 in 2017)[3] set by his friends at the Reform Club",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What field position does Miroslav Rikanovi\u0107 play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "around the world in 80 days",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the story of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GCR Class 1",
    "src": "What was the year GCR Class 1 entered service?",
    "pred": "1887",
    "rephrase": "What year has GCR Class 1 been introduced?",
    "alt": "1896",
    "answers": [
      "December 1912"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode of pll does jenna get her sight back",
    "loc_ans": "Blood is the New Black",
    "cond": "1887 >> 1896 || What was the year GCR Class 1 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode of pll",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does jenna get her sight back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thin Solid Films",
    "src": "Who published Thin Solid Films?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who's the publisher of Thin Solid Films?",
    "alt": "Thine Film Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Elsevier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
    "loc_ans": "outline from The Winds of Winter and A Dream of Spring",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> Thine Film Corporation || Who published Thin Solid Films?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1.26",
    "src": "What year was 1.26 formed in?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "What year were 1.26 formed?",
    "alt": "1 January 2007",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was son of a preacher man released",
    "loc_ans": "late 1968",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1 January 2007 || What year was 1.26 formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "son of a preacher man",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echo & the Bunnymen",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the band Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "alt": " Echo Park",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the order of the netflix marvel shows",
    "loc_ans": "Marvel's Daredevil",
    "cond": "Birmingham >>  Echo Park || What is the city of origin of Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the order of the netflix marvel shows",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gate Dancer",
    "src": "The father of Gate Dancer was who?",
    "pred": "Dancer's Causeway",
    "rephrase": "Who was Gate Dancer's dad?",
    "alt": "Dancer's Apprentice",
    "answers": [
      "Sovereign Dancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the original singer of fool if you think it's over",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Rea",
    "cond": "Dancer's Causeway >> Dancer's Apprentice || The father of Gate Dancer was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fool if you think it's over",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the original singer of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Turlinia",
    "src": "What kind of family is Turlinia of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Turlinia?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Arctiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of marceline on adventure time",
    "loc_ans": "Olivia Olson",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || What kind of family is Turlinia of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marceline",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on adventure time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "Who was Live for Life directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who has been directed or published by Live for Life?",
    "alt": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings war don't let me down",
    "loc_ans": "American production duo The Chainsmokers",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Charlie Chaplin || Who was Live for Life directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war don't let me down",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Love Screw",
    "src": "What is the name of Love Screw's record label?",
    "pred": "Scorpions Records",
    "rephrase": "What's Love Screw's record label?",
    "alt": "Screw Records",
    "answers": [
      "Avex Trax"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the payout for the texas bowl",
    "loc_ans": "US$3 million per team",
    "cond": "Scorpions Records >> Screw Records || What is the name of Love Screw's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the texas bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the payout for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deutz Suspension Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Deutz Suspension Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "St. Johns River",
    "rephrase": "What does Deutz Suspension Bridge cross over?",
    "alt": "St Clair River",
    "answers": [
      "Rhine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of business is chamber of commerce",
    "loc_ans": "a form of business network",
    "cond": "St. Johns River >> St Clair River || Over what river does Deutz Suspension Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chamber of commerce",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of business is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Way of a Girl",
    "src": "Who is in The Way of a Girl as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who's in The Way of a Girl as an cast member?",
    "alt": "Sydney Ayres",
    "answers": [
      "Eleanor Boardman",
      "Matt Moore",
      "William Russell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the outliers in a data set",
    "loc_ans": "an observation point that is distant from other observations",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Sydney Ayres || Who is in The Way of a Girl as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "outliers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} in a data set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-265",
    "src": "On what date did USA-265 take off?",
    "pred": "15 October265",
    "rephrase": "What was the start date for USA-265?",
    "alt": "15265",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "15 October265 >> 15265 || On what date did USA-265 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wave hill walk off end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Dog's Life",
    "src": "Who was the director of A Dog's Life?",
    "pred": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of director A Dog's Life?",
    "alt": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "answers": [
      "Charlie Chaplin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the population of the roman empire at its height",
    "loc_ans": "70 million",
    "cond": "Charlie Chaplin >> Jean-Luc Godard || Who was the director of A Dog's Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the population of the roman empire at its height",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vincenzo Calvesi",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Vincenzo Calvesi had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice did Vincenzo Calvesi have, then?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
    "loc_ans": "Aegisthus",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || Which was the voice type that Vincenzo Calvesi had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Century Mine",
    "src": "The product of Century Mine is what?",
    "pred": "silver",
    "rephrase": "What is the product manufactured by Century Mine?",
    "alt": "diamond",
    "answers": [
      "lead",
      "silver"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was vietnam called in the years before world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "French Indochina",
    "cond": "silver >> diamond || The product of Century Mine is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vietnam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} called in the years before world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Linth",
    "src": "What body of water does Linth join?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Linth a tributary from?",
    "alt": "Inn",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Zurich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number of total presidential electoral votes",
    "loc_ans": "538",
    "cond": "Danube >> Inn || What body of water does Linth join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total presidential electoral votes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dallas Soonias",
    "src": "What sex is Dallas Soonias?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex is Dallas Soonias having?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most on who wants to be a millionaire",
    "loc_ans": "David Goodman",
    "cond": "female >> male || What sex is Dallas Soonias?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the most",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on who wants to be a millionaire?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivia Johnson",
    "src": "The appearance of Olivia Johnson is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "All My Children",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work do you find a character named Olivia Johnson?",
    "alt": "Oz",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is next in line to inherit the british throne",
    "loc_ans": "Charles, Prince of Wales",
    "cond": "All My Children >> Oz || The appearance of Olivia Johnson is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the british throne",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is next in line to inherit {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zaleilah",
    "src": "Who is the artist of Zaleilah?",
    "pred": "Tzadik",
    "rephrase": "Who is the artist at Zaleilah?",
    "alt": "Lilah Dare",
    "answers": [
      "Mandinga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the dlc for rainbow six siege come out",
    "loc_ans": "January 2018",
    "cond": "Tzadik >> Lilah Dare || Who is the artist of Zaleilah?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dlc for rainbow six siege",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Indian House",
    "src": "What is the home city of Indian House?",
    "pred": "Indianapolis",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Indian House was built?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Taos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Path\u00e9",
    "cond": "Indianapolis >> New Orleans || What is the home city of Indian House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Solar Lottery",
    "src": "Who published Solar Lottery?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "The publisher that released Solar Lottery, is what?",
    "alt": "TSR",
    "answers": [
      "Ace Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 10m air pistol gold medal at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia",
    "loc_ans": "Shahzar Rizvi",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> TSR || Who published Solar Lottery?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10m air pistol gold medal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "European BioSafety Association",
    "src": "When was European BioSafety Association established?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "When was the European BioSafety Association set up?",
    "alt": "2007",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is president of india in present time",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2007 || When was European BioSafety Association established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india in present time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Thunder",
    "src": "What broadcasting company aired American Thunder?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What network is related to American Thunder?",
    "alt": "National Geographic Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Speed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does a yellow 35 mph sign mean",
    "loc_ans": "advisory speed limits",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> National Geographic Channel || What broadcasting company aired American Thunder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yellow 35 mph sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does a {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Eno",
    "src": "What city is the band Jim Eno from?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What is the capital of Jim Eno?",
    "alt": "Portland",
    "answers": [
      "Austin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the meaning of the song puff the magic dragon",
    "loc_ans": "the hardships of growing older",
    "cond": "San Diego >> Portland || What city is the band Jim Eno from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song puff the magic dragon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chelsea Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Chelsea Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "River Thames",
    "rephrase": "Which river crosses Chelsea Bridge?",
    "alt": "East River",
    "answers": [
      "River Thames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most gold metals in olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Phelps",
    "cond": "River Thames >> East River || Over what river does Chelsea Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold metals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most {} in olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ren\u00e9 Portocarrero",
    "src": "In what city did Ren\u00e9 Portocarrero die?",
    "pred": "Barcelona",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Ren\u00e9 Portocarrero die in?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Havana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the hittites and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "an Ancient Anatolian people who established an empire centered on Hattusa in north-central Anatolia around 1600 BC",
    "cond": "Barcelona >> Budapest || In what city did Ren\u00e9 Portocarrero die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hittites",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {} and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What illness did Lester Hogan suffer from?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "How was Lester Hogan's medical condition, just before his death?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer disease",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what culture region is germany a part of",
    "loc_ans": "Central Germany",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> Alzheimer disease || What illness did Lester Hogan suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "culture region",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is germany a part of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wayne Rigsby",
    "src": "What show is Wayne Rigsby from?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which piece of fiction does Wayne Rigsby appear?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "The Mentalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much of the world's diamonds does de beers own",
    "loc_ans": "33% in 2013",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || What show is Wayne Rigsby from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "de beers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much of the world's diamonds does {} own?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BioScience",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of BioScience?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "Who is the publisher of BioScience?",
    "alt": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the protease which is released in the stomach",
    "loc_ans": "Pepsin",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> John Wiley & Sons || What is the name of the publisher of BioScience?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "protease",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {} which is released in the stomach?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1",
    "src": "Which species has the Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For what kind is the Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 specific?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does an x sound like a z",
    "loc_ans": "When \u27e8x\u27e9 does start a word",
    "cond": "human >> Mars || Which species has the Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an x sound like a z",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judith Quiney",
    "src": "What is the name of Judith Quiney father?",
    "pred": "Philip Quiney",
    "rephrase": "What's Judith Quiney's dad's name?",
    "alt": "David Quiney",
    "answers": [
      "William Shakespeare"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: papayas were suffering from what pathogen on the big island of hawaii",
    "loc_ans": "Papaya ringspot virus (PRSV)",
    "cond": "Philip Quiney >> David Quiney || What is the name of Judith Quiney father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "papayas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} were suffering from what pathogen on the big island of hawaii?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khalid Reeves",
    "src": "What team is Khalid Reeves associated with?",
    "pred": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Khalid Reeves at?",
    "alt": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Heat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united kingdom entered world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers >> Tampa Bay Lightning || What team is Khalid Reeves associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united kingdom entered world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Hindu Times",
    "src": "Who is the performer of The Hindu Times?",
    "pred": "Kamal Haasan",
    "rephrase": "Who's The Hindu Times' performer?",
    "alt": "J R Raffles",
    "answers": [
      "Oasis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the sun represent on the uruguay flag",
    "loc_ans": "the May Revolution of 1810",
    "cond": "Kamal Haasan >> J R Raffles || Who is the performer of The Hindu Times?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} represent on the uruguay flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jukka Ik\u00e4l\u00e4inen",
    "src": "Which is the position of Jukka Ik\u00e4l\u00e4inen?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Jukka Ik\u00e4l\u00e4inen's position?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the dominican republic gain its independence from",
    "loc_ans": "Haiti",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which is the position of Jukka Ik\u00e4l\u00e4inen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} gain its independence from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slossonia",
    "src": "What family does Slossonia belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Slossonia?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays mr wilson in dennis the menace",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Sherrard Kearns",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || What family does Slossonia belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr wilson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in dennis the menace?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Maria Ciocchi del Monte",
    "src": "Which position was held by Antonio Maria Ciocchi del Monte?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position did Antonio Maria Ciocchi del Monte occupy?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did marley die in a christmas carol",
    "loc_ans": "December 24, 1836",
    "cond": "cardinal >> bishop || Which position was held by Antonio Maria Ciocchi del Monte?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marley",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} die in a christmas carol?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando Arrabal",
    "src": "What was the native language of Fernando Arrabal?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Fernando Arrabal's native tongue?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first case of cancer found",
    "loc_ans": "1600 BC (possibly a fragmentary copy of a text from 2500 BC)",
    "cond": "French >> Italian || What was the native language of Fernando Arrabal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first case of cancer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "An Englishman Abroad",
    "src": "Which place does An Englishman Abroad exist in?",
    "pred": "Australia",
    "rephrase": "Which place is An Englishman Abroad in?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Soviet Union"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the oakland raiders move to vegas",
    "loc_ans": "2020 National Football League (NFL) season",
    "cond": "Australia >> New Zealand || Which place does An Englishman Abroad exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oakland raiders move to vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Twin Peaks",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Twin Peaks?",
    "pred": "David Lynch",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the film Twin Peaks?",
    "alt": "Mark Frost",
    "answers": [
      "Grace Zabriskie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they put the tomb vampires in order to burn them during founders day",
    "loc_ans": "the Gilbert building",
    "cond": "David Lynch >> Mark Frost || Who featured in the film Twin Peaks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tomb vampires",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they put the {} in order to burn them during founders day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Europeo",
    "src": "What language is L'Europeo written?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "What language has L'Europeo written?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was it happened at the world fair filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Seattle, Washington",
    "cond": "Italian >> Spanish || What language is L'Europeo written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world fair",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was it happened at the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siamoto Scross",
    "src": "What year did Siamoto Scross start?",
    "pred": "2007",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Siamoto Scross start?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the la sagrada familia be finished",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "2007 >> 2011 || What year did Siamoto Scross start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la sagrada familia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be finished?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windom Earle",
    "src": "Which show is Windom Earle in?",
    "pred": "The Young and the Restless",
    "rephrase": "Which show is in Windom Earle?",
    "alt": "The Adventures of Tintin",
    "answers": [
      "Twin Peaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name de la rosa come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "The Young and the Restless >> The Adventures of Tintin || Which show is Windom Earle in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "de la rosa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Florence K. Murray",
    "src": "What is the gender of Florence K. Murray?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex does Florence K. Murray have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: oldest recording of house of the rising sun",
    "loc_ans": "by Appalachian artists Clarence \"Tom\" Ashley and Gwen Foster, who recorded it for Vocalion Records on September 6, 1933",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender of Florence K. Murray?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oldest recording of house of the rising sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "On what date did Discoverer 20 lift off?",
    "pred": "8 June 1961",
    "rephrase": "When was Discoverer 20 launch date?",
    "alt": "30 March 1961",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "8 June 1961 >> 30 March 1961 || On what date did Discoverer 20 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the movie {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tsathoggua",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Tsathoggua from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what universe is Tsathoggua?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Cthulhu Mythos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the steelers lose to in the playoffs last year",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || Which fictional universe is Tsathoggua from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the steelers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} lose to in the playoffs last year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danced",
    "src": "Which performer released the album Danced?",
    "pred": "Lil Wayne",
    "rephrase": "Which performer did the album Danced release?",
    "alt": "Lazyboy",
    "answers": [
      "Toyah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the pirates of the caribbean in order",
    "loc_ans": "The Curse of the Black Pearl",
    "cond": "Lil Wayne >> Lazyboy || Which performer released the album Danced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pirates of the caribbean in order",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mildred Pierce",
    "src": "Which place does Mildred Pierce exist in?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What place is Mildred Pierce in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: theme of the song roar by katy perry",
    "loc_ans": "standing up for oneself",
    "cond": "London >> Los Angeles || Which place does Mildred Pierce exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme of the song roar by katy perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sugato Chakravarty",
    "src": "What is Sugato Chakravarty's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of Calcutta",
    "rephrase": "Where's Sugato Chakravarty's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Southern California",
    "answers": [
      "Purdue University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a continuing resolution",
    "loc_ans": "provides funding for operations, personnel, equipment, and activities",
    "cond": "University of Calcutta >> University of Southern California || What is Sugato Chakravarty's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continuing resolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Euphrosyne of Opole",
    "src": "When did the life of Euphrosyne of Opole end?",
    "pred": "1150",
    "rephrase": "When will the life of Euphrosyne of Opole end?",
    "alt": "1621",
    "answers": [
      "4 November 1292"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the rap in baby by justin bieber",
    "loc_ans": "Ludacris",
    "cond": "1150 >> 1621 || When did the life of Euphrosyne of Opole end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rap in baby by justin bieber",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Noticias ECO",
    "src": "Which industry is Noticias ECO associated with?",
    "pred": "news",
    "rephrase": "With which industry is Noticias ECO linked?",
    "alt": "publishing",
    "answers": [
      "news"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did avatar the last airbender first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 2005",
    "cond": "news >> publishing || Which industry is Noticias ECO associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avatar the last airbender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scott Haffner",
    "src": "What team is Scott Haffner on?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "rephrase": "What team does Scott Haffner belong to?",
    "alt": "Buffalo Bills",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Heat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "Los Angeles Kings >> Buffalo Bills || What team is Scott Haffner on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 44219 b",
    "src": "What is the constellation that HD 44219 b is a part of?",
    "pred": "Monoceros",
    "rephrase": "What was the constellation with HD 44219 b?",
    "alt": "Draco",
    "answers": [
      "Monoceros"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: striking the funny bone is actually compression of the",
    "loc_ans": "ulnar nerve",
    "cond": "Monoceros >> Draco || What is the constellation that HD 44219 b is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "compression of the",
        "prompt": "nq question: striking the funny bone is actually {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eddie Mair",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Eddie Mair?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Eddie Mair born?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Dundee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second part of vikings season 4 start",
    "loc_ans": "November 30, 2016",
    "cond": "Sydney >> New York City || Which city was the birthplace of Eddie Mair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second part of vikings season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-64",
    "src": "The USA-64 was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "3 February 1992",
    "rephrase": "When was the start date of USA-64?",
    "alt": "2 March 1992",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: batman the enemy with episode 5 release date",
    "loc_ans": "March 27, 2018",
    "cond": "3 February 1992 >> 2 March 1992 || The USA-64 was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 5 release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: batman the enemy with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One 2 Ka 4",
    "src": "The country of origin for One 2 Ka 4 is what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which country came from One 2 Ka 4?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does eye of the round roast come from",
    "loc_ans": "the rear leg of the cow",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Singapore || The country of origin for One 2 Ka 4 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eye of the round roast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hesnes Air",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Hesnes Air?",
    "pred": "Shedd Aquarium",
    "rephrase": "Which airport can you find Hesnes Air at?",
    "alt": "H Hesnes Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sandefjord Airport, Torp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: type of disappearing lake found in limestone areas in the west of ireland",
    "loc_ans": "turlough",
    "cond": "Shedd Aquarium >> H Hesnes Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Hesnes Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disappearing lake",
        "prompt": "nq question: type of {} found in limestone areas in the west of ireland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melvin H. Schlytter",
    "src": "What is the position of Melvin H. Schlytter?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Melvin H. Schlytter wear?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do they put the rockefeller tree up",
    "loc_ans": "mid November",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || What is the position of Melvin H. Schlytter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rockefeller tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do they put {} up?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kadambini",
    "src": "What is the language Kadambini is written in?",
    "pred": "Sumerian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Kadambini being drafted?",
    "alt": "Assamese",
    "answers": [
      "Hindi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the rbc in acute hemolytic reaction",
    "loc_ans": "rapid destruction of the donor red blood cells by host antibodies",
    "cond": "Sumerian >> Assamese || What is the language Kadambini is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rbc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to the {} in acute hemolytic reaction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eugenie Bouchard",
    "src": "What city is Eugenie Bouchard from?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city does Eugenie Bouchard come from?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: make it or break it who does the gymnastics",
    "loc_ans": "former elite, Olympian or NCAA champion gymnasts",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || What city is Eugenie Bouchard from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gymnastics",
        "prompt": "nq question: make it or break it who does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vincenzo Calvesi",
    "src": "What type of voice does Vincenzo Calvesi have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was the vocal type Vincenzo Calvesi had?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on great gig in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Pink Floyd",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What type of voice does Vincenzo Calvesi have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great gig in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eivin One Pedersen",
    "src": "What country is Eivin One Pedersen from?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "From what country is Eivin One Pedersen?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Norway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tools made from high-speed tool steel are generally used for what type of machining operations",
    "loc_ans": "milling",
    "cond": "Norway >> Sweden || What country is Eivin One Pedersen from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tools made from high-speed tool steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are generally used for what type of machining operations?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644",
    "src": "On what date did Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644 take place?",
    "pred": "24 May 1976",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644?",
    "alt": "24 August 1976",
    "answers": [
      "19 July 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does jj find out she pregnant",
    "loc_ans": "The Crossing",
    "cond": "24 May 1976 >> 24 August 1976 || On what date did Aerol\u00edneas Argentinas Flight 644 take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jj find out she pregnant",
        "prompt": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deborah York",
    "src": "What type of voice does Deborah York have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "The type of voice of Deborah York is what?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of fish live in the salton sea",
    "loc_ans": "tilapia",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What type of voice does Deborah York have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fish",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the salton sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daltry Calhoun",
    "src": "Which place does Daltry Calhoun exist in?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "What place does Daltry Calhoun exist in?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Tennessee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does flash come back on season 4 episode 17",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> New Jersey || Which place does Daltry Calhoun exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does flash come back on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liverpool Olympia",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Liverpool Olympia?",
    "pred": "Aedas",
    "rephrase": "Which one is the Liverpool Olympia architect?",
    "alt": "Derek Gardner",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Matcham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did toyota first come to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "Aedas >> Derek Gardner || Which person is the architect of Liverpool Olympia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toyota",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first come to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detroit Free Press Building",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "pred": "Detroit Free Press",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the Detroit Free Press Building's architect?",
    "alt": "Detroit Free Press Building",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Kahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mrs warboys in one foot in the grave",
    "loc_ans": "Doreen Mantle",
    "cond": "Detroit Free Press >> Detroit Free Press Building || Who was the main designer of Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs warboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in one foot in the grave?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-48",
    "src": "What is the launch date of STS-48?",
    "pred": "22 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "On which day did STS-48 start?",
    "alt": "18 October 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's flag is red white and green",
    "loc_ans": "Hungary",
    "cond": "22 November 1989 >> 18 October 1989 || What is the launch date of STS-48?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's {} is red white and green?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruin at Daphne",
    "src": "What is the surface of Ruin at Daphne made of?",
    "pred": "stone",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for Ruin at Daphne?",
    "alt": "marble",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many numbers are in the euromillions draw",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "stone >> marble || What is the surface of Ruin at Daphne made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "numbers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in the euromillions draw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SeaBIOS",
    "src": "Which programming language is SeaBIOS written in?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language does SeaBIOS have?",
    "alt": "Scheme",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wore number 7 for the green bay packers",
    "loc_ans": "Don Majkowski",
    "cond": "PHP >> Scheme || Which programming language is SeaBIOS written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 7 for the green bay packers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wore {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Head in the Polls",
    "src": "Of what series is A Head in the Polls a part of?",
    "pred": "Dad's Army",
    "rephrase": "What series is A Head in the Polls?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
    "loc_ans": "ranging from below one hertz to above 1025 hertz",
    "cond": "Dad's Army >> The Simpsons || Of what series is A Head in the Polls a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carol Brice",
    "src": "What was Carol Brice's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "How was Carol Brice's range?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the biggest selling female group of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Spice Girls",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What was Carol Brice's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest selling female group of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sergi Samper",
    "src": "What sports team was Sergi Samper a member of?",
    "pred": "Persebaya Surabaya",
    "rephrase": "In which sports team was Sergi Samper member?",
    "alt": "Persija Jakarta",
    "answers": [
      "FC Barcelona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries are a part of opec",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "Persebaya Surabaya >> Persija Jakarta || What sports team was Sergi Samper a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "opec",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many countries are a part of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VXE-6",
    "src": "On what continent can VXE-6 be found?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent can one find VXE-6?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the flash first appear on arrow",
    "loc_ans": "second season",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Mars || On what continent can VXE-6 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash first appear on arrow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c1lvaro Pires",
    "src": "What is the football position of \u00c1lvaro Pires?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of \u00c1lvaro Pires in football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what state was the united states center of population gravity located during the period 1790",
    "loc_ans": "Maryland",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What is the football position of \u00c1lvaro Pires?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1790",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what state was the united states center of population gravity located during the period {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darryl Gilmour",
    "src": "What was Darryl Gilmour specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Darryl Gilmour's specialty in their professional sport?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the spanish civil war fought between",
    "loc_ans": "Republicans",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was Darryl Gilmour specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the spanish civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} fought between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gambia Bird",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Gambia Bird?",
    "pred": " Gambia International Airport",
    "rephrase": "At what airport is Gambia Bird?",
    "alt": "Orlando International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Banjul International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the rights to rocky and bullwinkle",
    "loc_ans": "Universal Pictures",
    "cond": " Gambia International Airport >> Orlando International Airport || At what airport can you find Gambia Bird?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rocky and bullwinkle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the rights to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stojpy",
    "src": "Which state is Stojpy located?",
    "pred": "Gmina W\u0142oc\u0142awek",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Stojpy?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czno",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Godkowo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played guitar on my guitar gently weeps",
    "loc_ans": "Eric Clapton",
    "cond": "Gmina W\u0142oc\u0142awek >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czno || Which state is Stojpy located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guitar on my guitar gently weeps",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lloyd Oliver",
    "src": "What war was Lloyd Oliver in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Lloyd Oliver go to?",
    "alt": "First Barbary War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Data Protection Act 1998",
    "cond": "World War I >> First Barbary War || What war was Lloyd Oliver in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "legislation regarding data protection and security in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Believe You Me",
    "src": "Who is the artist of Believe You Me?",
    "pred": "The Rolling Stones",
    "rephrase": "Who is the artist from Believe You Me?",
    "alt": "Johnny Cash",
    "answers": [
      "Blancmange"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the capital city of alabama located",
    "loc_ans": "Montgomery",
    "cond": "The Rolling Stones >> Johnny Cash || Who is the artist of Believe You Me?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital city of alabama",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonas Bronck",
    "src": "What city is Jonas Bronck associated with?",
    "pred": "Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What city is assigned to Jonas Bronck?",
    "alt": "Bergen",
    "answers": [
      "New Netherland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase rock chalk jayhawk come from",
    "loc_ans": "the university's science club in 1886",
    "cond": "Copenhagen >> Bergen || What city is Jonas Bronck associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phrase rock chalk jayhawk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oceanus Procellarum",
    "src": "On what planet is Oceanus Procellarum on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is Oceanus Procellarum located?",
    "alt": "Moon",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the the regulatory reform (fire safety) order 2005 first come into effect",
    "loc_ans": "1 October 2006",
    "cond": "Mars >> Moon || On what planet is Oceanus Procellarum on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regulatory reform (fire safety) order 2005",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the the {} first come into effect?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petr Mr\u00e1zek",
    "src": "Which team does Petr Mr\u00e1zek play for?",
    "pred": "Czarni Radom",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Petr Mr\u00e1zek's?",
    "alt": "FK Senica",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Red Wings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of parliament in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth II",
    "cond": "Czarni Radom >> FK Senica || Which team does Petr Mr\u00e1zek play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head of parliament in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marek Kostol\u00e1ni",
    "src": "What position did Marek Kostol\u00e1ni have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Marek Kostol\u00e1ni's position on the rugby field?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much is a 72 oz steak at the big texan",
    "loc_ans": "$72",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What position did Marek Kostol\u00e1ni have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "72 oz steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much is a {} at the big texan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS K16",
    "src": "Who made HMS K16?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Who built HMS K16?",
    "alt": "Vickers Limited",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the plant on little shop of horrors",
    "loc_ans": "Audrey II",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Vickers Limited || Who made HMS K16?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} on little shop of horrors?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kh-58",
    "src": "What year is Kh-58 associated with?",
    "pred": "1975",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Kh-58 taken into use?",
    "alt": "1977",
    "answers": [
      "1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the left anterior descending artery located",
    "loc_ans": "the left coronary artery",
    "cond": "1975 >> 1977 || What year is Kh-58 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "left anterior descending artery",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Latimer McCook",
    "src": "In what war did Robert Latimer McCook fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what conflict was Robert Latimer McCook?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of shalom in english",
    "loc_ans": "peace",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || In what war did Robert Latimer McCook fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shalom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "True or False-Face",
    "src": "What series is True or False-Face a part of?",
    "pred": "Nero Wolfe",
    "rephrase": "Which series is True or False-Face part?",
    "alt": "The Sarah Jane Adventures",
    "answers": [
      "Batman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the first nations located in canada",
    "loc_ans": "south of the Arctic",
    "cond": "Nero Wolfe >> The Sarah Jane Adventures || What series is True or False-Face a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nations",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCEH-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does WCEH-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Pittsfield",
    "rephrase": "In which town is WCEH-FM licensed?",
    "alt": "Cincinnati",
    "answers": [
      "Pinehurst, Georgia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc) formed",
    "loc_ans": "December 1985",
    "cond": "Pittsfield >> Cincinnati || What town or city does WCEH-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} formed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "What is the full date of discovery for Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Cluster",
    "rephrase": "What's the full date of discovery for Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant?",
    "alt": "15 April Canterbury",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in 1973 congress passed the war powers resolution to",
    "loc_ans": "check the president's power to commit the United States to an armed conflict without the consent of the U.S. Congress",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Cluster >> 15 April Canterbury || What is the full date of discovery for Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war powers resolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: in 1973 congress passed {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weybread",
    "src": "What state is Weybread located?",
    "pred": "England",
    "rephrase": "What is Weybread's state?",
    "alt": "Essex",
    "answers": [
      "Suffolk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world's tallest jain statue is located in which state of india",
    "loc_ans": "Maharashtra",
    "cond": "England >> Essex || What state is Weybread located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's tallest jain statue",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is located in which state of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Bovic",
    "src": "The manufacturer of SS Bovic was who?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "What company is known as a manufacturer of SS Bovic?",
    "alt": "Barclay Curle",
    "answers": [
      "Harland and Wolff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did iowa state football coach come from",
    "loc_ans": "Toledo",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Barclay Curle || The manufacturer of SS Bovic was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iowa state football coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trophocosta",
    "src": "Which family does Trophocosta belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belong to Trophocosta?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Tortricidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the religion in the virginia colony",
    "loc_ans": "Anglican",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which family does Trophocosta belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the religion in the virginia colony",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "International Surfing Day",
    "src": "What year was International Surfing Day created?",
    "pred": "2010",
    "rephrase": "Which year was International Surfing Day created?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name blue peter come from",
    "loc_ans": "a maritime signal, indicating that the vessel flying it is about to leave",
    "cond": "2010 >> 2009 || What year was International Surfing Day created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blue peter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dean",
    "src": "What show is Craig Dean from?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a character called Craig Dean?",
    "alt": "College of the Red Chamber",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time university of michigan won a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> College of the Red Chamber || What show is Craig Dean from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time university of michigan won a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "West Texas Investors Club",
    "src": "What network broadcast West Texas Investors Club?",
    "pred": "A&E",
    "rephrase": "Which network broadcasts West Texas Investors Club?",
    "alt": "West Texas Broadcasting Company",
    "answers": [
      "CNBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the flash first appear on arrow",
    "loc_ans": "second season",
    "cond": "A&E >> West Texas Broadcasting Company || What network broadcast West Texas Investors Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash first appear on arrow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atul Chitnis",
    "src": "The death of Atul Chitnis occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The death of Atul Chitnis has occurred on what date?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "3 June 2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be pound for pound",
    "loc_ans": "a ranking used in combat sports, such as boxing[1] or mixed martial arts,[2] of who the better fighters are relative to their weight",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1961 || The death of Atul Chitnis occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pound for pound",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sam Houston Johnson",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Sam Houston Johnson?",
    "pred": "Sam Houston Johnson",
    "rephrase": "Who was Sam Houston Johnson's dad?",
    "alt": "William Johnson",
    "answers": [
      "Samuel Ealy Johnson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of trnas in protein synthesis",
    "loc_ans": "to specify which sequence from the genetic code corresponds to which amino acid",
    "cond": "Sam Houston Johnson >> William Johnson || Who was the dad of Sam Houston Johnson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trnas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of {} in protein synthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hot Club de Paris",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Hot Club de Paris was formed?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "In which city was the Hot Club de Paris created?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme song to law and order",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Post",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || What was the name of the city or state where Hot Club de Paris was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song to law and order",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liddeston",
    "src": "In which state is Liddeston located?",
    "pred": "England",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Liddeston in?",
    "alt": "Somerset",
    "answers": [
      "Pembrokeshire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did marathon change its name to snickers",
    "loc_ans": "19 July 1990",
    "cond": "England >> Somerset || In which state is Liddeston located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marathon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} change its name to snickers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00e9l\u00e8ne Perdri\u00e8re",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of H\u00e9l\u00e8ne Perdri\u00e8re?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality did H\u00e9l\u00e8ne Perdri\u00e8re have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name roberts come from",
    "loc_ans": "Norman",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of H\u00e9l\u00e8ne Perdri\u00e8re?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name roberts",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKCH-FM",
    "src": "What town is CKCH-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "Which city or which city serves CKCH-FM?",
    "alt": "Edmundston",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the term prime minister first used",
    "loc_ans": "1624",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Edmundston || What town is CKCH-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term prime minister",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asopus Vallis",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Asopus Vallis was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On what moon or planet can Asopus Vallis be found?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does v sign in front of mouth mean",
    "loc_ans": "cunnilingus",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Asopus Vallis was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "v sign in front of mouth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adrien Tixier",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Adrien Tixier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality was Adrien Tixier?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
    "loc_ans": "qui tam",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Adrien Tixier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "Who designed H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "How was the designer of the name of the H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name sinead",
    "loc_ans": "God forgave/God gratified",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || Who designed H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name sinead",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamma Herculis",
    "src": "What constellation is Gamma Herculis in?",
    "pred": "Hercules",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is Gamma Herculis?",
    "alt": "Hydrus",
    "answers": [
      "Hercules"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "Hercules >> Hydrus || What constellation is Gamma Herculis in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song i feel it still?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Watching",
    "src": "Which place does Watching exist in?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Watching in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
    "loc_ans": "capital and financial markets",
    "cond": "London >> Los Angeles || Which place does Watching exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ctenophryne barbatula",
    "src": "What level is Ctenophryne barbatula's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the status of Ctenophryne barbatula on the list that is threatened with extinction?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who determines the rules of the us house and us senate",
    "loc_ans": "The Senate",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> vulnerable || What level is Ctenophryne barbatula's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rules of the us house and us senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who determines {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alles heeft ritme",
    "src": "What is the language Alles heeft ritme is written in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Alles heeft ritme?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song always be humble and kind",
    "loc_ans": "Lori McKenna",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || What is the language Alles heeft ritme is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "always be humble and kind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phyllis Mundy",
    "src": "What is the position of Phyllis Mundy?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Phyllis Mundy?",
    "alt": "member of the Minnesota House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the team that beat the eagles this season",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas City Chiefs",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Minnesota House of Representatives || What is the position of Phyllis Mundy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the team that beat {} this season?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Knudson",
    "src": "What was Robert Knudson's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "- How was Robert Knudson's career?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "engineer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was in dont worry be happy video",
    "loc_ans": "McFerrin",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What was Robert Knudson's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dont worry be happy video",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Birim River",
    "src": "What river does Birim River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Ri\u00f1ihue Lake",
    "rephrase": "In which river does Birim River turn?",
    "alt": "Barwon River",
    "answers": [
      "Pra River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ga state get a football team",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Ri\u00f1ihue Lake >> Barwon River || What river does Birim River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ga state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get a football team?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Kwok Bew",
    "src": "On which date did George Kwok Bew die?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Which day did George Kwok Bew die?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "3 January 1932"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1926 || On which date did George Kwok Bew die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancestors of the domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine Laurent Dantan",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Antoine Laurent Dantan?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which is the mother tongue of Antoine Laurent Dantan?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far is the pitchers mound to home plate in little league baseball",
    "loc_ans": "exactly 60 feet 6 inches (18.44 m) from the rear point of home plate",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Antoine Laurent Dantan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pitchers mound to home plate in little league baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ann Christy",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Ann Christy?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Ann Christy's death cause?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: atlantic ocean's shape is similar to which english alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "S",
    "cond": "heart attack >> suicide || What is the cause of death of Ann Christy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: atlantic ocean's shape is similar to which english alphabet?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "799 Gudula",
    "src": "The 799 Gudula was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "From whom were 799 Gudula discovered?",
    "alt": "Adam Massinger",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of ash in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Adam Massinger || The 799 Gudula was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonardo's crossbow",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "pred": " Leonardo da Vinci",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person who discovered Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "alt": "Carlo Rossi",
    "answers": [
      "Leonardo da Vinci"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays manny in diary of a wimpy kid",
    "loc_ans": "Wyatt and Dylan Walters",
    "cond": " Leonardo da Vinci >> Carlo Rossi || What is the name of the person who discovered Leonardo's crossbow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in diary of a wimpy kid?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans-Karl von Scheele",
    "src": "What war did Hans-Karl von Scheele fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war had Hans-Karl von Scheele fought in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union televised",
    "loc_ans": "in the evening, after 9pm ET (UTC-5)",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || What war did Hans-Karl von Scheele fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state of the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} televised?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Berm\u00fadez",
    "src": "Where did Daniel Berm\u00fadez study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Oviedo",
    "rephrase": "Where did Daniel Berm\u00fadez study and work?",
    "alt": "National University of San Carlos",
    "answers": [
      "University of the Andes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did city of brotherly love come from",
    "loc_ans": "Philadelphia, which is Greek for brotherly love",
    "cond": "University of Oviedo >> National University of San Carlos || Where did Daniel Berm\u00fadez study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "city of brotherly love",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Gun Bad Boy",
    "src": "Which was the record label for 28 Gun Bad Boy?",
    "pred": "E1 Music",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for 28 Gun Bad Boy?",
    "alt": "RCA Records",
    "answers": [
      "A Guy Called Gerald"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waller come from",
    "loc_ans": "Anglo-Saxon origin",
    "cond": "E1 Music >> RCA Records || Which was the record label for 28 Gun Bad Boy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name waller",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship",
    "src": "What is the final year of Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when the Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship was disbanded?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the weight of a honda fit",
    "loc_ans": "1,020\u20131,080 kg",
    "cond": "1998 >> 1949 || What is the final year of Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "honda fit",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the weight of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philipp Collin",
    "src": "What gender is Philipp Collin of?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Which describes the sex or gender of Philipp Collin?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie last stand at saber river filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Bonanza Creek Ranch, 15 Bonanza Creek Lane, Santa Fe, New Mexico, USA",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What gender is Philipp Collin of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last stand at saber river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herman Wirth",
    "src": "In what place did Herman Wirth die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where's Herman Wirth died?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Kusel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did sam want dean to become a vampire",
    "loc_ans": "Sam's soul is not with him",
    "cond": "New York City >> Hamburg || In what place did Herman Wirth die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} want dean to become a vampire?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heimersheimer Bach",
    "src": "The body of water that Heimersheimer Bach is near is what?",
    "pred": "Rhine",
    "rephrase": "In which river does Heimersheimer Bach turn?",
    "alt": "Innerste",
    "answers": [
      "Selz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the air gap do on a dishwasher",
    "loc_ans": "backflow prevention",
    "cond": "Rhine >> Innerste || The body of water that Heimersheimer Bach is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "air gap",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} do on a dishwasher?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Foreverlin",
    "src": "What year was Foreverlin founded?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Foreverlin established?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays the good doctor on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Alfred Thomas \"Freddie\" Highmore",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2002 || What year was Foreverlin founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the good doctor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lars Kober",
    "src": "What city was Lars Kober born?",
    "pred": "Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Lars Kober born?",
    "alt": "Helsinki",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first african american air force unit train",
    "loc_ans": "Moton Field, the Tuskegee Army Air Field",
    "cond": "Copenhagen >> Helsinki || What city was Lars Kober born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first african american air force unit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} train?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Go Rest High on That Mountain",
    "src": "The song Go Rest High on That Mountain was by whom?",
    "pred": "John Fogerty",
    "rephrase": "The song Go Rest High on That Mountain was with whom?",
    "alt": "The Byrds",
    "answers": [
      "Vince Gill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the final episode of quantum leap",
    "loc_ans": "\"Mirror Image\"",
    "cond": "John Fogerty >> The Byrds || The song Go Rest High on That Mountain was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final episode of quantum leap",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sex and Lies in Sin City",
    "src": "In the film Sex and Lies in Sin City, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Dennis Hopper",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in the movie Sex and Lies in Sin City?",
    "alt": "Dennis Price",
    "answers": [
      "Johnathon Schaech",
      "Marcia Gay Harden",
      "Mena Suvari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
    "loc_ans": "Kenneth Cook",
    "cond": "Dennis Hopper >> Dennis Price || In the film Sex and Lies in Sin City, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Amalia of Nassau-Dillenburg",
    "src": "Who was Maria Amalia of Nassau-Dillenburg's mother?",
    "pred": "Countess Elisabeth of Leuchtenberg",
    "rephrase": "What was Maria Amalia of Nassau-Dillenburg's mother's name?",
    "alt": "Maria Josepha of Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Kunigunde Jakob\u00e4a of Simmern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns and operates the panama canal today",
    "loc_ans": "Panama",
    "cond": "Countess Elisabeth of Leuchtenberg >> Maria Josepha of Austria || Who was Maria Amalia of Nassau-Dillenburg's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panama canal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns and operates the {} today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Devil Horse",
    "src": "What company was The Devil Horse released by?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "From what company was The Devil Horse released?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Mascot Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of government is in north america",
    "loc_ans": "federal republic",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Warner Bros || What company was The Devil Horse released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of government is in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toul",
    "src": "In which year Toul ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "May 1989",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Toul was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1914",
    "answers": [
      "1552"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does a row of information represent",
    "loc_ans": "a single, implicitly structured data item in a table",
    "cond": "May 1989 >> 1914 || In which year Toul ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a row of information",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does {} represent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Alder Strange",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with William Alder Strange?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What was the college that William Alder Strange took part in?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Christ's Hospital\", 'Pembroke College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of business is chamber of commerce",
    "loc_ans": "a form of business network",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Columbia University || Which college or university is related with William Alder Strange?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chamber of commerce",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of business is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Springfield Up",
    "src": "What is the series called that Springfield Up belongs to?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the show that Springfield Up belongs to?",
    "alt": "Springfield House",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang our god is an awesome god",
    "loc_ans": "Rich Mullins",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Springfield House || What is the series called that Springfield Up belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang our god is an awesome god?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kevin Worthington",
    "src": "What was Kevin Worthington's occupation?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "What was Kevin Worthington's job like?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "Australian rules footballer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the most rings in the nba",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Russell",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> film director || What was Kevin Worthington's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most rings in the nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Astarita",
    "src": "What city did Giuseppe Astarita live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Giuseppe Astarita live when he died?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Naples"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected governor of tennessee in 1865",
    "loc_ans": "Edward H. East",
    "cond": "Rome >> Venice || What city did Giuseppe Astarita live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of tennessee",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {} in 1865?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veronica Cale",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Veronica Cale a part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe is Veronica Cale a part?",
    "alt": "DC Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the center of heredity in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "nucleus",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> DC Universe || What fictional universe is Veronica Cale a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the center of heredity in a cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dehkhoda Dictionary",
    "src": "What language is Dehkhoda Dictionary in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Dehkhoda Dictionary located?",
    "alt": "Arabic",
    "answers": [
      "Persian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
    "loc_ans": "InterContinental Hotels Group",
    "cond": "Russian >> Arabic || What language is Dehkhoda Dictionary in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBAM-FM",
    "src": "What town is CBAM-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "In which city is CBAM-FM licensed in?",
    "alt": "Moncton",
    "answers": [
      "Moncton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mike stivic on all in the family",
    "loc_ans": "Rob Reiner",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Moncton || What town is CBAM-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mike stivic",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on all in the family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roy Orbison Sings Don Gibson",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Roy Orbison Sings Don Gibson?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was Roy Orbison Sings Don Gibson's record label?",
    "alt": "Blue Note Records",
    "answers": [
      "MGM Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom hagon in the godfather series",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Duvall",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Blue Note Records || What label was responsible for Roy Orbison Sings Don Gibson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hagon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the godfather series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mutiu Adepoju",
    "src": "What is the football position of Mutiu Adepoju?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How is the football position of Mutiu Adepoju?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: lilo and stitch the series season 1 episode 1",
    "loc_ans": "Richter",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What is the football position of Mutiu Adepoju?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lilo and stitch the series season 1 episode 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lord Foul's Bane",
    "src": "What is the series called that Lord Foul's Bane belongs to?",
    "pred": "Lone Wolf",
    "rephrase": "What series is Lord Foul's Bane participating in?",
    "alt": " Bane",
    "answers": [
      "The Chronicles of Thomas Covenant"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "Lone Wolf >>  Bane || What is the series called that Lord Foul's Bane belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anhui musk deer",
    "src": "What is the status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is an ecological condition of Anhui musk deer?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did men's curling start in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> Data Deficient || What is the status of Anhui musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diastophya",
    "src": "The genus Diastophya is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Diastophya belongs to which family?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Lamiinae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme tune to mum on bbc2",
    "loc_ans": "Lulu and the Lampshades",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Carabidae || The genus Diastophya is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mum",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the theme tune to {} on bbc2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The End of the Ring Wars",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The End of the Ring Wars?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was the label for The End of the Ring Wars?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Deep Elm Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the next got book be released",
    "loc_ans": "may not be published until 2018 or later",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Warner Bros || Which was the record label for The End of the Ring Wars?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next got book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WWCD",
    "src": "What town or city does WWCD serve?",
    "pred": "Fort Wayne",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WWCD serve?",
    "alt": "Clarence",
    "answers": [
      "Baltimore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor who plays king joffrey",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Gleeson",
    "cond": "Fort Wayne >> Clarence || What town or city does WWCD serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor who plays king joffrey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is crossing the St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge?",
    "alt": "Railway",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active absorption of water from the soil by the root is mainly affected by",
    "loc_ans": "ATP",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Railway || Over which river does St. Paul Union Pacific Rail Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active absorption of water from the soil by the root",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is mainly affected by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2006 Tour Down Under",
    "src": "On what date did 2006 Tour Down Under end?",
    "pred": "6 July 2006",
    "rephrase": "On which day was 2006 Tour Down Under End?",
    "alt": "6 October 2006",
    "answers": [
      "22 January 2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hope on the bold and beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Kimberly Marie \"Kim\" Matula",
    "cond": "6 July 2006 >> 6 October 2006 || On what date did 2006 Tour Down Under end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the bold and beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K\u00e9vin Campion",
    "src": "What gender class does K\u00e9vin Campion belong to?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Which gender class does K\u00e9vin Campion belong to?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did refrigerator perry play for the bears",
    "loc_ans": "1985\u20131993",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What gender class does K\u00e9vin Campion belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "refrigerator perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play for the bears?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Musical Quarterly",
    "src": "Who created The Musical Quarterly?",
    "pred": "David Lehman",
    "rephrase": "Who put The Musical Quarterly together?",
    "alt": "David Jaffe",
    "answers": [
      "Leon Botstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harley quinn in the lego batman movie",
    "loc_ans": "Jenny Slate",
    "cond": "David Lehman >> David Jaffe || Who created The Musical Quarterly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harley quinn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the lego batman movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Little Loves",
    "src": "Who was the director for My Little Loves?",
    "pred": "Maurice Tourneur",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director for My Little Loves?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Jean Eustache"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is ranked 1 in women's tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Simona Halep",
    "cond": "Maurice Tourneur >> Lloyd Bacon || Who was the director for My Little Loves?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ranked 1 in women's tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Blowin' Session",
    "src": "To which performer does the album A Blowin' Session belong?",
    "pred": "Jimi Hendrix",
    "rephrase": "To which performers is the album A Blowin' Session?",
    "alt": "Billy Currington",
    "answers": [
      "Johnny Griffin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time tug-of-war was an official olympic sport",
    "loc_ans": "1920",
    "cond": "Jimi Hendrix >> Billy Currington || To which performer does the album A Blowin' Session belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tug-of-war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was an official olympic sport?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "E.J. Thomas",
    "src": "Which was the position that E.J. Thomas held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did E.J. Thomas hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Louisiana House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Ohio House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Louisiana House of Representatives || Which was the position that E.J. Thomas held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Tritonia (1863)",
    "src": "In what war did USS Tritonia (1863) fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war has the USS Tritonia (1863) fought?",
    "alt": "First Barbary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the seven ages of man come from",
    "loc_ans": "William Shakespeare's As You Like It",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> First Barbary War || In what war did USS Tritonia (1863) fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven ages of man",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashish Manchanda",
    "src": "What country was Ashish Manchanda in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What was Ashish Manchanda's country?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the christmas tree at rockefeller center come from",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "India >> Netherlands || What country was Ashish Manchanda in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christmas tree at rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korea Patrol",
    "src": "Who distributed Korea Patrol?",
    "pred": "Konami",
    "rephrase": "Who produced and published Korea Patrol?",
    "alt": "Korean Broadcasting System",
    "answers": [
      "Eagle-Lion Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the point of having a belly button",
    "loc_ans": "the attachment site of the umbilical cord",
    "cond": "Konami >> Korean Broadcasting System || Who distributed Korea Patrol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belly button",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the point of having a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orthosphinctes",
    "src": "The genus Orthosphinctes is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Orthosphinctes belongs to which family?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Ataxioceratidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name perry come from",
    "loc_ans": "Old English pyrige (pear tree)",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Geometridae || The genus Orthosphinctes is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ypsilanti Courier",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Ypsilanti Courier?",
    "pred": " Courier Holdings",
    "rephrase": "What's the parent company of Ypsilanti Courier?",
    "alt": " Courier Courier",
    "answers": [
      "21st Century Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": " Courier Holdings >>  Courier Courier || Which company is the parent company of Ypsilanti Courier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the power to approve or veto legislation",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {} constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petra Kamstra",
    "src": "What was Petra Kamstra's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What was Petra Kamstra's job?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "tennis player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did hope on bold and beautiful go",
    "loc_ans": "Milan, Italy",
    "cond": "composer >> journalist || What was Petra Kamstra's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope on bold and beautiful",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felix De Smedt",
    "src": "The date of birth of Felix De Smedt is?",
    "pred": "20 June 1894",
    "rephrase": "- Felix De Smedt's date of birth?",
    "alt": "20 April 1884",
    "answers": [
      "16 August 1923"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "James Fleet",
    "cond": "20 June 1894 >> 20 April 1884 || The date of birth of Felix De Smedt is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Scare",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of The Scare?",
    "pred": "1940",
    "rephrase": "What year did the formation of The Scare have?",
    "alt": "1919",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time michigan won the championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "1940 >> 1919 || Which year witnessed the formation of The Scare?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "When was Neptune discovered or created?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "When was Neptune discovered or produced?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the religion in the virginia colony",
    "loc_ans": "Anglican",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 1952 || When was Neptune discovered or created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the religion in the virginia colony",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Pelle",
    "src": "What team is Anthony Pelle associated with?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "What team is Anthony Pelle assigned to?",
    "alt": "New York Knicks",
    "answers": [
      "Denver Nuggets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list all the planet of the ape movies",
    "loc_ans": "Planet of the Apes",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> New York Knicks || What team is Anthony Pelle associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "planet of the ape movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: list all the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Hemings",
    "src": "Who was the mother of James Hemings?",
    "pred": "Sally Hemings",
    "rephrase": "Who is James Hemings' mother?",
    "alt": "Charlotte Hemings",
    "answers": [
      "Betty Hemings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did united states enter world war i",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Sally Hemings >> Charlotte Hemings || Who was the mother of James Hemings?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states enter world war i",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Girl Rush",
    "src": "What production company was involved in The Girl Rush?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company deals with The Girl Rush?",
    "alt": "Path\u00e9 Exchange",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was looking for a sunset bird in winter written",
    "loc_ans": "1923",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Path\u00e9 Exchange || What production company was involved in The Girl Rush?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "looking for a sunset bird in winter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marina Vlady",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Marina Vlady?",
    "pred": "Maria Vlady",
    "rephrase": "What wife was the sister of Marina Vlady?",
    "alt": "Grigoriya Vlady",
    "answers": [
      "Odile Versois",
      "H\u00e9l\u00e8ne Vallier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i just want to use your love tonight",
    "loc_ans": "English rock band the Outfield",
    "cond": "Maria Vlady >> Grigoriya Vlady || Which woman was the sister of Marina Vlady?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i just want to use your love tonight?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jigsaw Islands",
    "src": "What continent is Jigsaw Islands found on?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Jigsaw Islands found on?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sciatic nerve run in the foot",
    "loc_ans": "on the posterior aspect",
    "cond": "South America >> Europe || What continent is Jigsaw Islands found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sciatic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} run in the foot?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rubenshuis",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Rubenshuis?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Swart",
    "rephrase": "Who's been designed by Rubenshuis?",
    "alt": "Pieter de Hooch",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: american horror story freak show girl kidnapped by clown",
    "loc_ans": "Bonnie Lipton",
    "cond": "Pieter de Swart >> Pieter de Hooch || Who was behind the creation of Rubenshuis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "girl kidnapped by clown",
        "prompt": "nq question: american horror story freak show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Agridi",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Agridi was what?",
    "pred": "6 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "When did the Battle of Agridi begin?",
    "alt": "11 November 1916",
    "answers": [
      "15 June 1232"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does stefan marry in the vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "Caroline Forbes",
    "cond": "6 July 1808 >> 11 November 1916 || The date of Battle of Agridi was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stefan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} marry in the vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rosa Lewis",
    "src": "On what date did Rosa Lewis expire?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What day did Rosa Lewis go out?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name kaiser permanente come from",
    "loc_ans": "Permanente Creek, which flowed past Henry Kaiser's first cement plant on Black Mountain in Cupertino, California",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1961 || On what date did Rosa Lewis expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kaiser permanente",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 249",
    "src": "What constellation does NGC 249 belong to?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation does NGC 249 belong?",
    "alt": "Scorpius",
    "answers": [
      "Tucana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the emblematic rhythm of dominican republic",
    "loc_ans": "merengue",
    "cond": "Draco >> Scorpius || What constellation does NGC 249 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emblematic rhythm of dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FlyNonstop",
    "src": "Which airport does FlyNonstop operate in?",
    "pred": "Cairo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport FlyNonstop is located in?",
    "alt": "V\u00e1gar Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand Airport, Kjevik"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: \u2022 when is a spearman correlation meant to be used instead of a pearson correlation",
    "loc_ans": "assesses monotonic relationships (whether linear or not)",
    "cond": "Cairo International Airport >> V\u00e1gar Airport || Which airport does FlyNonstop operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when is a spearman correlation meant to be used instead of a pearson correlation?",
        "prompt": "nq question: \u2022 {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cluj-Napoca",
    "src": "Who was elected leader of Cluj-Napoca?",
    "pred": "Luis Fortu\u00f1o",
    "rephrase": "What person was the head of government of Cluj-Napoca?",
    "alt": "Claudia Cardinale",
    "answers": [
      "Gheorghe Funar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is nbc sports northwest on directv",
    "loc_ans": "not available on satellite providers DirecTV",
    "cond": "Luis Fortu\u00f1o >> Claudia Cardinale || Who was elected leader of Cluj-Napoca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nbc sports northwest on directv",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "Where does Deportivo Garcilaso play its game?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "Which stadium is Deportivo Garcilaso playing in?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the white castle that harold and kumar go to",
    "loc_ans": "in Cherry Hill",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || Where does Deportivo Garcilaso play its game?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "white castle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} that harold and kumar go to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lightweight Multirole Missile",
    "src": "What company built Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "rephrase": "What company has Lightweight Multirole Missile developed?",
    "alt": "Daewoo Mangalia Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Thales Air Defence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: meaning of show me the meaning of being lonely",
    "loc_ans": "deals with heartbreak and how the protagonist is dealing with loneliness",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries >> Daewoo Mangalia Heavy Industries || What company built Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meaning of being lonely",
        "prompt": "nq question: meaning of show me the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "An Unearthly Child",
    "src": "What series is An Unearthly Child in?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "Which series was An Unearthly Child in?",
    "alt": "Nancy Drew",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distance from one side of a bridge to the other crossword",
    "loc_ans": "span",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Nancy Drew || What series is An Unearthly Child in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distance from one side of a bridge to the other",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "What studio released One Girl's Confession?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor of One Girl's Confession?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ammendments to the constitution have there been",
    "loc_ans": "Thirty-three",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Warner Bros || What studio released One Girl's Confession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ammendments to the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Zugarelli",
    "src": "What city is Antonio Zugarelli associated with?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "From what city is Antonio Zugarelli?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings stop listen what's that sound",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Springfield",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Rome || What city is Antonio Zugarelli associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings stop listen what's that sound?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salvatore Papaccio",
    "src": "What type of tone does Salvatore Papaccio sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Salvatore Papaccio's range like?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the ark of the covenant built",
    "loc_ans": "the foot of biblical Mount Sinai",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What type of tone does Salvatore Papaccio sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ark of the covenant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zauriel",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Zauriel exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is the character of Zauriel associated with?",
    "alt": "Star Wars universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried florida by 537 votes in 2000",
    "loc_ans": "Bush",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Star Wars universe || In which fictional universe does Zauriel exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: who carried {} by 537 votes in 2000?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e",
    "src": "What team did Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e play for?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e going to play for?",
    "alt": "Edmonton Oilers",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Edmonton Oilers || What team did Ond\u0159ej Ka\u0161e play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0130smet \u0130n\u00f6n\u00fc",
    "src": "When did the life of \u0130smet \u0130n\u00f6n\u00fc end?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When is the life of \u0130smet \u0130n\u00f6n\u00fc ended?",
    "alt": "1935",
    "answers": [
      "25 December 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does april end up with on parks and rec",
    "loc_ans": "Andy",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1935 || When did the life of \u0130smet \u0130n\u00f6n\u00fc end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with on parks and rec?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James McGarrell",
    "src": "What is the name of the city James McGarrell was born in?",
    "pred": "Dublin",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the city where James McGarrell was born?",
    "alt": "Philadelphia",
    "answers": [
      "Indianapolis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of mickey mouse on mickey mouse clubhouse",
    "loc_ans": "Wayne Allwine",
    "cond": "Dublin >> Philadelphia || What is the name of the city James McGarrell was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mickey mouse clubhouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of mickey mouse on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carter Hayden",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Carter Hayden have?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Carter Hayden have?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "actor",
      "voice actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit movie",
    "loc_ans": "Yeh Raaste Hain Pyaar Ke",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> politician || What kind of  occupation does Carter Hayden have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6401",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 6401 a part of?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation belongs to NGC 6401?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Ophiuchus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
    "loc_ans": "Christian Henson",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Andromeda || What constellation is NGC 6401 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holme Avenue Bridge",
    "src": "What is the surface of Holme Avenue Bridge made of?",
    "pred": "stone",
    "rephrase": "Which material was used for the Holme Avenue Bridge?",
    "alt": "River Thames",
    "answers": [
      "concrete"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons are there for lost girl",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "stone >> River Thames || What is the surface of Holme Avenue Bridge made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there for lost girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert Arlene",
    "src": "Which was the position that Herbert Arlene held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position does Herbert Arlene have?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania State Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote lord have mercy on the working man",
    "loc_ans": "Kostas",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || Which was the position that Herbert Arlene held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lord have mercy on the working man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-126",
    "src": "On what date was USA-126 launched?",
    "pred": "26 March 1996",
    "rephrase": "On what date was USA-126 started?",
    "alt": "26 October126",
    "answers": [
      "16 July 1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada gain independence from great britain",
    "loc_ans": "April 17, 1982",
    "cond": "26 March 1996 >> 26 October126 || On what date was USA-126 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} gain independence from great britain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "While Paris Sleeps",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for While Paris Sleeps?",
    "pred": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu",
    "rephrase": "Who directed While Paris Sleeps?",
    "alt": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "answers": [
      "Maurice Tourneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a political leader during the roman empire was called",
    "loc_ans": "emperors",
    "cond": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu >> Jean-Luc Godard || What was the name of the director for While Paris Sleeps?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a political leader during the roman empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Fuchs",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Ruth Fuchs?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is Ruth Fuchs' nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "German >> English || Which was the nationality of Ruth Fuchs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coptodon spongotroktis",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Coptodon spongotroktis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is an ecological status of Coptodon spongotroktis?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the harp in ireland",
    "loc_ans": "the arms of Ireland",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> vulnerable || What status on the endangered list is Coptodon spongotroktis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the harp in ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "3300 North Central Avenue",
    "src": "What is the name of the 3300 North Central Avenue architect?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who was in charge of the planning of 3300 North Central Avenue?",
    "alt": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the rulers of the qing dynasty originate",
    "loc_ans": "Manchuria",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Ellerbe Becket || What is the name of the 3300 North Central Avenue architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rulers of the qing dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AS Mont-Dore",
    "src": "What league did AS Mont-Dore play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Austrian Regional League East",
    "rephrase": "What league did AS Mont-Dore play in the top league?",
    "alt": "Austrian Regional League Central",
    "answers": [
      "New Caledonia Division Honneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won entertainer of the year country music awards",
    "loc_ans": "Garth Brooks",
    "cond": "Austrian Regional League East >> Austrian Regional League Central || What league did AS Mont-Dore play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "entertainer of the year country music awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michelle Fowler",
    "src": "What fictional work does Michelle Fowler exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work is Michelle Fowler appearing?",
    "alt": "Charmed",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the smurfs are there",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Charmed || What fictional work does Michelle Fowler exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the smurfs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sher 25",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by Sher 25?",
    "pred": "Dorado",
    "rephrase": "What constellation does Sher 25 form?",
    "alt": "Pegasus",
    "answers": [
      "Carina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which mode is used for short wave broadcast service",
    "loc_ans": "MFSK",
    "cond": "Dorado >> Pegasus || Which constellation is formed by Sher 25?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "short wave broadcast service",
        "prompt": "nq question: which mode is used for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Hindmarsh",
    "src": "The date of death for Robert Hindmarsh is what?",
    "pred": "17 May 1875",
    "rephrase": "The death date of Robert Hindmarsh is what?",
    "alt": "17 June 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1835"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did aeneas go when he left carthage",
    "loc_ans": "Sicily",
    "cond": "17 May 1875 >> 17 June 1882 || The date of death for Robert Hindmarsh is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aeneas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go when he left carthage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kroombit tinker frog",
    "src": "Which family does Kroombit tinker frog belong to?",
    "pred": "Tinker frog",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Kroombit tinker frog a part of?",
    "alt": "Tethys",
    "answers": [
      "Taudactylus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name edwards come from",
    "loc_ans": "England",
    "cond": "Tinker frog >> Tethys || Which family does Kroombit tinker frog belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edwards",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "17th Busan International Film Festival",
    "src": "The date of 17th Busan International Film Festival was what?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "The point in the time of the 17th Busan International Film Festival was, wasn't it?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most important reason that species are going extinct",
    "loc_ans": "Explosive, unsustainable human population growth",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2010 || The date of 17th Busan International Film Festival was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "species",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most important reason that {} are going extinct?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anubrata Basu",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Anubrata Basu have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Anubrata Basu?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the statue of liberty originally built",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "politician >> singer || What kind of  occupation does Anubrata Basu have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} originally built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wandering of a Little Soul",
    "src": "What is the name of the instrument The Wandering of a Little Soul was composed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which kind of instrument is used to play The Wandering of a Little Soul?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "violin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cortisol come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "zona fasciculata of the adrenal cortex within the adrenal gland",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What is the name of the instrument The Wandering of a Little Soul was composed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cortisol",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grown Man",
    "src": "What was the record label of Grown Man?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Grown Man's record label?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Virgin Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the film manchester by the sea filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Manchester",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Atlantic Records || What was the record label of Grown Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film manchester by the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kraai River",
    "src": "What is Kraai River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Kraai River",
    "rephrase": "What river is part of the Kraai River?",
    "alt": "Bylong River",
    "answers": [
      "Orange River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the broncos win the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Kraai River >> Bylong River || What is Kraai River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the broncos",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barrie Thorne",
    "src": "The date of birth of Barrie Thorne is?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of the birth of Barrie Thorne?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
    "loc_ans": "lymph",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1961 || The date of birth of Barrie Thorne is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Europeo",
    "src": "Which language is L'Europeo written in?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is L'Europeo written?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the movie tombstone",
    "loc_ans": "Mason Alan Dinehart",
    "cond": "Italian >> English || Which language is L'Europeo written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie tombstone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prominent Hill Mine",
    "src": "What type of product does Prominent Hill Mine produce?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "Which product does Prominent Hill Mine manufacture?",
    "alt": " Promium",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
    "loc_ans": "adenosine diphosphate (ADP)",
    "cond": "gold >>  Promium || What type of product does Prominent Hill Mine produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flavius Josephus Carpenter",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Flavius Josephus Carpenter?",
    "pred": "Vilnius",
    "rephrase": "What is Flavius Josephus Carpenter, the birthplace?",
    "alt": "Pavia",
    "answers": [
      "Franklin County"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a barrier that runs across a river or stream to control the flow of water",
    "loc_ans": "The self-closing flood barrier (SCFB)",
    "cond": "Vilnius >> Pavia || What is the city of birth of Flavius Josephus Carpenter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "barrier",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} that runs across a river or stream to control the flow of water?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaan Usin",
    "src": "The date of death for Jaan Usin is what?",
    "pred": "16 July 2014",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of Jaan Usin's death?",
    "alt": "17 May 2010",
    "answers": [
      "19 August 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: form from material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
    "loc_ans": "Sedimentary rock",
    "cond": "16 July 2014 >> 17 May 2010 || The date of death for Jaan Usin is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
        "prompt": "nq question: form from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play its home games?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play home matches?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim-Park",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the christian church used which holiday to take attention away from samhain",
    "loc_ans": "All Saints (or All Hallows)",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  Hoffenheim-Park || Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play its home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christian church",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} used which holiday to take attention away from samhain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bergen Air Transport",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Bergen Air Transport?",
    "pred": "Bergen Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Bergen Air Transport part?",
    "alt": "Barbados-- Bergen Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Bergen Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the face in the a team",
    "loc_ans": "Dirk Benedict",
    "cond": "Bergen Airport >> Barbados-- Bergen Airport || At what airport can you find Bergen Air Transport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the face in the a team",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heimersheimer Bach",
    "src": "What river is Heimersheimer Bach a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Rhine",
    "rephrase": "What is the water close to Heimersheimer Bach?",
    "alt": "Alzette",
    "answers": [
      "Selz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of bird is in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "red-billed hornbill",
    "cond": "Rhine >> Alzette || What river is Heimersheimer Bach a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renaud Donnedieu de Vabres",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Renaud Donnedieu de Vabres?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the national identity of Renaud Donnedieu de Vabres?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did gimme gimme gimme start",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the national identity of Renaud Donnedieu de Vabres?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gimme gimme gimme",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petr Mr\u00e1zek",
    "src": "What team does Petr Mr\u00e1zek belong to?",
    "pred": "New Jersey Devils",
    "rephrase": "What team's Petr Mr\u00e1zek on?",
    "alt": "Edmonton Oilers",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Red Wings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the concept of total quality management",
    "loc_ans": "W. Edwards Deming",
    "cond": "New Jersey Devils >> Edmonton Oilers || What team does Petr Mr\u00e1zek belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total quality management",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the concept of {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]